{"id": "0", "question": "-692 - 705 ", "answer": "-1397", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1", "question": "803276 * -522885 - -436674 * 398318 * -50794 ", "answer": "-8835280218350868", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2", "question": "-63 + 11 - 52 ", "answer": "-104", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3", "question": "-24384 * -65572 + -36155 * -35962 ", "answer": "2899113758", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4", "question": "-92 + -80 + 32 + 39 - 16 ", "answer": "-117", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5", "question": "-4781 + -6323 ", "answer": "-11104", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6", "question": "-74 + -85 + 68 + 88 ", "answer": "-3", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7", "question": "-51 * 98 + 35 * -70 - 53 ", "answer": "-7501", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8", "question": "751 * 68 + -176 ", "answer": "50892", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9", "question": "-223533 - -430696 + 226752 ", "answer": "433915", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "10", "question": "573 * 101 ", "answer": "57873", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "11", "question": "-7093 * 7977 ", "answer": "-56580861", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "12", "question": "-479 * 81 * 595 + -708 ", "answer": "-23086113", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "13", "question": "31 - 39 * 53 * 39 - -66 ", "answer": "-80516", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "14", "question": "-484351 - 823321 * -348808 * -697856 ", "answer": "-200410949998351359", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "15", "question": "-324 - 809 ", "answer": "-1133", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "16", "question": "1934 + -3984 - -4985 ", "answer": "2935", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "17", "question": "905 * -295 ", "answer": "-266975", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "18", "question": "4980 + 3467 - 9671 ", "answer": "-1224", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "19", "question": "86800 * 40095 - 24576 ", "answer": "3480221424", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "20", "question": "-636678 + -871857 ", "answer": "-1508535", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "21", "question": "-46 * -87 + 0 - -24 - -25 ", "answer": "4051", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "22", "question": "-79022 * 664706 - 827344 * 482685 - -674443 ", "answer": "-451872261729", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "23", "question": "33 - 45 + 25 + -63 + -28 ", "answer": "-78", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "24", "question": "1288 + -8662 - 5579 - 7117 ", "answer": "-20070", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "25", "question": "51131 * -28244 + 60310 * -45228 - -84992 ", "answer": "-4171759652", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "26", "question": "-18 + -37 ", "answer": "-55", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "27", "question": "-96094 + 39166 + -75842 + -78159 * -68131 ", "answer": "5324918059", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "28", "question": "-6123 - 4062 ", "answer": "-10185", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "29", "question": "-13111 * -11981 - -97015 ", "answer": "157179906", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "30", "question": "44479 - 29589 ", "answer": "14890", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "31", "question": "-4380 * -6403 ", "answer": "28045140", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "32", "question": "7 - -42 - -17 ", "answer": "66", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "33", "question": "77371 + 30076 * -51854 * -53884 - 3702 ", "answer": "84035379824805", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "34", "question": "-28867 * 20632 + -82784 * -66765 * -17772 ", "answer": "-98227750446664", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "35", "question": "31762 + -21817 ", "answer": "9945", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "36", "question": "82978 * -36737 + -65088 - 40761 ", "answer": "-3048468635", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "37", "question": "93164 * -71833 ", "answer": "-6692249612", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "38", "question": "-5823 - 6976 * -7528 + 6238 + 3560 ", "answer": "52519303", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "39", "question": "883537 - -393109 - 228321 ", "answer": "1048325", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "40", "question": "-693583 * 64342 ", "answer": "-44626517386", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "41", "question": "-372 * -39 - -790 * 283 ", "answer": "238078", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "42", "question": "843480 * -628548 ", "answer": "-530167667040", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "43", "question": "-31667 * -65879 + -21250 ", "answer": "2086169043", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "44", "question": "882054 + 543229 - 532291 - 942206 + 191362 ", "answer": "142148", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "45", "question": "131 + -926 - -3902 ", "answer": "3107", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "46", "question": "80105 + -420659 + 704948 + -933815 - 141599 ", "answer": "-711020", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "47", "question": "-305 * -948 * -708 + 722 ", "answer": "-204710398", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "48", "question": "-760184 * -954271 - -904413 ", "answer": "725422450277", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "49", "question": "-74 - 79 + -83 * -51 * -77 ", "answer": "-326094", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "50", "question": "137 + -445 ", "answer": "-308", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "51", "question": "412783 + -212527 ", "answer": "200256", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "52", "question": "57586 * 97174 + 55981 - -14409 - -27419 ", "answer": "5595959773", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "53", "question": "639 * -454 - -735 ", "answer": "-289371", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "54", "question": "9767 + 6524 * 8901 - -9769 ", "answer": "58089660", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "55", "question": "-52585 + -16423 * -53215 * -85965 ", "answer": "-75129107074510", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "56", "question": "84714 - -229228 ", "answer": "313942", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "57", "question": "639 + 965 + 252 * 271 * -469 ", "answer": "-32027344", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "58", "question": "337 + -274 + -332 - -571 + 350 ", "answer": "652", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "59", "question": "893269 - -765477 ", "answer": "1658746", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "60", "question": "-4030 * -5336 + 8620 + -6035 - -9309 ", "answer": "21515974", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "61", "question": "107 + -461 * 410 ", "answer": "-188903", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "62", "question": "-69 * 47 - 18 + -27 ", "answer": "-3288", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "63", "question": "33 * 69 * -51 * -39 * 40 ", "answer": "181158120", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "64", "question": "-200592 - 377056 ", "answer": "-577648", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "65", "question": "76171 * 29161 - 53141 + -6520 ", "answer": "2221162870", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "66", "question": "-70 + -61 * -29 ", "answer": "1699", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "67", "question": "-77 + 35 - -2 ", "answer": "-40", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "68", "question": "-775042 + 783541 ", "answer": "8499", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "69", "question": "83 - 27 ", "answer": "56", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "70", "question": "74 * 93 ", "answer": "6882", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "71", "question": "2507 - -3493 ", "answer": "6000", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "72", "question": "-2 - 335 ", "answer": "-337", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "73", "question": "-514 + 299 ", "answer": "-215", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "74", "question": "2031 * -1242 + 8646 - 7500 - 993 ", "answer": "-2522349", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "75", "question": "254465 + -804397 + -504652 + 875167 ", "answer": "-179417", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "76", "question": "-5478 * 58397 - 4781 * -92124 ", "answer": "120546078", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "77", "question": "85 - -53 - -16 - 89 + 25 ", "answer": "90", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "78", "question": "-74600 - 62361 - 77583 ", "answer": "-214544", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "79", "question": "-3879 * 4596 ", "answer": "-17827884", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "80", "question": "81018 - 38001 * 69049 ", "answer": "-2623850031", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "81", "question": "-6194 - 2574 * -8362 ", "answer": "21517594", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "82", "question": "-6016 + -1257 ", "answer": "-7273", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "83", "question": "37 * 18 * -27 + 61 * 57 ", "answer": "-14505", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "84", "question": "12670 * -47157 * 25135 - -44262 ", "answer": "-15017639396388", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "85", "question": "9160 + -89983 - 58978 ", "answer": "-139801", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "86", "question": "306 - -581 - -159 ", "answer": "1046", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "87", "question": "-955729 + 280172 - 945410 ", "answer": "-1620967", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "88", "question": "-2151 * 1227 ", "answer": "-2639277", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "89", "question": "1143 * 9309 + 4782 ", "answer": "10644969", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "90", "question": "-77 + -97 * 20 - -82 - -22 ", "answer": "-1913", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "91", "question": "-14202 * -22348 * -63857 * 52779 ", "answer": "-1069689763883104488", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "92", "question": "55 * -39 * 85 * 42 ", "answer": "-7657650", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "93", "question": "25 + -98 + -64 - 12 * 70 ", "answer": "-977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "94", "question": "487712 - 847445 - 846091 ", "answer": "-1205824", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "95", "question": "55596 - -79943 ", "answer": "135539", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "96", "question": "-5689 * 1502 ", "answer": "-8544878", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "97", "question": "-88 + 70 ", "answer": "-18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "98", "question": "-49 - -769 ", "answer": "720", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "99", "question": "-5413 - 574 * 1605 - 1636 ", "answer": "-928319", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "100", "question": "4291 + 2414 * 6548 + 9646 ", "answer": "15820809", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "101", "question": "-12 * -46 - -34 * 70 * -78 ", "answer": "-185088", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "102", "question": "-2638 * -4493 * -3274 ", "answer": "-38805196316", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "103", "question": "48060 + 3840 ", "answer": "51900", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "104", "question": "-18422 + 33607 * -3544 ", "answer": "-119121630", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "105", "question": "-6899 + 3489 - 6421 - 9995 ", "answer": "-19826", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "106", "question": "-26 - 100 - -90 - 5 ", "answer": "-41", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "107", "question": "74243 * -13129 ", "answer": "-974736347", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "108", "question": "-23899 + 83176 * 62292 - 31404 ", "answer": "5181144089", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "109", "question": "24 + -88 ", "answer": "-64", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "110", "question": "817 * 112 ", "answer": "91504", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "111", "question": "-45818 - 30289 ", "answer": "-76107", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "112", "question": "14016 * -1530 + 92622 * -75434 ", "answer": "-7008292428", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "113", "question": "519731 * 339982 - 757762 + -775644 - 504085 ", "answer": "176697147351", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "114", "question": "-822 + -618 * 177 * -278 ", "answer": "30408486", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "115", "question": "-49867 * 40209 - 66487 * 22836 * -74373 ", "answer": "112918307496033", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "116", "question": "-1308 * -56835 ", "answer": "74340180", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "117", "question": "388 * -326 ", "answer": "-126488", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "118", "question": "-38 * -63 - -1 + 52 ", "answer": "2447", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "119", "question": "-98283 - 7489 * 42045 * 1070 + 94156 ", "answer": "-336916259477", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "120", "question": "57532 - -93612 ", "answer": "151144", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "121", "question": "970015 * -673329 ", "answer": "-653139229935", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "122", "question": "10 + -44 ", "answer": "-34", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "123", "question": "-18767 * -57156 * -48666 * 84454 ", "answer": "-4408618890736157328", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "124", "question": "-31206 * 49328 - 66086 ", "answer": "-1539395654", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "125", "question": "772 - 680 ", "answer": "92", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "126", "question": "-691684 + 361240 - 184615 ", "answer": "-515059", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "127", "question": "707427 + 698847 * 793257 + -379625 * -25589 ", "answer": "564080206231", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "128", "question": "-111331 + -538756 - -648165 ", "answer": "-1922", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "129", "question": "64265 + -99894 - 84054 - 78954 * -77393 ", "answer": "6110367239", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "130", "question": "782 * -113 + -648 ", "answer": "-89014", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "131", "question": "702784 + -500481 + 865450 ", "answer": "1067753", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "132", "question": "995 + 950 ", "answer": "1945", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "133", "question": "-69961 * -29290 * 79718 * 88671 + -13682 ", "answer": "14484829279447729138", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "134", "question": "825545 - 875885 + 48531 + -120397 - 527561 ", "answer": "-649767", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "135", "question": "1110 - -5937 * -4175 - -7268 ", "answer": "-24778597", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "136", "question": "-868 + 805 + 694 ", "answer": "631", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "137", "question": "-11 + -54 + -79 ", "answer": "-144", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "138", "question": "2966 + -5418 + 5357 + -7226 ", "answer": "-4321", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "139", "question": "37 * -100 - -95 * 60 * 23 ", "answer": "127400", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "140", "question": "-74812 * -45369 * -19757 + 81101 * 60430 ", "answer": "-67053234238966", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "141", "question": "444321 * -478858 + -464810 - -16029 ", "answer": "-212767114199", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "142", "question": "77 + -896 + 152 ", "answer": "-667", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "143", "question": "457 * 273 * -207 ", "answer": "-25825527", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "144", "question": "-15847 * 3623 ", "answer": "-57413681", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "145", "question": "57 - 49 + 26 - -31 ", "answer": "65", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "146", "question": "-618687 + -223155 + 124504 * -891072 - -490295 ", "answer": "-110942379835", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "147", "question": "-80468 * 4831 ", "answer": "-388740908", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "148", "question": "95 + -8 + -32 - -46 * -89 ", "answer": "-4039", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "149", "question": "97 - 14 * -56 ", "answer": "881", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "150", "question": "4981 + -3558 ", "answer": "1423", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "151", "question": "-921 * 322 + 957 ", "answer": "-295605", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "152", "question": "233 - -416 - 715 ", "answer": "-66", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "153", "question": "96 * 94 + -82 * -89 ", "answer": "16322", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "154", "question": "-52797 - 41990 - 99962 * -32584 ", "answer": "3257067021", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "155", "question": "4539 - -5741 - -4077 + 6005 ", "answer": "20362", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "156", "question": "35759 + -72113 - -79605 * 78635 - -77380 ", "answer": "6259780201", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "157", "question": "246001 + -661694 + 747139 ", "answer": "331446", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "158", "question": "324441 + 421581 ", "answer": "746022", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "159", "question": "-6205 * -48699 * 77580 * 88530 * -37825 ", "answer": "-78502051326782763225000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "160", "question": "-89 + 62 * -14 ", "answer": "-957", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "161", "question": "-600408 * 11075 - -977499 + -695445 + -364512 ", "answer": "-6649601058", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "162", "question": "870825 - 864719 + -671280 - 626262 ", "answer": "-1291436", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "163", "question": "-9 * -41 * -80 ", "answer": "-29520", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "164", "question": "-505 * 227 - -425 ", "answer": "-114210", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "165", "question": "1565 - 817 ", "answer": "748", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "166", "question": "796564 * 569859 - 501314 ", "answer": "453928663162", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "167", "question": "-6086 - 8143 + 4860 ", "answer": "-9369", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "168", "question": "-87 * -98 - -37 ", "answer": "8563", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "169", "question": "-31 + -93 * -56 ", "answer": "5177", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "170", "question": "-958 - -326 - -891 ", "answer": "259", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "171", "question": "-37 - 38 - -30 - 46 * -30 ", "answer": "1335", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "172", "question": "73676 * -35332 + -46682 ", "answer": "-2603167114", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "173", "question": "772 - -803 + 256 * -810 + -771 ", "answer": "-206556", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "174", "question": "-25419 + 1573 + -99441 + -58807 ", "answer": "-182094", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "175", "question": "-100 * 78 * 77 ", "answer": "-600600", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "176", "question": "-8833 + 3791 * -8127 ", "answer": "-30818290", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "177", "question": "37 * 59 + -36 ", "answer": "2147", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "178", "question": "90416 + -26197 * -37092 * -50732 + 3089 ", "answer": "-49296239865263", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "179", "question": "-990 + 123 - -874 ", "answer": "7", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "180", "question": "-423 + 71 - 439 + -117 - -555 ", "answer": "-353", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "181", "question": "-43 + 71 ", "answer": "28", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "182", "question": "-3610 + 5166 * -2926 - -5259 ", "answer": "-15114067", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "183", "question": "-269 + -137 ", "answer": "-406", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "184", "question": "740 + -563 * 819 ", "answer": "-460357", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "185", "question": "4563 * 1387 - -5757 ", "answer": "6334638", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "186", "question": "6792 + -7582 * 7404 * -8685 ", "answer": "487550963472", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "187", "question": "-266256 + 283844 * -188807 + 232177 - -97232 ", "answer": "-53591670955", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "188", "question": "-4 + -18 + -1 + 0 * -98 ", "answer": "-23", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "189", "question": "-15 - 18 * -59 ", "answer": "1047", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "190", "question": "-793697 + -997956 ", "answer": "-1791653", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "191", "question": "9092 - 4952 - -1349 + -501 ", "answer": "4988", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "192", "question": "497 * -854 * 582 * -520 ", "answer": "128451916320", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "193", "question": "80 - -6 * 1 * 82 ", "answer": "572", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "194", "question": "-9011 - -4102 ", "answer": "-4909", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "195", "question": "-9 + 70 * -91 ", "answer": "-6379", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "196", "question": "5143 * -6652 - -3234 - 8074 ", "answer": "-34216076", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "197", "question": "-13061 * -99370 - 28404 + -5970 ", "answer": "1297837196", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "198", "question": "538657 - -26256 - 755190 * 509396 * -830508 ", "answer": "319488758058506833", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "199", "question": "74 + 737 ", "answer": "811", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "200", "question": "-45 + -5 ", "answer": "-50", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "201", "question": "780 - 121 - -844 * 526 ", "answer": "444603", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "202", "question": "2777 - 8724 * -101 - 8350 ", "answer": "875551", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "203", "question": "-468930 + 815947 ", "answer": "347017", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "204", "question": "321 + 66250 ", "answer": "66571", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "205", "question": "7241 * 4275 ", "answer": "30955275", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "206", "question": "36 - 49 ", "answer": "-13", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "207", "question": "90988 + -68090 - 50820 ", "answer": "-27922", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "208", "question": "-1067 * -1055 ", "answer": "1125685", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "209", "question": "136848 * 527087 + -577772 ", "answer": "72130224004", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "210", "question": "753 * -556 + 0 ", "answer": "-418668", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "211", "question": "179356 + 971275 * -407357 ", "answer": "-395655490819", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "212", "question": "650803 - -330177 + -592976 ", "answer": "388004", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "213", "question": "-560513 * -874527 * -737915 ", "answer": "-361713943616088165", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "214", "question": "-61 * -62 * -57 + -83 * 73 ", "answer": "-221633", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "215", "question": "-86540 + 10600 + 30117 ", "answer": "-45823", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "216", "question": "687867 + 260860 + -244511 + -915119 * 995539 ", "answer": "-911035949925", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "217", "question": "59052 + 13467 + -34972 * -28131 - 68166 ", "answer": "983801685", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "218", "question": "46 * 10 + 91 - 53 - 68 ", "answer": "430", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "219", "question": "258414 * 58416 ", "answer": "15095512224", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "220", "question": "-165939 + -953491 ", "answer": "-1119430", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "221", "question": "-729889 + -774106 - 789146 - 88933 + 640213 ", "answer": "-1741861", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "222", "question": "5427 + 4265 ", "answer": "9692", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "223", "question": "0 - -2 - -60 ", "answer": "62", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "224", "question": "-387665 * -128207 - 839167 * 615837 - 936778 ", "answer": "-467089657902", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "225", "question": "589138 + -503367 ", "answer": "85771", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "226", "question": "-530 + 414 + -657 - 306 - -320 ", "answer": "-759", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "227", "question": "941 + -685 ", "answer": "256", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "228", "question": "-93661 + 409659 + -272951 * 946079 ", "answer": "-258232893131", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "229", "question": "-3772 + -1780 - -1615 ", "answer": "-3937", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "230", "question": "3107 * -4221 * 6801 * -3882 ", "answer": "346246116706854", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "231", "question": "3075 - 4160 - 7730 ", "answer": "-8815", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "232", "question": "-243 - 692 * 990 - 157 + 538 ", "answer": "-684942", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "233", "question": "-83813 + -71305 ", "answer": "-155118", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "234", "question": "29261 + -84276 ", "answer": "-55015", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "235", "question": "910361 + -446169 + -183236 ", "answer": "280956", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "236", "question": "514 - -60 * 556 + 198 * -669 ", "answer": "-98588", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "237", "question": "537 + 156 - -159 * 526 * -235 ", "answer": "-19653297", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "238", "question": "729 - 856 - -984 * 155 ", "answer": "152393", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "239", "question": "581635 + 192927 * 809877 + 958341 ", "answer": "156248679955", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "240", "question": "67478 * -9537 + -59947 - 58341 * 37717 ", "answer": "-2844045130", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "241", "question": "27991 - 25822 - -42052 - 68737 ", "answer": "-24516", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "242", "question": "-48464 * -983177 ", "answer": "47648690128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "243", "question": "75 - -63 ", "answer": "138", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "244", "question": "879557 - 474272 + 903722 ", "answer": "1309007", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "245", "question": "149 * -385 + -824 ", "answer": "-58189", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "246", "question": "-9 - -51 ", "answer": "42", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "247", "question": "-64 - -42 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "248", "question": "23405 * -20357 ", "answer": "-476455585", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "249", "question": "-7993 * -18359 ", "answer": "146743487", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "250", "question": "-580 + 7998 ", "answer": "7418", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "251", "question": "868 * -28 + 258 * 945 ", "answer": "219506", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "252", "question": "-61119 * -85253 * 89546 - -97408 + 14983 ", "answer": "466586427281813", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "253", "question": "115 - -500 ", "answer": "615", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "254", "question": "-940 + -729 * -699 ", "answer": "508631", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "255", "question": "-2144 - 91361 * -67521 - -41851 * -60585 ", "answer": "3633241102", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "256", "question": "601 + -478 * -990 * 691 + 533 ", "answer": "326996154", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "257", "question": "-69 * -22 * 43 * 3 ", "answer": "195822", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "258", "question": "208536 + -319780 ", "answer": "-111244", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "259", "question": "-129368 + -536847 ", "answer": "-666215", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "260", "question": "-49069 - 12141 * -59949 * -59537 - 22719 ", "answer": "-43333458317221", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "261", "question": "-920947 * -510476 ", "answer": "470121340772", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "262", "question": "-389452 - -886212 + -390165 ", "answer": "106595", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "263", "question": "-909 + 4872 * 8497 - 5724 ", "answer": "41390751", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "264", "question": "-511079 * -662372 - -187168 - -481196 ", "answer": "338525087752", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "265", "question": "-603901 - 341208 * 783525 + 948845 - 394688 ", "answer": "-267345047944", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "266", "question": "971 * 780 ", "answer": "757380", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "267", "question": "-2096 + 10722 ", "answer": "8626", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "268", "question": "-525 + -713 * 910 - 776 ", "answer": "-650131", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "269", "question": "4581 + -5053 ", "answer": "-472", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "270", "question": "3641 + 6129 + 8383 + -9246 - -5841 ", "answer": "14748", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "271", "question": "1564 + -8932 + 4513 ", "answer": "-2855", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "272", "question": "5371 * -78458 * -23419 + 98609 ", "answer": "9868717940251", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "273", "question": "-57698 + 535477 ", "answer": "477779", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "274", "question": "-97 * -77 - -85 * 43 ", "answer": "11124", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "275", "question": "-25 - -55 ", "answer": "30", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "276", "question": "-46 - -72 + -48 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "277", "question": "-59617 + 53470 ", "answer": "-6147", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "278", "question": "-3181 * -3453 * 1084 * -3787 ", "answer": "-45090477536244", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "279", "question": "-99 * -21 ", "answer": "2079", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "280", "question": "-75722 - 36932 - 66646 ", "answer": "-179300", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "281", "question": "1015 - 639 * -365 * -5019 + 8197 ", "answer": "-1170597253", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "282", "question": "-672 - -234 ", "answer": "-438", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "283", "question": "792 * 250 * 884 - -313 * 538 ", "answer": "175200394", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "284", "question": "-90 + 82 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "285", "question": "-814823 - 509000 - -725714 ", "answer": "-598109", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "286", "question": "571 + -520 ", "answer": "51", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "287", "question": "7624 + 66956 * 62863 + 45057 ", "answer": "4209107709", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "288", "question": "-20 * -36 * 10 - -98 - -57 ", "answer": "7355", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "289", "question": "-50578 * 92176 * 51197 ", "answer": "-238684393440416", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "290", "question": "-3546 * 5199 - -728 + -2649 * 8115 ", "answer": "-39931561", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "291", "question": "-438 - 994 + 184 ", "answer": "-1248", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "292", "question": "3 + 45 - -4 - -11 ", "answer": "63", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "293", "question": "8124 * -6659 * 7601 ", "answer": "-411196739316", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "294", "question": "135 * -661 ", "answer": "-89235", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "295", "question": "7415 + -7797 ", "answer": "-382", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "296", "question": "-8403 - 9768 ", "answer": "-18171", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "297", "question": "-31 * -458 - -915 ", "answer": "15113", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "298", "question": "640897 - -517612 - -422498 - -374492 + 578962 ", "answer": "2534461", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "299", "question": "-215566 * -510736 * -245567 - -474444 ", "answer": "-27036267739144148", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "300", "question": "550461 + 259840 ", "answer": "810301", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "301", "question": "-66674 + -88704 ", "answer": "-155378", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "302", "question": "-736029 + -715425 * 611152 - 343239 * -881458 ", "answer": "-134683393167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "303", "question": "-592 * 376 * 901 ", "answer": "-200555392", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "304", "question": "-34 - 51 - -81 * 7 ", "answer": "482", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "305", "question": "865 - -103 ", "answer": "968", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "306", "question": "214 + 355 * 849 - 452 - -253 ", "answer": "301410", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "307", "question": "69451 + 42743 + -89810 + -6152 ", "answer": "16232", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "308", "question": "47 * 66 + 6 ", "answer": "3108", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "309", "question": "-472685 * -416323 - 338618 - -687541 * 444522 ", "answer": "502416399039", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "310", "question": "34515 + 68010 ", "answer": "102525", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "311", "question": "-967856 + -203048 ", "answer": "-1170904", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "312", "question": "179 - -437 - 888 - -132 ", "answer": "-140", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "313", "question": "-406766 + -699724 * -564971 - 136916 * 992059 ", "answer": "259494611194", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "314", "question": "-88915 + 97009 - 1556 ", "answer": "6538", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "315", "question": "-84427 * -10279 + 62804 * -23048 ", "answer": "-579681459", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "316", "question": "-59730 * 467766 ", "answer": "-27939663180", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "317", "question": "64 + -17 - 99 - -31 + -41 ", "answer": "-62", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "318", "question": "-325 - 653 ", "answer": "-978", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "319", "question": "68596 - 13130 + -22525 ", "answer": "32941", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "320", "question": "918 - 603 + -459 + 678 ", "answer": "534", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "321", "question": "42 + -85 ", "answer": "-43", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "322", "question": "580 + 72 ", "answer": "652", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "323", "question": "-59 * -367 * -353 * -802 + 738 ", "answer": "6130094956", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "324", "question": "550672 * 51047 ", "answer": "28110153584", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "325", "question": "61917 - -61588 - 16779 - -91565 ", "answer": "198291", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "326", "question": "-7932 - -4251 ", "answer": "-3681", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "327", "question": "-56354 * 89009 - 61078 ", "answer": "-5016074264", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "328", "question": "-59 - 94 - 65 + -57 ", "answer": "-275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "329", "question": "-388090 - 970696 * -376062 + -933581 + -405215 ", "answer": "365040152266", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "330", "question": "3631 + 66352 + 33746 + -64024 ", "answer": "39705", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "331", "question": "47 + -39 * 15 + -23 ", "answer": "-561", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "332", "question": "9789 * -1741 + 1557 - -6133 ", "answer": "-17034959", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "333", "question": "9373 * 7867 * 8408 ", "answer": "619983983528", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "334", "question": "9189 * 2527 + 4948 * -7720 - 5372 ", "answer": "-14983329", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "335", "question": "-182911 + -323806 - -373848 ", "answer": "-132869", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "336", "question": "-24 + 75 - -79 - 26 + 74 ", "answer": "178", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "337", "question": "-9638 - 1658 - 9511 - -6130 ", "answer": "-14677", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "338", "question": "-97361 * 74855 * 14873 + 84881 ", "answer": "-108393794117934", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "339", "question": "76 * -74 + -49 + -33 + 53 ", "answer": "-5653", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "340", "question": "-205 - 387 + 766 ", "answer": "174", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "341", "question": "-43 + 30 ", "answer": "-13", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "342", "question": "-999 + -430 ", "answer": "-1429", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "343", "question": "-201581 - -302368 + 877803 + 421125 ", "answer": "1399715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "344", "question": "-9086 * -3722 ", "answer": "33818092", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "345", "question": "-51 - -66 + 92 ", "answer": "107", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "346", "question": "-379 - -137 ", "answer": "-242", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "347", "question": "363317 - -497783 ", "answer": "861100", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "348", "question": "27 - 8 ", "answer": "19", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "349", "question": "23712 + 92219 - 16487 - 27041 ", "answer": "72403", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "350", "question": "-94434 - 63335 * 27621 ", "answer": "-1749470469", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "351", "question": "25 - -63 - -54 + 44 * -2 ", "answer": "54", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "352", "question": "-7271 * -278 * 1101 * -1148 - 9760 ", "answer": "-2554866132184", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "353", "question": "-863 * -38 - 712 ", "answer": "32082", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "354", "question": "16 * -27 - 77 - 83 + 41 ", "answer": "-551", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "355", "question": "-51 * -11 * -36 * 86 ", "answer": "-1736856", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "356", "question": "-750981 + -114624 - -681379 ", "answer": "-184226", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "357", "question": "-821666 * 190972 - -835183 ", "answer": "-156914364169", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "358", "question": "2407 - -5160 - -2235 * 2876 * -7112 ", "answer": "-45714932753", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "359", "question": "40 - -24 ", "answer": "64", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "360", "question": "-270 - -667 ", "answer": "397", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "361", "question": "543135 * -407997 - -858483 - 886087 ", "answer": "-221597478199", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "362", "question": "-18394 + -43372 * 84572 ", "answer": "-3668075178", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "363", "question": "84839 * 98117 ", "answer": "8324148163", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "364", "question": "138 * 945 - -636 - 581 + 215 ", "answer": "130680", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "365", "question": "4 * 85 * -26 * 19 * 66 ", "answer": "-11085360", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "366", "question": "9921 * -2390 * -2702 + 753 * -6955 ", "answer": "64062398265", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "367", "question": "18 - -2 - 33 + -1 ", "answer": "-14", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "368", "question": "-97251 * 57487 * 45479 * -4988 - -90993 ", "answer": "1268238907743699717", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "369", "question": "662496 + -951745 - 469605 ", "answer": "-758854", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "370", "question": "-42 + -63 - -34 + -67 - 43 ", "answer": "-181", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "371", "question": "-56 + -5 + -37 * 92 * 53 ", "answer": "-180473", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "372", "question": "-47221 * -42770 * -64692 ", "answer": "-130654691261640", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "373", "question": "-81 + 43 ", "answer": "-38", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "374", "question": "857498 * -69702 + -288144 ", "answer": "-59769613740", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "375", "question": "-8320 + 7498 - -4042 ", "answer": "3220", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "376", "question": "-2987 * 818 + 9533 ", "answer": "-2433833", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "377", "question": "7961 + 33878 + -25236 * 70982 + -55140 ", "answer": "-1791315053", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "378", "question": "1705 - -5834 ", "answer": "7539", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "379", "question": "-7585 + -8046 ", "answer": "-15631", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "380", "question": "-982 - 327 - -20 ", "answer": "-1289", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "381", "question": "79093 - -2148 - -41462 ", "answer": "122703", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "382", "question": "7555 - 3472 + -8443 - 5245 - -3824 ", "answer": "-5781", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "383", "question": "64792 - 41563 - -86517 - 63687 + 58422 ", "answer": "104481", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "384", "question": "-855899 * -273326 * -432674 * 860772 ", "answer": "-87126926621937030760272", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "385", "question": "500 * 482 * 777 ", "answer": "187257000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "386", "question": "-97636 + -161062 - -34751 ", "answer": "-223947", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "387", "question": "2531 + 81377 ", "answer": "83908", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "388", "question": "-13 + -32 * -72 * 72 ", "answer": "165875", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "389", "question": "-25 - -95 + 78 * 59 - -18 ", "answer": "4690", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "390", "question": "-100 + 90 + -25 - -15 * 35 ", "answer": "490", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "391", "question": "9719 * -1604 - -1107 - 9760 * 1991 ", "answer": "-35020329", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "392", "question": "-433 - -182 + 628 ", "answer": "377", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "393", "question": "-636490 + -189892 ", "answer": "-826382", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "394", "question": "10 * -24 - -6 ", "answer": "-234", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "395", "question": "-941476 * 578895 + 409254 ", "answer": "-545015339766", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "396", "question": "462 + 100 - -892 - 996 ", "answer": "458", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "397", "question": "93468 * 45625 - 91953 * 22897 ", "answer": "2159029659", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "398", "question": "64864 + -82375 + -51292 + -68915 - 73834 ", "answer": "-211552", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "399", "question": "-7163 - 1852 * -6078 * -5670 - 9571 ", "answer": "-63824122254", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "400", "question": "-668 - 708 + -426 - 333 ", "answer": "-2135", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "401", "question": "70374 * 60438 ", "answer": "4253263812", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "402", "question": "984 + -743 * 920 * 240 ", "answer": "-164053416", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "403", "question": "-880 * 654 - -932 ", "answer": "-574588", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "404", "question": "-3099 * -1338 ", "answer": "4146462", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "405", "question": "-51 * -71 + -10 + 80 + -69 ", "answer": "3622", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "406", "question": "9084 * 8377 + 6320 + 1422 - 1904 ", "answer": "76102506", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "407", "question": "84 - -7404 * 4253 + 7400 + -9985 ", "answer": "31486711", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "408", "question": "39035 - -58364 ", "answer": "97399", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "409", "question": "98544 * 42223 ", "answer": "4160823312", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "410", "question": "-673 + 8012 * 1795 ", "answer": "14380867", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "411", "question": "54814 + -76320 * 388810 + -67507 ", "answer": "-29673991893", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "412", "question": "186096 * -284425 * -15125 ", "answer": "800571616350000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "413", "question": "840954 - -632563 + 432774 - 792572 - 819114 ", "answer": "294605", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "414", "question": "-77 - -87 + 29 * -25 ", "answer": "-715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "415", "question": "-983 + 240 - 780 - -482 - 680 ", "answer": "-1721", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "416", "question": "-2886 * -7831 - 5204 ", "answer": "22595062", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "417", "question": "-42 - -69 + 5 ", "answer": "32", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "418", "question": "13 * -21 + -77 ", "answer": "-350", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "419", "question": "-31 * -50 * 59 ", "answer": "91450", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "420", "question": "-68 * 12 + -42 ", "answer": "-858", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "421", "question": "748 + 196 * -329 * -873 ", "answer": "56295280", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "422", "question": "-59 + -36 * -59 + 98 ", "answer": "2163", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "423", "question": "-81097 * 22751 ", "answer": "-1845037847", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "424", "question": "9872 - 121 + -8253 * 5387 ", "answer": "-44449160", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "425", "question": "708 - -828 - -792 + 210 ", "answer": "2538", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "426", "question": "-6656 * 4035 + -4238 ", "answer": "-26861198", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "427", "question": "1787 + 3178 * -3084 ", "answer": "-9799165", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "428", "question": "98 * 100 * 76 - 88 ", "answer": "744712", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "429", "question": "971537 * -591993 * -769393 - 211832 ", "answer": "442511077631690881", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "430", "question": "-746481 * -898045 ", "answer": "670373529645", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "431", "question": "206644 + -66243 * -615963 ", "answer": "40803443653", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "432", "question": "9046 - 3909 - 8324 + -7051 ", "answer": "-10238", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "433", "question": "-6 * -88 * -65 - 47 * -94 ", "answer": "-29902", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "434", "question": "59 + 90 * -86 + -53 * 97 ", "answer": "-12822", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "435", "question": "70070 - -51250 - -59571 - -71283 * 38614 ", "answer": "2752702653", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "436", "question": "25844 + 30169 ", "answer": "56013", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "437", "question": "-2332 * 8609 + -4263 - 6014 ", "answer": "-20086465", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "438", "question": "-50823 - -7997 ", "answer": "-42826", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "439", "question": "927930 - -287784 ", "answer": "1215714", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "440", "question": "-91967 * -28086 + 643485 * -384036 ", "answer": "-244538420298", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "441", "question": "-44 * -74 + -44 * 6 ", "answer": "2992", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "442", "question": "-71519 * 41759 ", "answer": "-2986561921", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "443", "question": "-66 - -90 - 76 ", "answer": "-52", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "444", "question": "70 + -52 * -74 - 87 ", "answer": "3831", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "445", "question": "-982 - -626 + 754 ", "answer": "398", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "446", "question": "-1691 * 9794 ", "answer": "-16561654", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "447", "question": "-997729 * 937066 + -677439 ", "answer": "-934938600553", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "448", "question": "1993 * -184 * -5442 - -5572 + 9225 ", "answer": "1995661501", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "449", "question": "327 + -421 - 61 ", "answer": "-155", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "450", "question": "35 - 42 + 89 * 67 ", "answer": "5956", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "451", "question": "-868363 - -191903 - -491312 * -870815 ", "answer": "-427842535740", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "452", "question": "926395 * -615336 + 869284 - -541255 + 35671 ", "answer": "-570042747510", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "453", "question": "8989 + 8218 * -2908 ", "answer": "-23888955", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "454", "question": "1689 * -8581 - -53769 + 81600 ", "answer": "-14357940", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "455", "question": "-569931 * -559941 - -472017 - 698739 ", "answer": "319127507349", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "456", "question": "421 * 821 + 512 * 886 + -647 ", "answer": "798626", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "457", "question": "959 + -979 + 555 - -413 ", "answer": "948", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "458", "question": "-3519 + -54588 * -14579 ", "answer": "795834933", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "459", "question": "-9701 + 884 - -9789 * -9760 * 5916 ", "answer": "-565218435057", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "460", "question": "229 * 357 ", "answer": "81753", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "461", "question": "58 - 37 - 76 * 77 - -71 ", "answer": "-5760", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "462", "question": "4121 + -7805 + -3700 + -8 - 7201 ", "answer": "-14593", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "463", "question": "-52 - 8 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "464", "question": "166401 * -612171 ", "answer": "-101865866571", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "465", "question": "47676 - 768534 ", "answer": "-720858", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "466", "question": "-7165 * 979 + 6449 ", "answer": "-7008086", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "467", "question": "-31 * 52 + 100 + -47 ", "answer": "-1559", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "468", "question": "-446 * -614 ", "answer": "273844", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "469", "question": "-57 + 87 * 62 + 42 - 88 ", "answer": "5291", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "470", "question": "20113 * -61544 + 17868 + -19301 - 70058 ", "answer": "-1237905963", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "471", "question": "760779 - -921932 + 702305 ", "answer": "2385016", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "472", "question": "445348 * 576090 ", "answer": "256560529320", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "473", "question": "-210 * -589 * 140 * 865 * 656 ", "answer": "9826131504000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "474", "question": "655 * 110 * -219 ", "answer": "-15778950", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "475", "question": "2807 + -108 + 7539 - 6223 * -1811 ", "answer": "11280091", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "476", "question": "-68 + 28 - 1 ", "answer": "-41", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "477", "question": "-165505 + 200198 * -848184 * 717636 - 103633 ", "answer": "-121857994704927890", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "478", "question": "57 + -93 + 68 + -46 * -11 ", "answer": "538", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "479", "question": "-556 * 238 * -752 ", "answer": "99510656", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "480", "question": "15 * -54 + -95 * 83 * 79 ", "answer": "-623725", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "481", "question": "772 + 784 * -690 ", "answer": "-540188", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "482", "question": "297 + 562 * 774 * -884 ", "answer": "-384529095", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "483", "question": "-26420 + 35296 ", "answer": "8876", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "484", "question": "5 * 13 - 70 - -1 + -68 ", "answer": "-72", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "485", "question": "1725 - 906 * -4734 * 7161 + 9604 ", "answer": "30713568973", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "486", "question": "7108 * 9697 ", "answer": "68926276", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "487", "question": "-96454 - -39406 - 92572 * 13303 ", "answer": "-1231542364", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "488", "question": "7389 - 8267 - -6096 ", "answer": "5218", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "489", "question": "-151529 * 323137 + -415669 + -218798 ", "answer": "-48965260940", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "490", "question": "93585 + -70679 - 79362 ", "answer": "-56456", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "491", "question": "1336 * 5370 ", "answer": "7174320", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "492", "question": "-501 - -567 * 453 ", "answer": "256350", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "493", "question": "97 * 53 * -12 * -34 ", "answer": "2097528", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "494", "question": "-248566 + -691304 - 756054 ", "answer": "-1695924", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "495", "question": "3108 - -9815 - 113 * -7681 + -3702 ", "answer": "877174", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "496", "question": "-731 * 172 - -984 + 659 ", "answer": "-124089", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "497", "question": "-5498 * 5146 + 3942 * 3456 ", "answer": "-14669156", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "498", "question": "601 - -974 + 393 - -829 ", "answer": "2797", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "499", "question": "30057 * 40018 - -39504 ", "answer": "1202860530", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "500", "question": "-6331 * -8677 * -4934 * -1931 ", "answer": "523387480333198", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "501", "question": "-775180 + -941567 * -345322 ", "answer": "325143024394", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "502", "question": "68689 + 40224 + -4467 ", "answer": "104446", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "503", "question": "-92 - 85 ", "answer": "-177", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "504", "question": "-81727 * -6229 + 95667 - -70846 ", "answer": "509243996", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "505", "question": "717 + 675 - -683 + 234 + 398 ", "answer": "2707", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "506", "question": "-700 - -44 * -716 + -963 ", "answer": "-33167", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "507", "question": "590760 * 824180 * 108610 ", "answer": "52881402766248000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "508", "question": "55 * -100 + -87 * -15 ", "answer": "-4195", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "509", "question": "-710036 - 890958 - -44492 * 812668 ", "answer": "36155623662", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "510", "question": "41822 * -70906 ", "answer": "-2965430732", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "511", "question": "-99 * 35 ", "answer": "-3465", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "512", "question": "-37040 + -821 ", "answer": "-37861", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "513", "question": "8875 * 945 - -8808 - 4022 * 7496 ", "answer": "-21753229", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "514", "question": "164067 + -145354 - -435790 * 184489 * -990304 ", "answer": "-79618917829119527", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "515", "question": "-14958 * 18495 * 65727 ", "answer": "-18183256898670", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "516", "question": "645 - 755 * 581 * -932 ", "answer": "408827105", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "517", "question": "40646 + -80892 - -93864 ", "answer": "53618", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "518", "question": "6068 + 9951 - 2497 ", "answer": "13522", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "519", "question": "-691788 * -267889 * 401733 ", "answer": "74450121924256956", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "520", "question": "49 * 13 + -3 ", "answer": "634", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "521", "question": "532 * 989 - -249 ", "answer": "526397", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "522", "question": "-94 * -15 - -72 - 18 + -73 ", "answer": "1391", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "523", "question": "-7287 - 9910 ", "answer": "-17197", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "524", "question": "72 * 26 ", "answer": "1872", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "525", "question": "-69 - -69 * 29 ", "answer": "1932", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "526", "question": "-29 - -10 - 91 ", "answer": "-110", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "527", "question": "-51 + -38 - -18 ", "answer": "-71", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "528", "question": "8311 - 99097 * -28298 - 76193 - -64267 ", "answer": "2804243291", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "529", "question": "79345 * -36253 * 46869 - -55592 * 64286 ", "answer": "-134814836856353", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "530", "question": "562858 - 368766 ", "answer": "194092", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "531", "question": "883 - -658 - 714 + 296 - 302 ", "answer": "821", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "532", "question": "-829514 * 569800 + 528165 ", "answer": "-472656549035", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "533", "question": "-6323 - -4376 ", "answer": "-1947", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "534", "question": "-468456 - 316884 * -431631 * 698735 ", "answer": "95570847610709484", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "535", "question": "8749 + 2850 * 1739 * -9778 ", "answer": "-48461225951", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "536", "question": "-94983 - -38777 - 71285 ", "answer": "-127491", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "537", "question": "1282 * 3716 * 8982 * 3833 * -1050 ", "answer": "-172212590465445600", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "538", "question": "660 - -820 + 512 * 604 ", "answer": "310728", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "539", "question": "3484 + 3765 + -233 - -8154 + 2709 ", "answer": "17879", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "540", "question": "-60232 - 62028 * 38075 - 90644 - 18724 ", "answer": "-2361885700", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "541", "question": "-7677 - -886 ", "answer": "-6791", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "542", "question": "854 + 586 * 610 - 339 ", "answer": "357975", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "543", "question": "229 + -659 + -84 ", "answer": "-514", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "544", "question": "26676 - -31330 + -59123 + 5321 ", "answer": "4204", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "545", "question": "5355 * -2723 * 7212 - 2666 * -5054 ", "answer": "-105149494016", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "546", "question": "82633 * -71030 * 5720 * 57081 + 9816 ", "answer": "-1916385766215996984", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "547", "question": "401426 * -233932 ", "answer": "-93906387032", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "548", "question": "29547 + 76375 - -64674 + 1082 - -37069 ", "answer": "208747", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "549", "question": "71109 * 86062 * -18920 + -43989 ", "answer": "-115786289825349", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "550", "question": "-374034 - 992276 * 496679 ", "answer": "-492843025438", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "551", "question": "416 * 449 - -408 ", "answer": "187192", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "552", "question": "-8229 + 459510 ", "answer": "451281", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "553", "question": "-754808 * -222169 * -39163 * -268181 ", "answer": "1761261789516220235656", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "554", "question": "-904722 + 381575 - -41139 + 113159 ", "answer": "-368849", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "555", "question": "83476 - 67955 - 72683 ", "answer": "-57162", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "556", "question": "-42789 + 93365 ", "answer": "50576", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "557", "question": "119 + -17 + 140 ", "answer": "242", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "558", "question": "298797 * -709437 - 937972 * 219414 ", "answer": "-417781835697", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "559", "question": "61 + 182 - -242 ", "answer": "485", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "560", "question": "544675 - -765338 - -389201 - 23103 - -672683 ", "answer": "2348794", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "561", "question": "42 - 33 - 67 + -87 * 76 ", "answer": "-6670", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "562", "question": "827 * 511 ", "answer": "422597", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "563", "question": "1906 - -476 ", "answer": "2382", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "564", "question": "-28 * -88 + -53 + -1 + 41 ", "answer": "2451", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "565", "question": "69 * 288 ", "answer": "19872", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "566", "question": "-593881 - 654481 + -54954 + -97731 * -873453 ", "answer": "85362131827", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "567", "question": "-7460 - 51950 - -78788 * -82181 * 94704 ", "answer": "-613196716237522", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "568", "question": "455726 - -952620 + 669067 + 36806 - 906062 ", "answer": "1208157", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "569", "question": "30 * -961 - -787 ", "answer": "-28043", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "570", "question": "96911 + -87003 * 82506 + -80392 * 26673 ", "answer": "-9322468423", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "571", "question": "6407 + -2377 ", "answer": "4030", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "572", "question": "704680 - 839041 + -207333 - -812752 ", "answer": "471058", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "573", "question": "92 - -71 - 6 - -5 ", "answer": "162", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "574", "question": "-41690 - -51519 * 5420 ", "answer": "279191290", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "575", "question": "748168 * -484437 ", "answer": "-362440261416", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "576", "question": "-37 * 33 * 76 + 54 * -57 ", "answer": "-95874", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "577", "question": "1403 * 8022 - -3460 ", "answer": "11258326", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "578", "question": "5112 - -8016 ", "answer": "13128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "579", "question": "329 - 296 - -373 - 204 + -431 ", "answer": "-229", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "580", "question": "-3747 * -3346 + 6753 ", "answer": "12544215", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "581", "question": "-59 - -93 + -83 + 52 * 0 ", "answer": "-49", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "582", "question": "15385 + 32297 + 44749 ", "answer": "92431", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "583", "question": "911 * -584 + -940 ", "answer": "-532964", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "584", "question": "-351934 + 245978 * 946972 ", "answer": "232933926682", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "585", "question": "-5612 + 4791 * -6333 + -3207 + -158 ", "answer": "-30350380", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "586", "question": "-32494 * -62073 + 67154 ", "answer": "2017067216", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "587", "question": "937151 + 225676 * 424647 - -118902 ", "answer": "95833692425", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "588", "question": "844 * 568 - -559 + 172 - -670 ", "answer": "480793", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "589", "question": "234776 * -160161 + 547162 ", "answer": "-37601411774", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "590", "question": "-819691 * 441210 - 576871 * 910508 ", "answer": "-886901526578", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "591", "question": "2015 * -4088 + -8859 ", "answer": "-8246179", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "592", "question": "682 - 171 * 291 ", "answer": "-49079", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "593", "question": "-98 * -33 - 78 - -57 ", "answer": "3213", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "594", "question": "380374 + 606049 * -27695 * 503682 ", "answer": "-8454064155736136", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "595", "question": "-413 * -748 - 13 ", "answer": "308911", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "596", "question": "-38719 - 88753 - -11786 - 31507 ", "answer": "-147193", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "597", "question": "9899 - 7783 - 3931 - -8778 - -2751 ", "answer": "9714", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "598", "question": "26 - 91 + 12 * 39 - 1 ", "answer": "402", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "599", "question": "-369 * 508 ", "answer": "-187452", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "600", "question": "2832 - 3838 - -1567 ", "answer": "561", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "601", "question": "-31 + 60 - 52 - 93 ", "answer": "-116", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "602", "question": "-15621 - 36096 * -98047 ", "answer": "3539088891", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "603", "question": "-75876 - 77081 - 80386 - 62022 ", "answer": "-295365", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "604", "question": "-492 + 438 - 314 * 287 * 233 ", "answer": "-20997548", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "605", "question": "-3112 * -9597 + 9650 - 7848 ", "answer": "29867666", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "606", "question": "-21 + -89 - 38 - 15 + -65 ", "answer": "-228", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "607", "question": "956 * 348 ", "answer": "332688", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "608", "question": "-10131 - -27224 ", "answer": "17093", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "609", "question": "-604 - -8934 - -2581 ", "answer": "10911", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "610", "question": "28 - 62 ", "answer": "-34", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "611", "question": "787 - 343 ", "answer": "444", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "612", "question": "-4803 - 3704 * -9885 - 1079 ", "answer": "36608158", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "613", "question": "90 * 67 - 37 ", "answer": "5993", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "614", "question": "4 - 90 + -37 ", "answer": "-123", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "615", "question": "-304 - 338 - -800 * -597 + -844 ", "answer": "-479086", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "616", "question": "-225 - 992 * -5479 - -5748 ", "answer": "5440691", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "617", "question": "5086 * 3499 - 5336 ", "answer": "17790578", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "618", "question": "-327 + -554 * -644 ", "answer": "356449", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "619", "question": "-277 - 925 + 201 * -719 * 837 ", "answer": "-120963605", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "620", "question": "10 * -123 ", "answer": "-1230", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "621", "question": "-135232 - 509278 - 546272 * 899320 ", "answer": "-491273979550", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "622", "question": "25 - 224 - -147 + 461 ", "answer": "409", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "623", "question": "55169 - -19488 ", "answer": "74657", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "624", "question": "161729 + 900398 * -727330 + 951534 - 627735 ", "answer": "-654885991812", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "625", "question": "586673 * -416753 * -417208 * 466467 - -642114 ", "answer": "47582624096892924814698", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "626", "question": "75 - 34 - -19 + 89 ", "answer": "149", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "627", "question": "-432715 + 847213 + -123437 * -939848 - 85968 ", "answer": "116012346106", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "628", "question": "-164250 * 734504 ", "answer": "-120642282000", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "629", "question": "-1 - -49 * 69 + -46 - 20 ", "answer": "3314", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "630", "question": "97064 - 8946 * -80060 + -57761 ", "answer": "716256063", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "631", "question": "98496 * 33638 ", "answer": "3313208448", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "632", "question": "379 * 958 * -416 + 570 ", "answer": "-151041542", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "633", "question": "-140 + -990 * -503 * -184 ", "answer": "-91626620", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "634", "question": "35222 * -1850 * 51134 ", "answer": "-3331927233800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "635", "question": "249007 + 211519 ", "answer": "460526", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "636", "question": "-8914 - -4781 ", "answer": "-4133", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "637", "question": "-5033 * -4060 + -9631 + -5124 + 6155 ", "answer": "20425380", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "638", "question": "-398 - 761 - -289 - -350 ", "answer": "-520", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "639", "question": "-62 - -80 * 61 + 55 ", "answer": "4873", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "640", "question": "-111 * 683 - -286 - -756 ", "answer": "-74771", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "641", "question": "87 * 841 * -942 * 948 ", "answer": "-65339301672", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "642", "question": "-3250 * -5071 + -6233 - 3737 ", "answer": "16470780", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "643", "question": "60 * -89 * -83 ", "answer": "443220", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "644", "question": "-9604 * 9168 + 269 ", "answer": "-88049203", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "645", "question": "153105 * 777807 * -363662 ", "answer": "-43307104111971570", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "646", "question": "121 - -743 * -353 ", "answer": "-262158", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "647", "question": "64 + 53 * 65 ", "answer": "3509", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "648", "question": "5480 - 4737 * 4405 ", "answer": "-20861005", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "649", "question": "-342 + 82 + 962 - 735 ", "answer": "-33", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "650", "question": "620 + 51 * -576 * 64 - 776 ", "answer": "-1880220", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "651", "question": "-8447 * 8966 ", "answer": "-75735802", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "652", "question": "-43086 * 97562 - 60957 - -8711 ", "answer": "-4203608578", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "653", "question": "-897 * -448 + 197 ", "answer": "402053", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "654", "question": "38753 * -26801 ", "answer": "-1038619153", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "655", "question": "176 - 762 ", "answer": "-586", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "656", "question": "6596 - -1973 + 7362 + -7329 ", "answer": "8602", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "657", "question": "-310 * -933 ", "answer": "289230", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "658", "question": "-69 + -50 * -684 + 283 ", "answer": "34414", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "659", "question": "2 - -63 * 75 * 14 ", "answer": "66152", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "660", "question": "-860 - 968 * -44 - 415 ", "answer": "41317", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "661", "question": "78536 * -20364 + -5882 + 14658 * -79733 ", "answer": "-2768039300", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "662", "question": "81125 + 3963 + 6138 ", "answer": "91226", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "663", "question": "4108 * -5926 - -1616 ", "answer": "-24342392", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "664", "question": "218837 + 617682 - 981745 * 680862 ", "answer": "-668432027671", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "665", "question": "-7329 - 209 - 2202 ", "answer": "-9740", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "666", "question": "-5958 + 59493 + -75181 ", "answer": "-21646", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "667", "question": "4598 - -44431 ", "answer": "49029", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "668", "question": "562285 * -365339 ", "answer": "-205424639615", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "669", "question": "380 - -68963 ", "answer": "69343", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "670", "question": "-996 - 773 - 817 ", "answer": "-2586", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "671", "question": "-30683 + 658703 ", "answer": "628020", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "672", "question": "-467 + 3162 * 6877 + 5557 * -3493 ", "answer": "2334006", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "673", "question": "889 * 616 + 723 + 738 ", "answer": "549085", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "674", "question": "149711 + 705506 * 22708 - 81551 ", "answer": "16020698408", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "675", "question": "-58 - -149 ", "answer": "91", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "676", "question": "-306 - 44 - 281 - -110 ", "answer": "-521", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "677", "question": "23231 * -407231 * 307943 * 204545 ", "answer": "-595892528064798642535", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "678", "question": "-20 * -80 + -49 * -16 ", "answer": "2384", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "679", "question": "-8877 - 8768 - -3858 * 9930 - 9274 ", "answer": "38283021", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "680", "question": "-63788 * 90833 ", "answer": "-5794055404", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "681", "question": "-416 * -999 + -807 + 579 ", "answer": "415356", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "682", "question": "-37784 - 30888 * -44763 ", "answer": "1382601760", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "683", "question": "-1803 - 4732 * 2270 + -9365 ", "answer": "-10752808", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "684", "question": "-78 + 61 + -70 ", "answer": "-87", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "685", "question": "4115 + 2261 - 937 ", "answer": "5439", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "686", "question": "746 * -30 * -996 - -110 * 134 ", "answer": "22305220", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "687", "question": "-2 - 0 - 77 - 52 * 25 ", "answer": "-1379", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "688", "question": "5080 + -3950 - -6676 * -4093 + -2371 ", "answer": "-27326109", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "689", "question": "-4196 * -15636 ", "answer": "65608656", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "690", "question": "43 + 30 + -21 ", "answer": "52", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "691", "question": "-581 + 4988 + 369 + -568 ", "answer": "4208", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "692", "question": "-40 - 79 ", "answer": "-119", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "693", "question": "-33759 - -20212 ", "answer": "-13547", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "694", "question": "-40363 + -60923 * 2795 * 6045 ", "answer": "-1029341340688", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "695", "question": "-23 + 14 * -40 - 10 ", "answer": "-593", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "696", "question": "-421 * 893 * -63 + -567 ", "answer": "23684472", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "697", "question": "96721 + 95291 + -29457 * 32403 * 3023 ", "answer": "-2885438709921", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "698", "question": "-84 + 93 - -42 + 55 - 61 ", "answer": "45", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "699", "question": "38 + -27 ", "answer": "11", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "700", "question": "-33 - 81 + 94 ", "answer": "-20", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "701", "question": "100 * -735 - 196 * 822 ", "answer": "-234612", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "702", "question": "-921706 + -472278 + 572654 ", "answer": "-821330", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "703", "question": "-177891 * 547142 - -314486 * 330186 - 486460 ", "answer": "6506750414", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "704", "question": "6399 + 4535 - 4109 + 5218 - -641 ", "answer": "12684", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "705", "question": "385 - 855 * -660 * -78 - 763 ", "answer": "-44015778", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "706", "question": "-40 - -6 * 19 + 61 * 72 ", "answer": "4466", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "707", "question": "-54073 - 73973 ", "answer": "-128046", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "708", "question": "-80414 - -59280 ", "answer": "-21134", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "709", "question": "-310476 + -527412 + 430802 - -320318 ", "answer": "-86768", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "710", "question": "716 - 936 - 357 - -779 ", "answer": "202", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "711", "question": "-39 + -69 * 22 - -58 + -37 ", "answer": "-1536", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "712", "question": "880 * 141 * -741 + 25 - -124 ", "answer": "-91943131", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "713", "question": "54 + -39 - 28 ", "answer": "-13", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "714", "question": "-13 - 538 - 719 + 715 ", "answer": "-555", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "715", "question": "793870 * -661168 * 515047 * -55775 ", "answer": "15078136034665131428000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "716", "question": "20 + -58 ", "answer": "-38", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "717", "question": "321 * 776 * 941 * -209 - -122 ", "answer": "-48989461102", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "718", "question": "-8426 - 3701 ", "answer": "-12127", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "719", "question": "69712 + -27062 ", "answer": "42650", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "720", "question": "-40236 * -93555 ", "answer": "3764278980", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "721", "question": "-54 - 88 * -8 - 7 * 0 ", "answer": "650", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "722", "question": "77989 * -25797 ", "answer": "-2011882233", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "723", "question": "72660 * -27744 * 85396 - 65892 ", "answer": "-172148006565732", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "724", "question": "226031 + 725021 ", "answer": "951052", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "725", "question": "253 + -114 - 450 * 782 ", "answer": "-351761", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "726", "question": "-8073 * 22476 - -5061 * -75025 - -31931 ", "answer": "-561118342", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "727", "question": "1452 - 8848 - 1611 + -9477 - -5559 ", "answer": "-12925", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "728", "question": "489 - 243 - 133 * 965 * 440 ", "answer": "-56471554", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "729", "question": "-934 * 435 + 765 + -542 ", "answer": "-406067", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "730", "question": "447 + 41 * -587 + -180 - 737 ", "answer": "-24537", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "731", "question": "-90 * -40 ", "answer": "3600", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "732", "question": "-125294 + 687801 + -337995 * 291138 - -224448 ", "answer": "-98402401355", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "733", "question": "-779690 * 789110 * 167512 ", "answer": "-103063630097360800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "734", "question": "-56 * 31 ", "answer": "-1736", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "735", "question": "-74 + -50 * -62 + -13 ", "answer": "3013", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "736", "question": "-4796 * 9648 + 3300 ", "answer": "-46268508", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "737", "question": "-89 + -100 + 905 ", "answer": "716", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "738", "question": "2656 + -9113 + 8934 - 1828 - 8748 ", "answer": "-8099", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "739", "question": "921212 - -737785 * -820716 ", "answer": "-605511032848", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "740", "question": "233 - -803 * 538 ", "answer": "432247", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "741", "question": "25480 + 28766 - 86101 ", "answer": "-31855", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "742", "question": "674706 * 594420 ", "answer": "401058740520", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "743", "question": "8407 + 2133 * -4032 ", "answer": "-8591849", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "744", "question": "-54 * 73 + 41 ", "answer": "-3901", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "745", "question": "-4223 * 2850 ", "answer": "-12035550", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "746", "question": "-46090 + -2045 - -11576 + 95706 * -20593 ", "answer": "-1970910217", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "747", "question": "3863 + -415 - -3515 ", "answer": "6963", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "748", "question": "-772572 * -300885 ", "answer": "232455326220", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "749", "question": "-1137 * -4123 - 664 ", "answer": "4687187", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "750", "question": "94 + 31 - -5 + -89 * -56 ", "answer": "5114", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "751", "question": "765 + 682 * 525 * -815 ", "answer": "-291809985", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "752", "question": "65 * 143 + 513 - 343 + -622 ", "answer": "8843", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "753", "question": "6478 * -133 ", "answer": "-861574", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "754", "question": "-4952 + -6072 ", "answer": "-11024", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "755", "question": "-3789 - -5247 * -4983 * 9934 + -1693 ", "answer": "-259732392616", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "756", "question": "3435 + 16763 + 3653 + 73125 ", "answer": "96976", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "757", "question": "-8 - 96 - -78 + 54 ", "answer": "28", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "758", "question": "-50 * 72 * 70 + 70 ", "answer": "-251930", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "759", "question": "-345788 - -753066 - 377561 ", "answer": "29717", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "760", "question": "52409 - -48706 - -23567 ", "answer": "124682", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "761", "question": "747 + 717 + -429 ", "answer": "1035", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "762", "question": "-739034 - 289349 ", "answer": "-1028383", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "763", "question": "8 * 92 + -620 + 101 - -141 ", "answer": "358", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "764", "question": "-78775 + -64084 * 78672 ", "answer": "-5041695223", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "765", "question": "-155 - 391 - -527 + 395 - 865 ", "answer": "-489", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "766", "question": "4885 + -1305 * -1493 - -7187 ", "answer": "1960437", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "767", "question": "719 + -653 ", "answer": "66", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "768", "question": "85 + 75 ", "answer": "160", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "769", "question": "-616 + 153 * 909 + -534 ", "answer": "137927", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "770", "question": "-8108 * 9681 * -4460 - -7056 ", "answer": "350081231136", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "771", "question": "-1013 * 4000 * 1330 * -4945 * -4522 ", "answer": "-120508569616400000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "772", "question": "-883926 * -922473 + 558806 * -317971 - -559015 ", "answer": "637714325387", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "773", "question": "54321 * -13096 ", "answer": "-711387816", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "774", "question": "6747 - -2564 - 9495 - 1918 ", "answer": "-2102", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "775", "question": "307 - -169 * 719 - -972 ", "answer": "122790", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "776", "question": "-343 - -668 - -920 * 204 + -500 ", "answer": "187505", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "777", "question": "-283212 * 649152 - 608151 ", "answer": "-183848244375", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "778", "question": "-1582 * -1206 ", "answer": "1907892", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "779", "question": "77 * 827 + -823 + 782 ", "answer": "63638", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "780", "question": "-996600 - 532283 + -228274 ", "answer": "-1757157", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "781", "question": "-8203 + -44556 - -409869 ", "answer": "357110", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "782", "question": "-32 + 34 ", "answer": "2", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "783", "question": "-568 * -256 + 780 * 229 * -155 ", "answer": "-27540692", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "784", "question": "-712416 + -944702 * -75521 + -7223 - 675929 ", "answer": "71343444174", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "785", "question": "-253 + -742 - -523 + -945 ", "answer": "-1417", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "786", "question": "25507 + 11630 - -52537 * -83080 ", "answer": "-4364736823", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "787", "question": "-21788 * 67361 + 45480 - -37129 ", "answer": "-1467578859", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "788", "question": "-98452 * 35079 ", "answer": "-3453597708", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "789", "question": "-3281 * 2692 - 3668 ", "answer": "-8836120", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "790", "question": "-512 * -763 ", "answer": "390656", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "791", "question": "51582 + -20873 - 18214 * -11478 + -19430 ", "answer": "209071571", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "792", "question": "4765 * 6399 ", "answer": "30491235", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "793", "question": "-389264 + -947919 ", "answer": "-1337183", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "794", "question": "-72 * 15 * -84 ", "answer": "90720", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "795", "question": "-694 + 464 * 249 - 193 - -367 ", "answer": "115016", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "796", "question": "-691538 + 868686 + 933233 ", "answer": "1110381", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "797", "question": "-474 - 9341 ", "answer": "-9815", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "798", "question": "84607 * -83489 ", "answer": "-7063753823", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "799", "question": "-749077 + 972422 + -541190 + -235453 + -449143 ", "answer": "-1002441", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "800", "question": "-7906 - -4368 + 4481 + -7809 ", "answer": "-6866", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "801", "question": "96 * 316 - -388 ", "answer": "30724", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "802", "question": "24670 + -16138 ", "answer": "8532", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "803", "question": "-992420 + -13515 + -815512 ", "answer": "-1821447", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "804", "question": "-78 - -944 - 108 - -663 * 356 ", "answer": "236786", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "805", "question": "-90 - -701 * 643 ", "answer": "450653", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "806", "question": "-994614 - -957681 - -173496 * -637225 - 950434 ", "answer": "-110556975967", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "807", "question": "81 - 33 - 17 ", "answer": "31", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "808", "question": "-67024 * 48165 + 81539 ", "answer": "-3228129421", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "809", "question": "-73 * -38 ", "answer": "2774", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "810", "question": "-32 + 1 - -11 ", "answer": "-20", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "811", "question": "-42573 + 7143 * -95320 - 60738 ", "answer": "-680974071", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "812", "question": "626 * -476 ", "answer": "-297976", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "813", "question": "-617 + 22 ", "answer": "-595", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "814", "question": "34 - -59 ", "answer": "93", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "815", "question": "-396984 * -74970 + -917657 ", "answer": "29760972823", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "816", "question": "-5748 * -5977 * 1799 ", "answer": "61806077004", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "817", "question": "-164 * -77 ", "answer": "12628", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "818", "question": "585052 * -402293 * 433680 + -845662 - 375118 ", "answer": "-102071932775889260", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "819", "question": "-183438 * 409588 + -348243 ", "answer": "-75134351787", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "820", "question": "-90234 + -20004 * 18287 * -15720 + 68105 ", "answer": "5750582664431", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "821", "question": "572 * 175 + 167 * -445 ", "answer": "25785", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "822", "question": "813652 * 860872 + 707200 - -342824 * 720258 ", "answer": "947372660336", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "823", "question": "2613 - -2445 * 1926 - 3370 - -4090 ", "answer": "4712403", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "824", "question": "100254 * -69355 + 284450 ", "answer": "-6952831720", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "825", "question": "1185 * -8289 * 5314 + 3393 - -9012 ", "answer": "-52196566605", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "826", "question": "-61 - 5 * -50 - 11 ", "answer": "178", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "827", "question": "4500 * -1856 + 3945 * -4412 ", "answer": "-25757340", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "828", "question": "86 + -1 + 71 * -29 ", "answer": "-1974", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "829", "question": "168090 + -722345 * 220539 ", "answer": "-159305075865", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "830", "question": "-97014 - -78609 * 15912 ", "answer": "1250729394", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "831", "question": "9012 - -6320 ", "answer": "15332", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "832", "question": "198 - 133 + -921 ", "answer": "-856", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "833", "question": "-16105 + 89486 * -14620 ", "answer": "-1308301425", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "834", "question": "-71706 + 94832 ", "answer": "23126", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "835", "question": "18 + -35 ", "answer": "-17", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "836", "question": "714 + -3858 ", "answer": "-3144", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "837", "question": "-12 + -20 + 3 - 61 + -65 ", "answer": "-155", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "838", "question": "-943 + -234 - 117 + -119 + -689 ", "answer": "-2102", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "839", "question": "-96 + -65 * 40 - -28 * -29 ", "answer": "-3508", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "840", "question": "-81405 - 21858 * 19202 ", "answer": "-419798721", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "841", "question": "215 * -564 - 622 + -659 + -540 ", "answer": "-123081", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "842", "question": "20480 * 71812 - 77552 - -61491 * 43090 ", "answer": "4120279398", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "843", "question": "-358 - -39 + -245 + 196 ", "answer": "-368", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "844", "question": "-9758 + -9035 + 3961 * -8178 ", "answer": "-32411851", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "845", "question": "-7396 + -8449 - -1177 * -8363 ", "answer": "-9859096", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "846", "question": "-72 - -21 * 81 ", "answer": "1629", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "847", "question": "-344830 * -887121 ", "answer": "305905934430", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "848", "question": "-43789 + -916376 + -537065 * 140877 ", "answer": "-75661066170", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "849", "question": "940826 + 615017 + 919946 * 375068 - -898951 ", "answer": "345044761122", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "850", "question": "-928 - 914 * -561 ", "answer": "511826", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "851", "question": "-456 + -404 - 848 * -123 - 991 ", "answer": "102453", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "852", "question": "-436172 + -8182 - -908391 - 441510 * -553576 ", "answer": "244409803797", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "853", "question": "-1916 * 7251 ", "answer": "-13892916", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "854", "question": "-657 + -687 ", "answer": "-1344", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "855", "question": "-39007 + 2891 + -11699 ", "answer": "-47815", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "856", "question": "-912 - -292 * 930 + -134 ", "answer": "270514", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "857", "question": "352 + 681 ", "answer": "1033", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "858", "question": "-37195 * -90792 - 72795 * -61280 - 35814 ", "answer": "7837850226", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "859", "question": "-828 - -6783 ", "answer": "5955", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "860", "question": "-581863 - 283672 ", "answer": "-865535", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "861", "question": "-889 + 872 - -160 * 992 ", "answer": "158703", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "862", "question": "-60561 - -67329 ", "answer": "6768", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "863", "question": "57 - -35 - -43 * -73 + 14 ", "answer": "-3033", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "864", "question": "-38 + -93 + -92 + -79 * 29 ", "answer": "-2514", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "865", "question": "725 - 419 + 264 - -71 ", "answer": "641", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "866", "question": "100 * 13 * -76 * -5 ", "answer": "494000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "867", "question": "443 + -375 * 149 ", "answer": "-55432", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "868", "question": "633 + 720 * -57 ", "answer": "-40407", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "869", "question": "2189 - -5700 + -9613 ", "answer": "-1724", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "870", "question": "27 + -73 + 19 * 43 - -99 ", "answer": "870", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "871", "question": "-10 * -64 ", "answer": "640", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "872", "question": "-86 * -97 - 23 + -13 * 39 ", "answer": "7812", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "873", "question": "-28 + 28 - -95 - 77 ", "answer": "18", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "874", "question": "566 + 530 * 786 + 558 - 420 ", "answer": "417284", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "875", "question": "-98461 + -146508 * 560737 + 866749 ", "answer": "-82151688108", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "876", "question": "-168 + -187 ", "answer": "-355", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "877", "question": "327168 - -590493 - 815996 * -307144 ", "answer": "250629193085", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "878", "question": "-1568 * -9182 + 9549 ", "answer": "14406925", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "879", "question": "3092 - 8973 ", "answer": "-5881", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "880", "question": "-35 * 24 * -47 + -14 * 13 ", "answer": "39298", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "881", "question": "-14101 - -45309 ", "answer": "31208", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "882", "question": "588 * -748 * 936 ", "answer": "-411675264", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "883", "question": "11977 - -64380 - 76700 ", "answer": "-343", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "884", "question": "420094 + -800817 * -307095 * -346678 - 373616 ", "answer": "-85257444664648492", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "885", "question": "253 * 186 * -175 * 920 ", "answer": "-7576338000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "886", "question": "-24 * -30 * 1 * 39 + -23 ", "answer": "28057", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "887", "question": "69201 * 39671 ", "answer": "2745272871", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "888", "question": "32842 - -88785 + 26705 + 70814 ", "answer": "219146", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "889", "question": "53888 + -36739 ", "answer": "17149", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "890", "question": "78168 * -34363 + -14252 * -98833 * 40411 ", "answer": "56918951966492", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "891", "question": "25 + -53 ", "answer": "-28", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "892", "question": "742230 * 352900 + -603294 + -844931 + 812408 ", "answer": "261932331183", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "893", "question": "1 * -5 ", "answer": "-5", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 1}
{"id": "894", "question": "-489528 * -319467 * -854591 - 918608 * 277513 ", "answer": "-133648067764137320", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "895", "question": "445960 - 930241 ", "answer": "-484281", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "896", "question": "-7732 + 3673 * -8452 ", "answer": "-31051928", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "897", "question": "703 - 793 + 473 * 553 * -452 ", "answer": "-118229278", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "898", "question": "61 * -62 * -98 + 22 ", "answer": "370658", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "899", "question": "-99 + 24 + 69 ", "answer": "-6", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "900", "question": "543166 * 237190 * -218220 - 590739 - 119929 ", "answer": "-28114055872009468", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "901", "question": "11294 + -64498 - -24736 ", "answer": "-28468", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "902", "question": "7122 + -86437 ", "answer": "-79315", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "903", "question": "-772657 + 217329 + -179999 ", "answer": "-735327", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "904", "question": "-3983 - -6927 ", "answer": "2944", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "905", "question": "-600603 - 661607 + -746803 ", "answer": "-2009013", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "906", "question": "-75 - 64 - -21 * 73 * 97 ", "answer": "148562", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "907", "question": "-802 - 189 - -12 ", "answer": "-979", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "908", "question": "-49 + 89 - 28 - -91 ", "answer": "103", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "909", "question": "1232 + 6977 * -7386 * 1576 * 7878 ", "answer": "-639808810013584", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "910", "question": "62469 - 464860 ", "answer": "-402391", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "911", "question": "-24 - -973 * 812 ", "answer": "790052", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "912", "question": "5641 * -2581 - 8243 - -2293 ", "answer": "-14565371", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "913", "question": "3511 - -7740 * -921 ", "answer": "-7125029", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "914", "question": "81 + -73 * 93 * 75 + 84 ", "answer": "-509010", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "915", "question": "-56 * -40 + -66 + 94 ", "answer": "2268", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "916", "question": "769 * 97 * 185 + 855 - 300 ", "answer": "13800260", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "917", "question": "-958 + 855 + -674 ", "answer": "-777", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "918", "question": "-54 * -51 + 76 - -71 - 59 ", "answer": "2842", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "919", "question": "312 + -767 - -402 ", "answer": "-53", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "920", "question": "48 + -36 - 85 + -22 ", "answer": "-95", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "921", "question": "-19925 - 74029 - 31724 * 30366 - -6710 ", "answer": "-963418228", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "922", "question": "529669 - 733828 ", "answer": "-204159", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "923", "question": "2607 * -1459 ", "answer": "-3803613", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "924", "question": "-47 + -58 + 38 - 18 + 17 ", "answer": "-68", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "925", "question": "-77902 + -34627 * 66853 - -77350 + -87360 ", "answer": "-2315006743", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "926", "question": "-59076 * -20695 + -95528 + -34582 ", "answer": "1222447710", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "927", "question": "-3003 - 8379 ", "answer": "-11382", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "928", "question": "-449 * 997 - -520 + 158 ", "answer": "-446975", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "929", "question": "73 * -75 ", "answer": "-5475", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "930", "question": "34997 + 5241 ", "answer": "40238", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "931", "question": "122288 * 860430 ", "answer": "105220263840", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "932", "question": "72547 * -91323 + 91746 ", "answer": "-6625117935", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "933", "question": "-93 - -77 * -72 ", "answer": "-5637", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "934", "question": "-7737 - -3206 + 5241 ", "answer": "710", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "935", "question": "7240 * -5419 ", "answer": "-39233560", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "936", "question": "22 * 12 - -53 * -6 ", "answer": "-54", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "937", "question": "1203 - -1843 + 7240 ", "answer": "10286", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "938", "question": "8536 * -7418 + -5830 + 1438 * 1712 ", "answer": "-60864022", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "939", "question": "-22101 * 53912 * -77237 - 10763 * 44371 ", "answer": "92028111718471", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "940", "question": "849 + 629 - 970 ", "answer": "508", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "941", "question": "98756 - 28855 - -2784 ", "answer": "72685", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "942", "question": "-1 + -12 ", "answer": "-13", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "943", "question": "-55 * -76 ", "answer": "4180", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "944", "question": "171 * 426 + 195 - -504 ", "answer": "73545", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "945", "question": "36 + 2 - -5 * -49 ", "answer": "-207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "946", "question": "15827 - 65933 * -85808 ", "answer": "5657594691", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "947", "question": "7156 * 5378 - -7855 - -1615 + 8530 ", "answer": "38502968", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "948", "question": "8507 - 3565 - -2678 ", "answer": "7620", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "949", "question": "33 + -82 ", "answer": "-49", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "950", "question": "4684 - -4374 * 2417 - -6879 * -9221 ", "answer": "-52854617", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "951", "question": "6615 + 8401 + -9144 - 2347 - -5975 ", "answer": "9500", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "952", "question": "267354 + -625758 - 284996 ", "answer": "-643400", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "953", "question": "91457 - -413303 ", "answer": "504760", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "954", "question": "-986 - -536 - -273 ", "answer": "-177", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "955", "question": "5159 * -7759 ", "answer": "-40028681", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "956", "question": "-59220 * -86116 ", "answer": "5099789520", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "957", "question": "-71169 - -51686 * -107 ", "answer": "-5601571", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "958", "question": "76779 * -73663 ", "answer": "-5655771477", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "959", "question": "-31 + -40 ", "answer": "-71", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "960", "question": "-4745 * 4600 + 2351 ", "answer": "-21824649", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "961", "question": "-9251 - 5867 - -2092 + 6249 ", "answer": "-6777", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "962", "question": "1710 + -2710 * 7458 ", "answer": "-20209470", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "963", "question": "276728 * 859162 + 498693 + 741855 ", "answer": "237755422484", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "964", "question": "-21 - -99 ", "answer": "78", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "965", "question": "71942 - -59441 * -27920 ", "answer": "-1659520778", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "966", "question": "9 - 59 ", "answer": "-50", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "967", "question": "-1868 + -3779 + -7550 ", "answer": "-13197", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "968", "question": "30 + -83 * 99 * 74 - -60 ", "answer": "-607968", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "969", "question": "-95 + -59 - 13 - 74 - 19 ", "answer": "-260", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "970", "question": "2432 + 9992 * -3742 + -8982 ", "answer": "-37396614", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "971", "question": "-43 * -18 - 99 + 22 ", "answer": "697", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "972", "question": "26 * 26 * -28 ", "answer": "-18928", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "973", "question": "-67955 - -51615 - -43480 - 61200 - -45871 ", "answer": "11811", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "974", "question": "81 - -21 * 62 ", "answer": "1383", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "975", "question": "2776 + -6153 + 6045 - 9385 ", "answer": "-6717", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "976", "question": "85 * -77 - -84 - -87 - 83 ", "answer": "-6457", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "977", "question": "-991 * -784 - 308 ", "answer": "776636", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "978", "question": "-489156 * 75382 ", "answer": "-36873557592", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "979", "question": "160 * -698 - -207 ", "answer": "-111473", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "980", "question": "226270 + -990223 + -543545 ", "answer": "-1307498", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "981", "question": "-488 * -112 - -382 - 405 ", "answer": "54633", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "982", "question": "-943 + 933 * -871 - 845 ", "answer": "-814431", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "983", "question": "657 - 647 * 52 - -676 ", "answer": "-32311", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "984", "question": "6 * 38 ", "answer": "228", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "985", "question": "-17 - -47 + -83 ", "answer": "-53", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "986", "question": "-3394 - 206 + 1821 ", "answer": "-1779", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "987", "question": "71918 * -90647 ", "answer": "-6519150946", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "988", "question": "2524 * -9979 * -3080 * 5533 + 9314 ", "answer": "429227718522754", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "989", "question": "493682 + -411953 ", "answer": "81729", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "990", "question": "-39 + 55 - 38 + 24 * -20 ", "answer": "-502", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "991", "question": "682 * -134 + -168 - 174 * -835 ", "answer": "53734", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "992", "question": "-7431 * -6532 - 6150 - -7925 - -2492 ", "answer": "48543559", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "993", "question": "-901224 + 876386 * 368178 - 856758 * -114657 ", "answer": "420898445490", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "994", "question": "492914 * 952513 + -65981 - -379552 ", "answer": "469507306453", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "995", "question": "-586577 - -420516 ", "answer": "-166061", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "996", "question": "979430 * 464022 + 275975 - -436779 + 52912 ", "answer": "454477833126", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "997", "question": "-859 * -206 * 33 ", "answer": "5839482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "998", "question": "-4316 - -8483 ", "answer": "4167", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "999", "question": "581 * 455 ", "answer": "264355", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1000", "question": "-33828 - 4502 * -93100 - 73055 + 29860 ", "answer": "419059177", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1001", "question": "3230 * -8202 * 216 - -9831 ", "answer": "-5722361529", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1002", "question": "55569 + -74991 * -6747 - -11674 ", "answer": "506031520", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1003", "question": "-53279 - 47858 + -36457 - -60067 + 1550 ", "answer": "-75977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1004", "question": "989478 - 572894 - 972970 ", "answer": "-556386", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1005", "question": "-2813 + 464 - -5231 - -6780 + 9684 ", "answer": "19346", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1006", "question": "-11 * -32 ", "answer": "352", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1007", "question": "-56414 - 97142 - -46373 ", "answer": "-107183", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1008", "question": "89 + -47 ", "answer": "42", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1009", "question": "11373 * 78446 - -46720 + 17082 - 36613 ", "answer": "892193547", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1010", "question": "-983593 - -28303 * 697085 * -209844 - -239425 ", "answer": "-4140137502200388", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1011", "question": "-10 * -98 * -4 + -3 ", "answer": "-3923", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1012", "question": "258462 - -684916 * -556535 + -412188 ", "answer": "-381179879786", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1013", "question": "-81213 * 36431 - -84723 * -93508 + -52556 ", "answer": "-10881001643", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1014", "question": "-993081 + 746290 * -696879 * -933439 ", "answer": "485457194782928409", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1015", "question": "212 - 926 + -692 ", "answer": "-1406", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1016", "question": "21 + -43 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1017", "question": "809567 - 563722 ", "answer": "245845", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1018", "question": "651235 * -161507 ", "answer": "-105179011145", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1019", "question": "-655770 + -242644 * -150411 + 827400 - 631593 ", "answer": "36495866721", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1020", "question": "-28 - -67 - -70 + 53 - 19 ", "answer": "143", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1021", "question": "35928 + -283540 + 383431 ", "answer": "135819", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1022", "question": "913 - -793 - -699 ", "answer": "2405", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1023", "question": "-34734 + -66549 - 71806 ", "answer": "-173089", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1024", "question": "-54913 + -68597 + 34030 - -12821 ", "answer": "-76659", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1025", "question": "29 * 80 * -15 - -93 + 65 ", "answer": "-34642", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1026", "question": "-3819 * 6386 - -662 * 4061 - -8268 ", "answer": "-21691484", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1027", "question": "1774 * 5712 - -603 + -4975 + -8037 ", "answer": "10120679", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1028", "question": "-79 - 99 - 89 ", "answer": "-267", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1029", "question": "-200216 - -583948 - -772195 - -576376 * 90119 ", "answer": "51943584671", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1030", "question": "-511944 - -255504 - 758851 ", "answer": "-1015291", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1031", "question": "12882 + 91051 - -95280 + -9771 ", "answer": "189442", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1032", "question": "-30 * 44 + 46 ", "answer": "-1274", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1033", "question": "-79047 - -44638 ", "answer": "-34409", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1034", "question": "596545 - -542718 ", "answer": "1139263", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1035", "question": "-7309 + -9785 * -3274 ", "answer": "32028781", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1036", "question": "6 + 37 * 58 + -78 ", "answer": "2074", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1037", "question": "-370569 * 127850 + -465297 ", "answer": "-47377711947", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1038", "question": "625 + 147 + -429 + 285 - 721 ", "answer": "-93", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1039", "question": "-58 * 98 * -47 - 6 + 92 ", "answer": "267234", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1040", "question": "-10211 * 99316 + -43535 ", "answer": "-1014159211", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1041", "question": "-792753 + -358095 * -257692 + 959566 - -166809 ", "answer": "92278550362", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1042", "question": "-353254 * 234467 ", "answer": "-82826405618", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1043", "question": "91 - -55 - 64 - -100 - 64 ", "answer": "118", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1044", "question": "224409 - -136417 + 171786 + 925567 - -69674 ", "answer": "1527853", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1045", "question": "-76 - 87 * -58 ", "answer": "4970", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1046", "question": "155 + 411 * 681 * 208 + -71 ", "answer": "58217412", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1047", "question": "-193898 - 371559 + 851939 * 647464 ", "answer": "551599267239", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1048", "question": "-9793 + -63203 - -71135 ", "answer": "-1861", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1049", "question": "-795149 + -328278 + 28955 * 532502 ", "answer": "15417471983", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1050", "question": "-488 + 534 - -749 * 694 ", "answer": "519852", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1051", "question": "55102 - 92258 + -84618 * -67211 ", "answer": "5687223242", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1052", "question": "685 - -7507 ", "answer": "8192", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1053", "question": "-537626 - 476331 * 112739 + -266713 ", "answer": "-53701884948", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1054", "question": "2451 * 2402 ", "answer": "5887302", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1055", "question": "-414 - 927 ", "answer": "-1341", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1056", "question": "-4041 + -4949 * 1407 - 9904 ", "answer": "-6977188", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1057", "question": "204 + -702 * -710 + -129 * -546 ", "answer": "569058", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1058", "question": "-34 + -99 * 87 ", "answer": "-8647", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1059", "question": "3554 * -4141 * -4901 * 9385 ", "answer": "676926683075890", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1060", "question": "-419002 + -29431 - 34870 + -392615 + -342270 ", "answer": "-1218188", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1061", "question": "-76533 + -49690 * 62017 - -54839 ", "answer": "-3081646424", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1062", "question": "-8936 * -336 ", "answer": "3002496", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1063", "question": "-26789 - 81427 - 29410 - -18551 * -35175 ", "answer": "-652669051", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1064", "question": "12 * 27 + 63 ", "answer": "387", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1065", "question": "-79497 - 75338 - -51507 * -80825 ", "answer": "-4163208110", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1066", "question": "8387 + -4819 ", "answer": "3568", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1067", "question": "-628 - 702 - 327 ", "answer": "-1657", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1068", "question": "-6099 - 9342 - 8964 ", "answer": "-24405", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1069", "question": "-545 + -886 - -130 ", "answer": "-1301", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1070", "question": "-13 * 2 - -84 ", "answer": "58", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1071", "question": "427056 - 574911 ", "answer": "-147855", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1072", "question": "159221 * 841315 + 384731 * 93000 + -296918 ", "answer": "169734701697", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1073", "question": "35 + -20 ", "answer": "15", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1074", "question": "-94 - 62 * -50 * 45 + -4 ", "answer": "139402", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1075", "question": "608 + 30 - -272 - -576 * -460 ", "answer": "-264050", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1076", "question": "863 * -603 + -17 ", "answer": "-520406", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1077", "question": "-33623 + -40614 - 72804 ", "answer": "-147041", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1078", "question": "-212 * -4077 * -5556 ", "answer": "-4802184144", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1079", "question": "844612 + -488023 - 493843 + -84713 ", "answer": "-221967", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1080", "question": "-977 - 652 + -435 + 964 ", "answer": "-1100", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1081", "question": "-4740 + 6031 * -4600 - 7192 * 351 ", "answer": "-30271732", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1082", "question": "-65 * -88 - -50 ", "answer": "5770", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1083", "question": "11 + -86 * -65 - -15 ", "answer": "5616", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1084", "question": "4576 - -3792 - 7303 + 8374 ", "answer": "9439", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1085", "question": "27 + 42 * -30 ", "answer": "-1233", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1086", "question": "87424 * -494775 - 646908 + 646769 * 307369 ", "answer": "155540884253", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1087", "question": "107065 * 760773 ", "answer": "81452161245", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1088", "question": "69644 - 47112 + -48265 - -7403 ", "answer": "-18330", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1089", "question": "-99 * -48 ", "answer": "4752", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1090", "question": "524433 * -771605 * -666778 - -873194 ", "answer": "269815134914785964", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1091", "question": "25872 - -49274 * 90606 - 25114 - 845 ", "answer": "4464519957", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1092", "question": "68 - 46 ", "answer": "22", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1093", "question": "504 - -154 - -84 ", "answer": "742", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1094", "question": "42224 - -351881 - 432287 + 395515 + -602288 ", "answer": "-244955", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1095", "question": "-4306 + 2819 * 1997 - 701 ", "answer": "5624536", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1096", "question": "8419 + 3906 ", "answer": "12325", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1097", "question": "-6040 + -7644 * -1378 ", "answer": "10527392", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1098", "question": "-4297 * -7339 * -2265 - -4738 ", "answer": "-71428317257", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1099", "question": "-8069 - -2642 - 4575 - -1052 ", "answer": "-8950", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1100", "question": "-6298 + -2234 - 2453 + -6688 * 6190 ", "answer": "-41409705", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1101", "question": "-148 - -592 * 255 * 827 - -771 ", "answer": "124844543", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1102", "question": "408191 - 101023 + -350387 * -818266 ", "answer": "286710076110", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1103", "question": "550 * 490 * -94 ", "answer": "-25333000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1104", "question": "-7129 - 655 - 7969 * -1014 + -453 ", "answer": "8072329", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1105", "question": "873504 * -125023 - -579291 ", "answer": "-109207511301", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1106", "question": "-3122 * -1978 + -6727 ", "answer": "6168589", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1107", "question": "570 - 2171 - -598 ", "answer": "-1003", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1108", "question": "95 - 46 * 44 * -13 - -61 ", "answer": "26468", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1109", "question": "315109 + -361812 * 575908 * -248339 - -515400 ", "answer": "51746503048413853", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1110", "question": "2978 + -47514 * -71496 ", "answer": "3397063922", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1111", "question": "691 + -47 * -698 ", "answer": "33497", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1112", "question": "-80 - 65 - 909 + -155 ", "answer": "-1209", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1113", "question": "885 + 865 - 573 + -780 ", "answer": "397", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1114", "question": "935 * -730 + 428 ", "answer": "-682122", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1115", "question": "-611746 + 482904 + -837801 ", "answer": "-966643", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1116", "question": "-624 - 674 ", "answer": "-1298", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1117", "question": "-3750 + 71320 * 35333 * 36871 ", "answer": "92913060223010", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1118", "question": "639535 + -452581 + 899567 ", "answer": "1086521", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1119", "question": "67595 - -97542 + -80237 ", "answer": "84900", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1120", "question": "-653671 + 924103 * 960243 * -226158 ", "answer": "-200684340192258253", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1121", "question": "-85578 * -905436 * 616347 - 309636 - -544419 ", "answer": "47757895071659559", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1122", "question": "-551 + 990 + 791 ", "answer": "1230", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1123", "question": "-87 * 728 - 223 + -296 - -569 ", "answer": "-63286", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1124", "question": "-332241 + 66172 + -156731 ", "answer": "-422800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1125", "question": "-1443 - -286 + -8673 ", "answer": "-9830", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1126", "question": "-7101 - 3866 + 3016 ", "answer": "-7951", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1127", "question": "11127 + -77498 + -73686 - -34240 ", "answer": "-105817", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1128", "question": "216799 - 544107 - -545568 ", "answer": "218260", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1129", "question": "7313 * -9505 ", "answer": "-69510065", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1130", "question": "-934393 - -542057 ", "answer": "-392336", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1131", "question": "12 - 89 + 98 - -27 * 5 ", "answer": "156", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1132", "question": "5514 - -7434 * -2278 + -457 ", "answer": "-16929595", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1133", "question": "1895 * 3401 + 1566 ", "answer": "6446461", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1134", "question": "418 + 213 ", "answer": "631", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1135", "question": "-266572 + 498666 ", "answer": "232094", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1136", "question": "-2 - 62 ", "answer": "-64", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1137", "question": "-672102 * 309504 + -879987 - 82067 ", "answer": "-208019219462", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1138", "question": "-382 * -711 ", "answer": "271602", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1139", "question": "-6502 - 7119 - 8108 + 4853 ", "answer": "-16876", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1140", "question": "-71 - -18 - 20 * 78 ", "answer": "-1613", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1141", "question": "597753 - -748003 * 112746 ", "answer": "84334943991", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1142", "question": "307896 - -929839 * 794401 ", "answer": "738665339335", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1143", "question": "-48 + 3 ", "answer": "-45", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1144", "question": "-56 - -88 ", "answer": "32", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1145", "question": "-48660 - -63120 ", "answer": "14460", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1146", "question": "-2 + -492 ", "answer": "-494", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1147", "question": "783 + -5904 - -515 * -622 ", "answer": "-325451", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1148", "question": "2422 + -1411 + -7000 - -2793 * -2030 ", "answer": "-5675779", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1149", "question": "-954435 - 879101 - -390930 ", "answer": "-1442606", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1150", "question": "641 * 791 * -165 ", "answer": "-83660115", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1151", "question": "260 + -908 ", "answer": "-648", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1152", "question": "-1 - -70 * -47 + 74 ", "answer": "-3217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1153", "question": "-404685 * -706498 ", "answer": "285909143130", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1154", "question": "19 * -76 ", "answer": "-1444", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1155", "question": "-32 * -23 + 38 - 26 ", "answer": "748", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1156", "question": "-94479 - 2344 - -36161 - -81765 + -36003 ", "answer": "-14900", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1157", "question": "-8577 - -3377 ", "answer": "-5200", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1158", "question": "33514 + 67645 * -8138 - 5302 ", "answer": "-550466798", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1159", "question": "998068 * 47332 - -137587 + -289364 * -435799 ", "answer": "173345233999", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1160", "question": "6961 - -6383 - -1844 - -3736 + 989 ", "answer": "19913", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1161", "question": "-687916 + -391594 - 466777 ", "answer": "-1546287", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1162", "question": "10214 + 35868 ", "answer": "46082", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1163", "question": "92 * 57 - -81 * 98 - -34 ", "answer": "13216", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1164", "question": "13761 - -69447 ", "answer": "83208", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1165", "question": "-699343 + -268508 - -218413 ", "answer": "-749438", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1166", "question": "-94012 + 36228 ", "answer": "-57784", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1167", "question": "985900 - 193085 * -133180 * 468792 - -183315 ", "answer": "12055014549326815", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1168", "question": "51093 + -88716 - 61035 ", "answer": "-98658", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1169", "question": "472465 * 768150 + 913541 ", "answer": "362924903291", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1170", "question": "658 + 515 * 167 + 422 * -827 ", "answer": "-262331", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1171", "question": "1259 - -3472 ", "answer": "4731", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1172", "question": "-304 + -591 * -893 + -614 - -416 ", "answer": "527261", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1173", "question": "-1172 * 6356 + 1358 * 2178 ", "answer": "-4491508", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1174", "question": "-87737 + 3247 + 75875 * 59094 ", "answer": "4483672760", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1175", "question": "60 + 57 - 27 * -14 ", "answer": "495", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1176", "question": "167 + -427 * -482 ", "answer": "205981", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1177", "question": "-993973 + 375009 - -674197 + -938169 ", "answer": "-882936", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1178", "question": "-24002 - 42853 - 68696 - 23244 * 69865 ", "answer": "-1624077611", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1179", "question": "-67426 - 56143 ", "answer": "-123569", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1180", "question": "-20814 * 91809 ", "answer": "-1910912526", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1181", "question": "-155 + -827 + -161 + -460 + 411 ", "answer": "-1192", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1182", "question": "59731 - -54009 - 77479 + -38181 ", "answer": "-1920", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1183", "question": "-803 * 674 * -28 ", "answer": "15154216", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1184", "question": "53944 * 80526 ", "answer": "4343894544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1185", "question": "-78 + 34 ", "answer": "-44", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1186", "question": "-89342 * 1759 - 50088 - -35312 ", "answer": "-157167354", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1187", "question": "-6881 + 6215 ", "answer": "-666", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1188", "question": "-4742 + 986 + 1471 ", "answer": "-2285", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1189", "question": "17 + 6506 ", "answer": "6523", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1190", "question": "-24 - 19 ", "answer": "-43", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1191", "question": "47 - 84 + 53 ", "answer": "16", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1192", "question": "85207 - 68181 * 49968 + 46412 ", "answer": "-3406736589", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1193", "question": "57468 - 28820 * -71596 + 66116 + 61953 ", "answer": "2063582257", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1194", "question": "-75 + 40 + 74 * 87 - 77 ", "answer": "6326", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1195", "question": "-805 * 349 - -349 - 23 + -695 ", "answer": "-281314", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1196", "question": "-497246 - 195326 * -801832 - -937359 + -72841 ", "answer": "156619004504", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1197", "question": "-94731 - -60385 + -36929 - -78121 * -67046 ", "answer": "-5237771841", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1198", "question": "-430 - 782 * -917 - 103 ", "answer": "716561", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1199", "question": "44456 * -3436 - -97601 * 46675 * 64032 ", "answer": "291699331302784", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1200", "question": "-9068 + 2076 ", "answer": "-6992", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1201", "question": "95977 - 98032 + 13862 ", "answer": "11807", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1202", "question": "-864906 * -580565 * -510456 ", "answer": "-256317390637161840", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1203", "question": "-47856 - -41258 * -29427 ", "answer": "-1214147022", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1204", "question": "-36 - -91 + -41 - 69 * 39 ", "answer": "-2677", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1205", "question": "-931453 - 264796 + 289630 * -563247 * -84006 ", "answer": "13704170001415411", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1206", "question": "16 * -18 ", "answer": "-288", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1207", "question": "445 * -192 - 50 + -198 ", "answer": "-85688", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1208", "question": "-920 - 926 - 704 + 741 ", "answer": "-1809", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1209", "question": "-77729 + -66351 + -87434 * 93318 ", "answer": "-8159310092", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1210", "question": "-5085 * -51929 * -93934 + 82413 ", "answer": "-24804114735897", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1211", "question": "23 - 2344 ", "answer": "-2321", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1212", "question": "963 + -268 * -893 ", "answer": "240287", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1213", "question": "-711 + -285 ", "answer": "-996", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1214", "question": "-76 * 67 - -72 + -52 + 95 ", "answer": "-4977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1215", "question": "7163 * -7789 ", "answer": "-55792607", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1216", "question": "-48 + -47 * 75 ", "answer": "-3573", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1217", "question": "-455 + 542 ", "answer": "87", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1218", "question": "-79903 - 62418 + -28389 ", "answer": "-170710", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1219", "question": "4766 * 9715 - 1418 - 8315 ", "answer": "46291957", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1220", "question": "-438 * 924 - 497 ", "answer": "-405209", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1221", "question": "20106 * 31599 - -23300 - -61427 ", "answer": "635414221", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1222", "question": "533299 + -459369 + -457712 - 465008 ", "answer": "-848790", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1223", "question": "804 * 435 ", "answer": "349740", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1224", "question": "779 * 1726 ", "answer": "1344554", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1225", "question": "-3 + 47 + -77 ", "answer": "-33", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1226", "question": "-59288 + 14189 - -53948 + -13741 ", "answer": "-4892", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1227", "question": "-750 + -223 - 519 + -346 ", "answer": "-1838", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1228", "question": "-99 + -39 ", "answer": "-138", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1229", "question": "-2149 + -2275 + 1190 - 1606 ", "answer": "-4840", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1230", "question": "-211190 * 480913 - 594158 - 375656 ", "answer": "-101564986284", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1231", "question": "-373 - 853 + -194 ", "answer": "-1420", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1232", "question": "-66 + 51 * -30 ", "answer": "-1596", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1233", "question": "-395079 * 750871 + -620667 ", "answer": "-296653984476", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1234", "question": "8966 + 4319 ", "answer": "13285", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1235", "question": "-917 + 457 * -836 * 207 ", "answer": "-79085681", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1236", "question": "-34059 + -22266 - 49296 + -46106 ", "answer": "-151727", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1237", "question": "-99 - 49 ", "answer": "-148", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1238", "question": "-77921 + -39397 * -90613 + -33347 ", "answer": "3569769093", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1239", "question": "-864 + 607 + 285 + 923 ", "answer": "951", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1240", "question": "15 - -1 - 1 + 51 ", "answer": "66", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1241", "question": "1078 + -8949 - 2599 + -869 ", "answer": "-11339", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1242", "question": "-500 - 7542 * -9644 * -2755 - 3000 ", "answer": "-200385060740", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1243", "question": "89 - 336 ", "answer": "-247", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1244", "question": "711 - -1003 + -478 * 7068 ", "answer": "-3376790", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1245", "question": "7333 + -2087 + -3589 - 6821 ", "answer": "-5164", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1246", "question": "53 + 24 * -39 ", "answer": "-883", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1247", "question": "-87414 + 24982 * 31971 ", "answer": "798612108", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1248", "question": "3399 * -72917 - -68237 - -58778 ", "answer": "-247717868", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1249", "question": "228 - 992 * -859 - -825 * 808 ", "answer": "1518956", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1250", "question": "5279 - 4033 - -2538 ", "answer": "3784", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1251", "question": "-148896 + 154032 ", "answer": "5136", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1252", "question": "-24384 * 17715 - -43972 ", "answer": "-431918588", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1253", "question": "-962 * 330 ", "answer": "-317460", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1254", "question": "-8069 - -1219 - -4980 * -289 ", "answer": "-1446070", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1255", "question": "-25 - -39 - 16 * -37 ", "answer": "606", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1256", "question": "90235 - -44638 - 92403 - 22685 - 48689 ", "answer": "-28904", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1257", "question": "66025 - -69934 * -14699 + -68044 ", "answer": "-1027961885", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1258", "question": "5497 - -6332 + -8702 - -7271 + -2566 ", "answer": "7832", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1259", "question": "-7432 - -817 ", "answer": "-6615", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1260", "question": "-2547 * -3158 * -4912 ", "answer": "-39509308512", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1261", "question": "5344 * -7281 * 8101 + -5980 + 1685 ", "answer": "-315207192359", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1262", "question": "504093 - -333442 - -712415 * -634888 - 627585 ", "answer": "-452303524570", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1263", "question": "628 + 8505 * 1610 * 9316 ", "answer": "127564454428", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1264", "question": "-39 + -80 * -29 - 61 * 9 ", "answer": "1732", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1265", "question": "-370 + 914 - 5388 * 9523 + 9560 ", "answer": "-51299820", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1266", "question": "15 - -92 * -25 * 37 - -82 ", "answer": "-85003", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1267", "question": "-57711 * 96893 ", "answer": "-5591791923", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1268", "question": "-97 - -5812 - 8378 ", "answer": "-2663", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1269", "question": "-11 - -26 * -57 ", "answer": "-1493", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1270", "question": "-4037 * -3852 + 3917 ", "answer": "15554441", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1271", "question": "-730 - -324 ", "answer": "-406", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1272", "question": "-17568 + 19141 + -27750 ", "answer": "-26177", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1273", "question": "96 * -23 + -80 - -13 ", "answer": "-2275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1274", "question": "47 - -67 - -28 + 75 ", "answer": "217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1275", "question": "6840 + 7556 ", "answer": "14396", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1276", "question": "-8105 * -8725 ", "answer": "70716125", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1277", "question": "-49 - 4 + 49 * -22 - 35 ", "answer": "-1166", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1278", "question": "-4116 + 1808 * -9953 ", "answer": "-17999140", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1279", "question": "-244729 - 674760 ", "answer": "-919489", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1280", "question": "88 * -15 - -31 * -1 ", "answer": "-1351", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1281", "question": "18135 + -94355 ", "answer": "-76220", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1282", "question": "-220 * -199 * -752 ", "answer": "-32922560", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1283", "question": "-37691 + 772448 + 230925 + 378633 + -73413 ", "answer": "1270902", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1284", "question": "179 + 378 - 623 * 996 ", "answer": "-619951", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1285", "question": "-3246 + 7240 + -7983 * 4890 * -2174 ", "answer": "84866159374", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1286", "question": "-403 + 50 ", "answer": "-353", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1287", "question": "51 - 72 + 56 - 43 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1288", "question": "612 - -768 * 920 ", "answer": "707172", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1289", "question": "138 - -802 ", "answer": "940", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1290", "question": "-391 - -824 - -911 + 58 - 817 ", "answer": "585", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1291", "question": "51564 * 12328 - -785 - 69738 ", "answer": "635612039", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1292", "question": "3702 - -3741 ", "answer": "7443", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1293", "question": "9742 + -5511 ", "answer": "4231", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1294", "question": "76509 - 40453 ", "answer": "36056", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1295", "question": "30 * 20 - -25 * -29 ", "answer": "-125", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1296", "question": "-2002 + -12 ", "answer": "-2014", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1297", "question": "-12174 * -87370 - -12870 + 88516 * -18549 ", "answer": "-578228034", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1298", "question": "59878 + -28104 + -84404 * -26373 * -56933 ", "answer": "-126732100303862", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1299", "question": "62 - -85 ", "answer": "147", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1300", "question": "-4712 + -4166 - 2723 + -7193 ", "answer": "-18794", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1301", "question": "83 + -17 - -72 ", "answer": "138", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1302", "question": "-675366 * 771042 ", "answer": "-520735551372", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1303", "question": "-4159 - -4814 ", "answer": "655", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1304", "question": "-406 * -47 ", "answer": "19082", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1305", "question": "-2280 - 4841 ", "answer": "-7121", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1306", "question": "55 * -29 * 7 ", "answer": "-11165", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1307", "question": "39294 + -37272 - -56760 ", "answer": "58782", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1308", "question": "-48173 * 32445 - 63839 - 21284 ", "answer": "-1563058108", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1309", "question": "-536 * 67 - -719 - -819 ", "answer": "-34374", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1310", "question": "-9323 + -3538 + 7160 * 4402 * 1202 ", "answer": "37885007779", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1311", "question": "20 - -8 + -48 ", "answer": "-20", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1312", "question": "91923 * -92199 * -16823 - -88424 ", "answer": "142578435661595", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1313", "question": "-220 * -948 ", "answer": "208560", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1314", "question": "-5078 * -8036 ", "answer": "40806808", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1315", "question": "68360 + 6269 * 96962 * 38142 * -63008 ", "answer": "-1460827685751459448", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1316", "question": "-143 + 6593 * 3304 + 3758 ", "answer": "21786887", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1317", "question": "66976 + 17494 - -68689 ", "answer": "153159", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1318", "question": "-3223 * -6499 ", "answer": "20946277", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1319", "question": "7779 - -4246 + 7139 - 1812 ", "answer": "17352", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1320", "question": "-86 - 71 ", "answer": "-157", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1321", "question": "32230 + 75633 * -49418 ", "answer": "-3737599364", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1322", "question": "80 - -46 ", "answer": "126", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1323", "question": "-91920 * -984866 + -710080 - -471975 + 318238 ", "answer": "90528962853", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1324", "question": "1845 * 5037 + -2160 + 559 + 8845 ", "answer": "9300509", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1325", "question": "-588 + 268 ", "answer": "-320", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1326", "question": "144 + -906 * 499 ", "answer": "-451950", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1327", "question": "-83 * -74 + -44 ", "answer": "6098", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1328", "question": "-543 - -40 ", "answer": "-503", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1329", "question": "112 * 399 + -634 ", "answer": "44054", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1330", "question": "77092 * -1689 ", "answer": "-130208388", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1331", "question": "-215090 * -598587 + -30635 + -640005 + 978059 ", "answer": "128750385249", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1332", "question": "735394 * -611894 - -962599 ", "answer": "-449982213637", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1333", "question": "-37114 + 49598 + 27515 ", "answer": "39999", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1334", "question": "80 * -21 * -32 - 29 ", "answer": "53731", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1335", "question": "565398 * -899481 ", "answer": "-508564758438", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1336", "question": "-68988 * -14046 * -10189 + 72831 ", "answer": "-9873196436841", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1337", "question": "-9251 - 4977 + -8305 - -577 + -273 ", "answer": "-22229", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1338", "question": "-911565 + 556079 + -116424 + -829511 ", "answer": "-1301421", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1339", "question": "95905 - 66810 ", "answer": "29095", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1340", "question": "3 - 64 - 83 ", "answer": "-144", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1341", "question": "3921 + 8673 - -4013 ", "answer": "16607", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1342", "question": "-960 + 994 ", "answer": "34", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1343", "question": "-846 + 666 ", "answer": "-180", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1344", "question": "386 * -185 * -794 * 279 + -917 ", "answer": "15819170743", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1345", "question": "196 - 770 * 883 ", "answer": "-679714", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1346", "question": "-704 + -343 - 595 ", "answer": "-1642", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1347", "question": "-72137 - 52680 + -2652 ", "answer": "-127469", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1348", "question": "329646 - -33815 + 611550 ", "answer": "975011", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1349", "question": "43593 + -19000 + -19986 + 43856 ", "answer": "48463", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1350", "question": "8383 + -8585 - -2064 ", "answer": "1862", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1351", "question": "30324 + 73630 + -50232 + -83226 ", "answer": "-29504", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1352", "question": "-49339 * -43977 * -658077 ", "answer": "-1427883104726631", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1353", "question": "1401 * 4165 * 8529 ", "answer": "49768122285", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1354", "question": "-1768 - 8341 - 7260 + 1393 ", "answer": "-15976", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1355", "question": "979 * -295 * 110 + 335 ", "answer": "-31768215", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1356", "question": "486 - 135 ", "answer": "351", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1357", "question": "52 * -64 + -20 - 37 - 27 ", "answer": "-3412", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1358", "question": "75 + 23 + 65 + 2 ", "answer": "165", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1359", "question": "-50 * -49 - -45 * 62 + -9 ", "answer": "5231", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1360", "question": "-6724 - -8907 ", "answer": "2183", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1361", "question": "-3533 + 62306 + 79962 ", "answer": "138735", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1362", "question": "33352 - 9103 ", "answer": "24249", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1363", "question": "-1471 - 2937 ", "answer": "-4408", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1364", "question": "34 + -96 ", "answer": "-62", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1365", "question": "-3317 + 1076 ", "answer": "-2241", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1366", "question": "43609 + 10653 + -48433 * -59399 ", "answer": "2876926029", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1367", "question": "58 + 54 * -5 * -6 * -97 ", "answer": "-157082", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1368", "question": "-30676 + 80720 + 57961 ", "answer": "108005", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1369", "question": "9243 * 8949 - 9656 ", "answer": "82705951", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1370", "question": "-7083 + -8081 + 8172 ", "answer": "-6992", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1371", "question": "-66518 - -13605 - -23598 * -19704 ", "answer": "-465027905", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1372", "question": "634 - -264 + 181 * 189 + -827 ", "answer": "34280", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1373", "question": "-709709 - -971603 * -616540 - -408229 - -806111 ", "answer": "-599031608989", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1374", "question": "-739 - -933 ", "answer": "194", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1375", "question": "-293750 * -923759 - 427766 * 680914 + -274787 ", "answer": "-19917926661", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1376", "question": "50953 + -76809 + 4359 * 14750 ", "answer": "64269394", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1377", "question": "-58721 - -57782 + -17662 ", "answer": "-18601", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1378", "question": "82 * 1196 - -7499 - -4971 * 6161 ", "answer": "30731902", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1379", "question": "-664 * 36 - 901 * 841 ", "answer": "-781645", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1380", "question": "-780 - -464 - 246 * -674 - -991 ", "answer": "166479", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1381", "question": "98337 * -51458 ", "answer": "-5060225346", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1382", "question": "-7709 * 8955 ", "answer": "-69034095", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1383", "question": "9540 + -5788 ", "answer": "3752", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1384", "question": "38 - -78 - 81 - -74 ", "answer": "109", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1385", "question": "-8876 - 9969 * -5218 - -5565 - -9784 ", "answer": "52024715", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1386", "question": "-347 + 945 * 523 ", "answer": "493888", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1387", "question": "-12 + 60 ", "answer": "48", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1388", "question": "170 + -588 ", "answer": "-418", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1389", "question": "74 * -48 * 13 - -34 ", "answer": "-46142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1390", "question": "-8369 - -9843 - -1360 * -3212 ", "answer": "-4366846", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1391", "question": "29109 + -28228 + -31422 - 49503 ", "answer": "-80044", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1392", "question": "83 + -29 ", "answer": "54", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1393", "question": "419140 * -382672 ", "answer": "-160393142080", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1394", "question": "11 - 65 * 25 * -16 + -86 ", "answer": "25925", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1395", "question": "-3 + -3697 - -9750 + -3932 ", "answer": "2118", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1396", "question": "-972 * 389 + -579 + -107 + 219 ", "answer": "-378575", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1397", "question": "490572 + 558920 * 859985 ", "answer": "480663306772", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1398", "question": "-2098 + -11 ", "answer": "-2109", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1399", "question": "-595 * 452 ", "answer": "-268940", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1400", "question": "27 * -57 * 58 ", "answer": "-89262", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1401", "question": "-7236 * 5192 - -1717 ", "answer": "-37567595", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1402", "question": "104 - -610 ", "answer": "714", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1403", "question": "-15 + -98 * 49 - 27 ", "answer": "-4844", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1404", "question": "-339 - 40 + -803 * -969 * -318 ", "answer": "-247438405", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1405", "question": "-8045 * 2585 + 6560 - -6178 ", "answer": "-20783587", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1406", "question": "-28 + -16 ", "answer": "-44", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1407", "question": "-801 + 26 + 973 * -801 + 953 ", "answer": "-779195", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1408", "question": "-1110 + -3519 * 8859 + -8180 ", "answer": "-31184111", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1409", "question": "-99 - -337 - 613 ", "answer": "-375", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1410", "question": "-1158 + 3776 + 2409 - 2175 ", "answer": "2852", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1411", "question": "-90 * 59 + -43 ", "answer": "-5353", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1412", "question": "-93111 - 82579 + -43783 + -50126 ", "answer": "-269599", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1413", "question": "-424202 + -816285 - -165807 - 467402 * 71659 ", "answer": "-33494634598", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1414", "question": "-7252 * -9528 * 7594 * -8132 ", "answer": "-4267047787822848", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1415", "question": "-82 + -14 * 72 ", "answer": "-1090", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1416", "question": "-8 + 4 - 63 ", "answer": "-67", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1417", "question": "74849 + 77636 * -9635 + -4525 ", "answer": "-747952536", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1418", "question": "-862659 - 529455 + -511854 - -576044 ", "answer": "-1327924", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1419", "question": "27 - -19 * 57 ", "answer": "1110", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1420", "question": "97 + 48 + 38 ", "answer": "183", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1421", "question": "-355447 - 213077 ", "answer": "-568524", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1422", "question": "-617692 - -208197 + -528369 ", "answer": "-937864", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1423", "question": "-68 + 46 + 12 - -4 - -70 ", "answer": "64", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1424", "question": "-868495 * 68875 + 233578 ", "answer": "-59817359547", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1425", "question": "94 * -6384 + -304 + -9704 - 936 ", "answer": "-611040", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1426", "question": "-35 * -97 * -11 ", "answer": "-37345", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1427", "question": "404 - 160 ", "answer": "244", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1428", "question": "-41 + -25 ", "answer": "-66", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1429", "question": "144155 * -737633 * -670082 - -577313 ", "answer": "71252154373406743", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1430", "question": "-8248 + 6907 - 842 + -8985 ", "answer": "-11168", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1431", "question": "-816 * -887 - 950 - 24 ", "answer": "722818", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1432", "question": "-9497 * -9585 ", "answer": "91028745", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1433", "question": "280 - -625 + 664 ", "answer": "1569", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1434", "question": "-523434 + 200989 + 272695 + 160097 - -374600 ", "answer": "484947", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1435", "question": "806 * 876 + -370 ", "answer": "705686", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1436", "question": "8454 + -1670 * 4906 - 3458 ", "answer": "-8188024", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1437", "question": "423749 - 734569 - 704290 * -608722 * 856092 ", "answer": "367021037624168140", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1438", "question": "-74700 * 57779 - -66842 * 54250 * 34714 ", "answer": "125874844357700", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1439", "question": "962188 - 978832 + 398484 - 51310 ", "answer": "330530", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1440", "question": "-5731 * -148246 * -740470 ", "answer": "-629101702218220", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1441", "question": "70 + 21 + 95 ", "answer": "186", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1442", "question": "-71636 - 9994 * 31100 + -73444 ", "answer": "-310958480", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1443", "question": "-306 * -196 ", "answer": "59976", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1444", "question": "3 * 58 ", "answer": "174", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1445", "question": "-79 * -67 ", "answer": "5293", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1446", "question": "-6941 * -8635 * -7399 ", "answer": "-443463023465", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1447", "question": "67 * 92 + -41 + -92 - 82 ", "answer": "5949", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1448", "question": "-769 * 498 ", "answer": "-382962", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1449", "question": "-57032 - -28769 + -59527 * 75978 + 30068 ", "answer": "-4522740601", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1450", "question": "24496 - -19689 - -41565 + 4472 - 23675 ", "answer": "66547", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1451", "question": "-18303 + -83790 ", "answer": "-102093", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1452", "question": "45 + 540 - 552 - -116 * -905 ", "answer": "-104947", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1453", "question": "58733 + -83932 ", "answer": "-25199", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1454", "question": "68224 * -20644 ", "answer": "-1408416256", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1455", "question": "-52 - -98 + 43 ", "answer": "89", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1456", "question": "81 + 80 * -27 - 83 ", "answer": "-2162", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1457", "question": "7904 - 1526 ", "answer": "6378", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1458", "question": "-9426 + 1524 ", "answer": "-7902", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1459", "question": "21 * -77 ", "answer": "-1617", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1460", "question": "152 - -872 + -884 * 108 ", "answer": "-94448", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1461", "question": "-87 + -21 - 69 ", "answer": "-177", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1462", "question": "160 - -555 * 447 ", "answer": "248245", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1463", "question": "-22 + -77 - -49 ", "answer": "-50", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1464", "question": "-9003 - 2946 * 5719 + -7606 - 1803 ", "answer": "-16866586", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1465", "question": "126806 + -67597 - -35590 ", "answer": "94799", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1466", "question": "25 + 100 - -64 - -44 * -99 ", "answer": "-4167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1467", "question": "394 - 174 + -284 * -61 ", "answer": "17544", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1468", "question": "-21 + -10 ", "answer": "-31", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1469", "question": "-705025 * 445890 + -240266 + 860726 - -258272 ", "answer": "-314362718518", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1470", "question": "48906 * -20896 - 93219 ", "answer": "-1022032995", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1471", "question": "635749 * 266480 ", "answer": "169414393520", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1472", "question": "-832 * 9252 - -7447 + -8741 * -4022 ", "answer": "27466085", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1473", "question": "-877996 + -851910 * 992339 + -239821 + 3208 ", "answer": "-845384632099", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1474", "question": "-749 * -97 * -507 * 111 * 387 ", "answer": "-1582324144947", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1475", "question": "696 - -21 * -307 - -463 * -592 ", "answer": "-279847", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1476", "question": "-34 * 8 * -60 ", "answer": "16320", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1477", "question": "654 - 335 ", "answer": "319", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1478", "question": "3916 - 7657 - 1710 ", "answer": "-5451", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1479", "question": "370366 + 818920 - 789243 + -316514 ", "answer": "83529", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1480", "question": "-93 - 41 * -89 ", "answer": "3556", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1481", "question": "-55842 + 23283 ", "answer": "-32559", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1482", "question": "25732 * -57826 * 833 + -14553 - 99720 ", "answer": "-1239486314729", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1483", "question": "735 - 444 - -457 ", "answer": "748", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1484", "question": "-7997 + -9331 ", "answer": "-17328", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1485", "question": "-3364 - -4121 ", "answer": "757", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1486", "question": "-582 - -644 + 97 * -308 - -107 ", "answer": "-29707", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1487", "question": "912713 * 934447 ", "answer": "852881924711", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1488", "question": "-68568 * -30446 + -62692 ", "answer": "2087558636", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1489", "question": "69 - -47 * -7 ", "answer": "-260", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1490", "question": "-4271 - -3169 * 3524 ", "answer": "11163285", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1491", "question": "15 - -53 * -98 ", "answer": "-5179", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1492", "question": "-6590 - -62378 + 43345 * -70697 + -18397 ", "answer": "-3064324074", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1493", "question": "565 - 319 * 370 ", "answer": "-117465", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1494", "question": "842 - -771 ", "answer": "1613", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1495", "question": "5975 + -5607 ", "answer": "368", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1496", "question": "90 - -92 * -77 ", "answer": "-6994", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1497", "question": "561 * -6179 ", "answer": "-3466419", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1498", "question": "-851 - 9657 - -8690 ", "answer": "-1818", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1499", "question": "574 + -271 ", "answer": "303", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1500", "question": "9988 + -4597 - -8468 ", "answer": "13859", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1501", "question": "-41 * -96 + -39 ", "answer": "3897", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1502", "question": "680932 + -695578 + -679271 - -813408 ", "answer": "119491", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1503", "question": "541 - -898 - 663 + 489 + -759 ", "answer": "506", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1504", "question": "252885 * -410135 + -262363 * 795287 ", "answer": "-312370872656", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1505", "question": "1559 - -7845 + 8055 + 7408 ", "answer": "24867", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1506", "question": "-56958 - 9664 ", "answer": "-66622", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1507", "question": "4669 - -4434 - 6517 + 1964 ", "answer": "4550", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1508", "question": "586983 - 519521 + 274807 - -181320 ", "answer": "523589", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1509", "question": "-91 - -15 + -39 * 88 ", "answer": "-3508", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1510", "question": "-19 + -6 - 200 ", "answer": "-225", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1511", "question": "-3364 - -3201 - -5921 * -4119 ", "answer": "-24388762", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1512", "question": "839483 * 403639 + -346257 * -985518 - -474157 ", "answer": "680091058920", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1513", "question": "9133 - 3369 - -9193 ", "answer": "14957", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1514", "question": "84784 * 30286 ", "answer": "2567768224", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1515", "question": "79 * -28 + 41 ", "answer": "-2171", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1516", "question": "56 - -9 - 19 ", "answer": "46", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1517", "question": "-741 - 768 + 675 * 780 ", "answer": "524991", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1518", "question": "-96 - -49 ", "answer": "-47", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1519", "question": "-200 * -309 - -207 - 328 ", "answer": "61679", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1520", "question": "667 + -585 + 990 + 582 ", "answer": "1654", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1521", "question": "-75976 - -82457 ", "answer": "6481", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1522", "question": "-29428 + -34484 * -394 - 30332 * -31127 ", "answer": "957701432", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1523", "question": "30 - -83 + 98 * -57 * -19 ", "answer": "106247", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1524", "question": "1 - -92 + 94 * 76 + 4 ", "answer": "7241", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1525", "question": "-1569 * -3 * -3864 + 865 ", "answer": "-18186983", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1526", "question": "-67 - 57 + -83 * 72 + -19 ", "answer": "-6119", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1527", "question": "233 * 209 ", "answer": "48697", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1528", "question": "60376 + 76969 + -34412 ", "answer": "102933", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1529", "question": "6202 + -3991 * 2287 + -8776 ", "answer": "-9129991", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1530", "question": "-780292 + -272982 - 358685 ", "answer": "-1411959", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1531", "question": "-655 - -966 * -568 + 45 ", "answer": "-549298", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1532", "question": "453 + 321 - 679 * 826 * -147 ", "answer": "82446312", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1533", "question": "-808121 - -642416 * -955631 ", "answer": "-613913452617", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1534", "question": "-522764 + -321995 * 67932 ", "answer": "-21874287104", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1535", "question": "1026 + 6843 - -240 - -5334 - -7986 ", "answer": "21429", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1536", "question": "56 - 30 * 21 ", "answer": "-574", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1537", "question": "24 * -93 ", "answer": "-2232", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1538", "question": "67 - 3 + -30 - -65 - 62 ", "answer": "37", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1539", "question": "41357 * 60143 + -47543 * 91480 - 82260 ", "answer": "-1861981849", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1540", "question": "-551 - 175 - 756 ", "answer": "-1482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1541", "question": "-3 + -18 ", "answer": "-21", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1542", "question": "-35768 * -77472 * 70760 - 5061 - -84129 ", "answer": "196077268856028", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1543", "question": "975 * 276 ", "answer": "269100", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1544", "question": "-545 + -947 ", "answer": "-1492", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1545", "question": "-211 - 523 + -158 * 895 ", "answer": "-142144", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1546", "question": "2248 + 6610 - 7049 * 4967 ", "answer": "-35003525", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1547", "question": "-99 + -61 + 100 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1548", "question": "3477 - -5526 * -5471 ", "answer": "-30229269", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1549", "question": "-753 - 102 + -633 + 479 * 112 ", "answer": "52160", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1550", "question": "944337 * 305651 * -332114 - 321413 - -899872 ", "answer": "-95860570744421659", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1551", "question": "-11644 - 50935 + -4435 * 76429 + -73049 ", "answer": "-339098243", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1552", "question": "110713 - -198920 ", "answer": "309633", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1553", "question": "-5597 * -4365 + -6882 * -949 - 1484 ", "answer": "30960439", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1554", "question": "36 * 33 - -88 ", "answer": "1276", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1555", "question": "7213 + -7835 + 6131 + -68 ", "answer": "5441", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1556", "question": "906593 + 514365 * -122886 ", "answer": "-63207350797", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1557", "question": "-33 * 22 + 93 + 63 - 35 ", "answer": "-605", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1558", "question": "-5024 * -9042 ", "answer": "45427008", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1559", "question": "83419 + 90630 * 30601 * 12177 ", "answer": "33771309890929", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1560", "question": "86608 - 807257 + -909867 ", "answer": "-1630516", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1561", "question": "883035 + 372581 - 309203 ", "answer": "946413", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1562", "question": "50099 + -37195 - 93536 * -92714 ", "answer": "8672109608", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1563", "question": "83777 * -81931 - -41087 * 62483 ", "answer": "-4296694366", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1564", "question": "-4792 * 8339 - 8302 - 6225 ", "answer": "-39975015", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1565", "question": "26 - -55 + 85 ", "answer": "166", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1566", "question": "-38 + -26 + 29 ", "answer": "-35", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1567", "question": "2098 + 3508 ", "answer": "5606", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1568", "question": "65 - -53 + -63 + -21 ", "answer": "34", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1569", "question": "425930 * -57144 ", "answer": "-24339343920", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1570", "question": "8068 * -5042 + 8836 + 7293 * 2767 ", "answer": "-20490289", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1571", "question": "6775 - -2355 * 1272 + 490 - -8671 ", "answer": "3011496", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1572", "question": "823 * -258 + -500 + -912 - 649 ", "answer": "-214395", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1573", "question": "29 + 79 - -29 - 57 ", "answer": "80", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1574", "question": "-608 + -186 * -978 * 816 - 80 ", "answer": "148436240", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1575", "question": "-66383 - -26329 ", "answer": "-40054", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1576", "question": "6 + -33 ", "answer": "-27", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1577", "question": "330 + -72 ", "answer": "258", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1578", "question": "78277 - 86959 + 88513 * -716 * -28138 ", "answer": "1783254407822", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1579", "question": "394743 + -198013 * -183705 * 384419 ", "answer": "13983617150605878", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1580", "question": "-534 * 322 ", "answer": "-171948", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1581", "question": "-99 * 41 - 72 ", "answer": "-4131", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1582", "question": "-408160 - -137543 - -183930 + -734363 ", "answer": "-821050", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1583", "question": "-750112 * 862062 * -243983 * 515857 ", "answer": "81386713235866214028864", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1584", "question": "322493 * 4337 - -813497 - -542094 ", "answer": "1400007732", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1585", "question": "-1505 * -6648 * -6467 ", "answer": "-64703887080", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1586", "question": "-69794 - 68917 ", "answer": "-138711", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1587", "question": "5657 + 6694 ", "answer": "12351", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1588", "question": "4599 - 196 * -1408 ", "answer": "280567", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1589", "question": "179188 - 468516 + -285829 - 790738 + -658338 ", "answer": "-2024233", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1590", "question": "-522307 - 645379 ", "answer": "-1167686", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1591", "question": "-4975 * -5471 ", "answer": "27218225", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1592", "question": "-5853 - 9697 * 197 * 6301 * -462 ", "answer": "5561027932305", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1593", "question": "-910 * -834 ", "answer": "758940", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1594", "question": "-10 * -22 + -70 - 8 ", "answer": "142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1595", "question": "409138 + -435111 + 503588 + -403254 ", "answer": "74361", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1596", "question": "999 - -665 - 993 - -170 ", "answer": "841", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1597", "question": "-466 + 200 * -133 ", "answer": "-27066", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1598", "question": "-86 * -68 - 20 ", "answer": "5828", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1599", "question": "31 - 77 - -56 - -51 ", "answer": "61", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1600", "question": "-704115 - 742228 * -386725 ", "answer": "287037419185", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1601", "question": "856 - 443 ", "answer": "413", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1602", "question": "199570 - 398042 * -859434 ", "answer": "342091027798", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1603", "question": "6740 - 2797 ", "answer": "3943", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1604", "question": "9 * -73 - -37 - 53 * -81 ", "answer": "3673", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1605", "question": "89 + -70 ", "answer": "19", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1606", "question": "538336 - -21281 ", "answer": "559617", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1607", "question": "8672 - -8627 + -7906 ", "answer": "9393", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1608", "question": "136 * 460 * -482 - 467 + -57 ", "answer": "-30154444", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1609", "question": "-2523 - 671 * -4550 ", "answer": "3050527", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1610", "question": "481909 - 904989 ", "answer": "-423080", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1611", "question": "23478 - -66750 * 37718 ", "answer": "2517699978", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1612", "question": "984392 - 597725 ", "answer": "386667", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1613", "question": "-5732 * 1496 + 9427 + -1284 ", "answer": "-8566929", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1614", "question": "-376 + -482 * -728 ", "answer": "350520", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1615", "question": "84 + -62 - 30 * 55 * 96 ", "answer": "-158378", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1616", "question": "-10 - 10 - 75 + 95 ", "answer": "0", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1617", "question": "-4870 * -6594 ", "answer": "32112780", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1618", "question": "-5468 * 981 ", "answer": "-5364108", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1619", "question": "22347 * 55645 + 37386 + -70385 + -20348 ", "answer": "1243445468", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1620", "question": "-534 - 420 + -927 * -928 * 994 ", "answer": "855093510", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1621", "question": "-17799 + 39451 * -25491 + -32322 * -40231 ", "answer": "294683142", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1622", "question": "160638 * 791290 + -274870 - -623755 + -923011 ", "answer": "127110668894", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1623", "question": "163 - 926 ", "answer": "-763", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1624", "question": "-943 + 156 ", "answer": "-787", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1625", "question": "490 - -172 * -338 - 327 * -450 ", "answer": "89504", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1626", "question": "114357 - 513893 + 987815 + -331131 * 93473 ", "answer": "-30951219684", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1627", "question": "-621214 - 698969 + -623076 * -841972 ", "answer": "524611225689", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1628", "question": "4273 * 3761 ", "answer": "16070753", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1629", "question": "100 * -12 - -47 - -79 ", "answer": "-1074", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1630", "question": "-98355 * 60501 * -98956 ", "answer": "588845184307380", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1631", "question": "-55089 + 32583 ", "answer": "-22506", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1632", "question": "-704810 + 598128 + -74760 - 525811 * -229160 ", "answer": "120494667318", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1633", "question": "-68 + 70 - -45 ", "answer": "47", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1634", "question": "-9666 - -7888 * -2907 - -6518 + -3557 ", "answer": "-22937121", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1635", "question": "-311 * 851 * -115 - 622 - 811 ", "answer": "30434582", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1636", "question": "-448 - 989 * 42 + 337 ", "answer": "-41649", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1637", "question": "-509806 + -605637 ", "answer": "-1115443", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1638", "question": "767269 * 619433 ", "answer": "475271738477", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1639", "question": "-90772 * 98541 ", "answer": "-8944763652", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1640", "question": "5353 + 5741 + 2935 ", "answer": "14029", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1641", "question": "26613 * 17905 ", "answer": "476505765", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1642", "question": "90 + 78 ", "answer": "168", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1643", "question": "-3368 + 6003 * -2306 * 6918 ", "answer": "-95765310092", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1644", "question": "-696 - -866 - -804 ", "answer": "974", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1645", "question": "-597158 * 995840 + 822901 ", "answer": "-594672999819", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1646", "question": "-82402 - -37517 * 79095 - -78850 ", "answer": "2967403563", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1647", "question": "-234228 - -265633 - 88682 ", "answer": "-57277", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1648", "question": "-9223 - -20 + -6169 ", "answer": "-15372", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1649", "question": "-348 + 745 + 368 - 278 ", "answer": "487", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1650", "question": "-4412 + -98858 - -24905 * -68097 + -10020 ", "answer": "-1696069075", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1651", "question": "249 - 458 * 569 * -447 * -513 ", "answer": "-59758904973", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1652", "question": "743 * -83 + -594 * -743 ", "answer": "379673", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1653", "question": "-816 * 737 ", "answer": "-601392", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1654", "question": "-5920 * 24313 ", "answer": "-143932960", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1655", "question": "32 + -14 + -37 ", "answer": "-19", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1656", "question": "-51235 - 95466 * -78541 * -78763 ", "answer": "-590564588585113", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1657", "question": "693820 * 146460 + -114621 - -859948 + 237996 ", "answer": "101617860523", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1658", "question": "-879 + -773 * -319 - 102 - 521 ", "answer": "245085", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1659", "question": "-794207 - -412920 - 925947 + -417821 ", "answer": "-1725055", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1660", "question": "321060 - 982750 ", "answer": "-661690", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1661", "question": "-35 * -53 + 31 - -47 * 26 ", "answer": "3108", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1662", "question": "65 - -75 * -39 - 20 ", "answer": "-2880", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1663", "question": "66519 - 22150 * 72454 + 41797 - -35878 ", "answer": "-1604711906", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1664", "question": "-39040 - -83092 + -85247 * 33435 + -45282 ", "answer": "-2850234675", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1665", "question": "226 + -2945 ", "answer": "-2719", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1666", "question": "-5699 * -71 * 9660 * 2728 ", "answer": "10662977629920", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1667", "question": "3249 - -6220 + 2648 + -6907 ", "answer": "5210", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1668", "question": "503 + 717 * -713 + -113 ", "answer": "-510831", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1669", "question": "-393 * 446 * -558 * 587 - 752 ", "answer": "57411607036", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1670", "question": "14170 - 95726 - -88489 + 27254 ", "answer": "34187", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1671", "question": "152803 - -270200 ", "answer": "423003", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1672", "question": "765600 + 909792 + 952400 * 154169 ", "answer": "146832230992", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1673", "question": "-3137 * -7295 ", "answer": "22884415", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1674", "question": "4948 + 8175 * 498 - 5230 + -6837 ", "answer": "4064031", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1675", "question": "-304898 + 28511 ", "answer": "-276387", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1676", "question": "44 + 59 ", "answer": "103", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1677", "question": "-981 - -870 - -980 ", "answer": "869", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1678", "question": "491 - 771 - -340 ", "answer": "60", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1679", "question": "-3740 - 44166 * -11703 * 68849 * -96822 ", "answer": "-3445537327529694584", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1680", "question": "-7503 - 8215 - -8730 - 9181 * 2987 ", "answer": "-27430635", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1681", "question": "-9797 - -3254 - 2373 * 2323 + -1818 ", "answer": "-5520840", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1682", "question": "572177 * 988768 * 129486 * -397125 + 694865 ", "answer": "-29092084609286830129135", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1683", "question": "134617 + 972638 * -211892 * -273343 ", "answer": "56334409943748545", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1684", "question": "-47 + 77 * 64 ", "answer": "4881", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1685", "question": "64251 + 22869 + 89252 + 79602 * 83729 ", "answer": "6665172230", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1686", "question": "-11407 * -79544 * -53771 ", "answer": "-48789568956568", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1687", "question": "-28718 * 519389 * -667364 * -916760 + -726301 ", "answer": "-9125682825273592479581", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1688", "question": "399681 * -80143 - 508576 ", "answer": "-32032142959", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1689", "question": "-30364 - -87628 + -80529 ", "answer": "-23265", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1690", "question": "14289 + -39089 + -53974 ", "answer": "-78774", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1691", "question": "-15417 * -750669 - -159840 * -361658 * 203978 ", "answer": "-11791429266692187", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1692", "question": "-495099 * -879007 * -835490 * -951530 * -755482 ", "answer": "-261379935009605706300298492200", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1693", "question": "-7873 * 8013 ", "answer": "-63086349", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1694", "question": "442 * -91 ", "answer": "-40222", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1695", "question": "67 * -95 ", "answer": "-6365", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1696", "question": "-5635 + 31175 * -56147 ", "answer": "-1750388360", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1697", "question": "-64616 + 2138 * 94803 - 12773 - -87622 ", "answer": "202699047", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1698", "question": "73652 + -93647 ", "answer": "-19995", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1699", "question": "-14572 * -95648 - -45575 ", "answer": "1393828231", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1700", "question": "-628 - 744 + -458 - 61 + -139 ", "answer": "-2030", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1701", "question": "32265 * 2099 + -18943 ", "answer": "67705292", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1702", "question": "9681 * 2910 + 8503 - 7708 - -8968 ", "answer": "28181473", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1703", "question": "-42874 + 36916 + 46956 + 43482 ", "answer": "84480", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1704", "question": "-754190 - -711680 + 405825 - -99723 * 641474 ", "answer": "63970075017", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1705", "question": "953 + 395 - 638 * -695 ", "answer": "444758", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1706", "question": "31758 * 15124 + 46916 - -84913 ", "answer": "480439821", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1707", "question": "-80 + 33 * 50 * -61 ", "answer": "-100730", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1708", "question": "-2448 + 8748 * -5165 + -193 ", "answer": "-45186061", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1709", "question": "-929 - 2625 - -7614 - 9409 ", "answer": "-5349", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1710", "question": "-83662 * 50654 - -59273 + 31592 ", "answer": "-4237724083", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1711", "question": "679 + -69 * -36 * -227 + -938 ", "answer": "-564127", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1712", "question": "1198 + 9304 * -8497 * -1357 ", "answer": "107279112614", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1713", "question": "10 * -50 + -61 - 62 - -9 ", "answer": "-614", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1714", "question": "-441051 + 35901 - -326855 - -212029 - 631114 ", "answer": "-497380", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1715", "question": "1807 * 354 - 4039 - 4312 ", "answer": "631327", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1716", "question": "-74 * -4 ", "answer": "296", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1717", "question": "-417 + -159 + 837 ", "answer": "261", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1718", "question": "60106 * -19117 - -27926 ", "answer": "-1149018476", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1719", "question": "-512 + -389 * -652 - -59 - -89 ", "answer": "253264", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1720", "question": "388088 - 438411 + -69220 ", "answer": "-119543", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1721", "question": "-19781 * 93817 + -85921 * 54824 ", "answer": "-6566326981", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1722", "question": "6 - 37 ", "answer": "-31", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1723", "question": "-156729 - 215273 + -972953 ", "answer": "-1344955", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1724", "question": "1741 - -7788 ", "answer": "9529", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1725", "question": "72 - 38 ", "answer": "34", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1726", "question": "44 + -87 ", "answer": "-43", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1727", "question": "-548 * -190 + -153 - -326 ", "answer": "104293", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1728", "question": "333 + 799 + -388 ", "answer": "744", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1729", "question": "7691 - 5532 * 1959 + -6022 + 2358 ", "answer": "-10833161", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1730", "question": "-9593 - 2245 * -539 ", "answer": "1200462", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1731", "question": "-125570 * -722984 - -259334 ", "answer": "90785360214", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1732", "question": "-3349 * -8363 ", "answer": "28007687", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1733", "question": "-441399 - 782500 - 794333 + -457670 ", "answer": "-2475902", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1734", "question": "-54184 * 65254 - -52576 + 6529 * 19974 ", "answer": "-3405259914", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1735", "question": "-4254 + -8565 * 9066 * -70 * 1648 ", "answer": "8957737450146", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1736", "question": "13249 * 16519 ", "answer": "218860231", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1737", "question": "-72 * -40 * -14 + 20 ", "answer": "-40300", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1738", "question": "4964 + -9336 * 3648 + -4141 * 6780 ", "answer": "-62128744", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1739", "question": "57 - -41 ", "answer": "98", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1740", "question": "-1706 + -8847 - -8072 - -5422 + -7709 ", "answer": "-4768", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1741", "question": "5024 - -6688 * 15676 + -95930 ", "answer": "104750182", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1742", "question": "-98931 * 82320 ", "answer": "-8143999920", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1743", "question": "5258 + 9369 + 8089 ", "answer": "22716", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1744", "question": "422 + -947 ", "answer": "-525", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1745", "question": "-741 * 5149 - -5684 ", "answer": "-3809725", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1746", "question": "-7803 + -9420 ", "answer": "-17223", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1747", "question": "66 + -16 + 97 * 68 + -99 ", "answer": "6547", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1748", "question": "-38 * -61 * -61 ", "answer": "-141398", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1749", "question": "558316 - -867472 + -333848 + -628598 * 484643 ", "answer": "-304644528574", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1750", "question": "85115 * 66972 ", "answer": "5700321780", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1751", "question": "-7813 * -3525 + 3045 * 3651 - 5556 ", "answer": "38652564", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1752", "question": "-165839 - -281793 + 367542 - 342407 + -951419 ", "answer": "-810330", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1753", "question": "90 * -53 - 38 - 87 - -16 ", "answer": "-4879", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1754", "question": "604276 * -366319 + 944919 * 158271 + 853945 ", "answer": "-71803651050", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1755", "question": "98 * -23 * -42 * -72 ", "answer": "-6816096", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1756", "question": "69 + 93 * -3 + 93 + 71 ", "answer": "-46", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1757", "question": "165 + 130 * 994 ", "answer": "129385", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1758", "question": "-7512 + 54587 ", "answer": "47075", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1759", "question": "-85260 + -71663 - 51848 ", "answer": "-208771", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1760", "question": "68265 - -19146 - -87643 ", "answer": "175054", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1761", "question": "-758 * 463 - -431 + -935 + 507 ", "answer": "-350951", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1762", "question": "8668 * 3978 - 4136 + 2844 - -6202 ", "answer": "34486214", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1763", "question": "-200495 + 344661 ", "answer": "144166", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1764", "question": "-438316 * -551155 ", "answer": "241580054980", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1765", "question": "-76 * -3 * -73 ", "answer": "-16644", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1766", "question": "-131 + 684 + 333 - 941 + 886 ", "answer": "831", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1767", "question": "849360 + -174195 - -461419 * 248002 ", "answer": "114433510003", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1768", "question": "200694 - 558075 - 668748 ", "answer": "-1026129", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1769", "question": "-8880 * -58876 * 15382 * 16422 - -93934 ", "answer": "132065724199785454", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1770", "question": "-89551 + 31535 + -27622 + -75708 ", "answer": "-161346", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1771", "question": "-33736 + -33681 + -48765 ", "answer": "-116182", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1772", "question": "-36452 * 50611 ", "answer": "-1844872172", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1773", "question": "-2764 - 5791 + 6903 + -5263 ", "answer": "-6915", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1774", "question": "-5455 + -302 ", "answer": "-5757", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1775", "question": "-25752 - 1481 - -8721 * 23684 * 41752 ", "answer": "8623798916095", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1776", "question": "-82 * 39 * -76 + -47 ", "answer": "243001", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1777", "question": "35 * 65 ", "answer": "2275", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1778", "question": "54 + -695 + -674 * 550 ", "answer": "-371341", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1779", "question": "-25 - 28 ", "answer": "-53", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1780", "question": "6110 + -8638 ", "answer": "-2528", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1781", "question": "-5984 * 2338 * 792 ", "answer": "-11080548864", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1782", "question": "451 * -80 + -421 * 138 ", "answer": "-94178", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1783", "question": "4878 * -4027 * -2583 + -5926 ", "answer": "50739686672", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1784", "question": "811728 + -621538 - -942500 ", "answer": "1132690", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1785", "question": "-56815 * -53012 ", "answer": "3011876780", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1786", "question": "15 - -31 - 23 * 47 ", "answer": "-1035", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1787", "question": "-942 * -53 - 123 + -150 * 626 ", "answer": "-44097", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1788", "question": "-72 - -6 * 29 + 3 * 72 ", "answer": "318", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1789", "question": "-27 - 79 ", "answer": "-106", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1790", "question": "800669 * -285995 + -377402 ", "answer": "-228987708057", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1791", "question": "-78780 - -94160 ", "answer": "15380", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1792", "question": "-78284 + -73795 - 94317 ", "answer": "-246396", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1793", "question": "872 - -344 * -435 * -140 - -495 ", "answer": "20950967", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1794", "question": "3999 - 4135 - -7873 ", "answer": "7737", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1795", "question": "63 + -84 ", "answer": "-21", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1796", "question": "-3617 * 6705 * 9649 + 9622 ", "answer": "-234007393643", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1797", "question": "-426 + -813 * -18 + 510 + 418 ", "answer": "15136", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1798", "question": "185645 * -482805 * 350611 - -549894 - -320397 ", "answer": "-31425381112091184", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1799", "question": "-4076 * 8942 * 8372 ", "answer": "-305139240224", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1800", "question": "567543 - -631293 - 949749 + 27177 * -638748 ", "answer": "-17359005309", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1801", "question": "-600 + 765 * -669 ", "answer": "-512385", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1802", "question": "-80 - -96 - -85 - -96 + 76 ", "answer": "273", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1803", "question": "-78787 - -43216 * -41439 + 56013 ", "answer": "-1790850598", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1804", "question": "750 + 768 * -853 - -535 - 849 ", "answer": "-654668", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1805", "question": "-31 - -4 + -84 - 41 ", "answer": "-152", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1806", "question": "84668 + 365730 - 453234 - 371492 - 326008 ", "answer": "-700336", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1807", "question": "843 * 342 * -485 ", "answer": "-139828410", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1808", "question": "6429 - -3003 ", "answer": "9432", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1809", "question": "-35432 - -33536 + 77515 + 83121 * 64795 ", "answer": "5385900814", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1810", "question": "-91055 * -94959 ", "answer": "8646491745", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1811", "question": "-428833 + -631388 ", "answer": "-1060221", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1812", "question": "-30 + 33 - 61 - -47 ", "answer": "-11", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1813", "question": "7457 + 6264 - -1093 - 9970 - 6089 ", "answer": "-1245", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1814", "question": "540603 * 31341 - -363449 + 58613 + -380316 ", "answer": "16943080369", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1815", "question": "228 * 5576 ", "answer": "1271328", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1816", "question": "25543 + -43183 * -14355 ", "answer": "619917508", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1817", "question": "-985582 - 717460 + -809045 * -475669 ", "answer": "384835923063", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1818", "question": "3151 + -6673 ", "answer": "-3522", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1819", "question": "87 + 32 * 35 + 12 ", "answer": "1219", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1820", "question": "640 - -591 * -401 - 677 * 376 ", "answer": "-490903", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1821", "question": "241491 + -685460 ", "answer": "-443969", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1822", "question": "69160 + 738230 + 744203 * 870756 ", "answer": "648020034858", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1823", "question": "-987 * 305 - -997 * -438 ", "answer": "-737721", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1824", "question": "789 - -609 * 161 + -484 * 916 ", "answer": "-344506", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1825", "question": "8498 + -4444 ", "answer": "4054", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1826", "question": "3889 + -5746 * -1918 ", "answer": "11024717", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1827", "question": "-178518 * 960050 * 691479 ", "answer": "-118509962269526100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1828", "question": "91 * 32 * -45 ", "answer": "-131040", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1829", "question": "126 * 94 * 580 - -702 * -527 ", "answer": "6499566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1830", "question": "89429 * -2327 - -65897 ", "answer": "-208035386", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1831", "question": "-12980 * -99178 + 80166 ", "answer": "1287410606", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1832", "question": "-5920 * -7421 * -1808 + -233 * 4108 ", "answer": "-79430591724", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1833", "question": "-2793 * 8256 ", "answer": "-23059008", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1834", "question": "-710590 * -296276 - -123051 * 224328 - -769933 ", "answer": "238135317501", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1835", "question": "-49254 * 48174 ", "answer": "-2372762196", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1836", "question": "-8626 + 9892 ", "answer": "1266", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1837", "question": "-960 + 528 + 787 - -819 - -170 ", "answer": "1344", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1838", "question": "10785 + -9348 * 2012 * 29160 * -11492 ", "answer": "6302746168553505", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1839", "question": "73 + 98 * -24 - -53 - 12 ", "answer": "-2238", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1840", "question": "-2657 * -5455 + 1222 + 9227 - 5851 ", "answer": "14498533", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1841", "question": "28786 - 7108 ", "answer": "21678", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1842", "question": "468 + 55 ", "answer": "523", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1843", "question": "-8344 - 791 ", "answer": "-9135", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1844", "question": "663 + 332 - -33 ", "answer": "1028", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1845", "question": "920 - 365 * -65 * 467 - -271 ", "answer": "11080766", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1846", "question": "-11815 * -51715 - -92618 - 40851 + 21044 ", "answer": "611085536", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1847", "question": "-24 - 54 - -20 + 81 ", "answer": "23", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1848", "question": "-897820 - -349351 + 292263 - -755912 - 930107 ", "answer": "-430401", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1849", "question": "-4329 - -8865 - -200 ", "answer": "4736", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1850", "question": "-11979 - 20556 + -81960 ", "answer": "-114495", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1851", "question": "-417523 + 368699 * 424069 ", "answer": "156353398708", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1852", "question": "-50 * 11 * -55 ", "answer": "30250", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1853", "question": "96011 + -48974 - 53477 - 61147 ", "answer": "-67587", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1854", "question": "-232 - 701 ", "answer": "-933", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1855", "question": "-369 + -108 - -244 * 554 * -87 ", "answer": "-11760789", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1856", "question": "24808 + -59888 + 25977 - -61423 ", "answer": "52320", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1857", "question": "-302581 + 744227 - -889041 * 75702 + 646988 ", "answer": "67303270416", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1858", "question": "606405 + -471690 ", "answer": "134715", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1859", "question": "-691 * 128 * -280 ", "answer": "24765440", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1860", "question": "-447 * 398 * -129 + 686 ", "answer": "22950560", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1861", "question": "-68 + -25 + -63 - 23 ", "answer": "-179", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1862", "question": "267429 - 669993 * -258869 * 933614 - -664478 ", "answer": "161926402334093945", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1863", "question": "-4869 + -4847 * -6677 + -7769 ", "answer": "32350781", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1864", "question": "72412 - -43248 - -48277 - 42483 ", "answer": "121454", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1865", "question": "262124 * 419197 + 552894 - -443918 ", "answer": "109882591240", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1866", "question": "-82013 * 13005 + -54746 * 46044 * 17678 ", "answer": "-44562440017737", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1867", "question": "-1025 - 34233 - 82492 * -62736 ", "answer": "5175182854", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1868", "question": "-8397 * 4551 - -841 ", "answer": "-38213906", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1869", "question": "-78 * 28 - 78 * 24 ", "answer": "-4056", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1870", "question": "-65 + -38 * 51 * -84 ", "answer": "162727", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1871", "question": "-24178 - 78512 + 26892 ", "answer": "-75798", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1872", "question": "-1160 - -1193 - -3184 * 3611 + -7084 ", "answer": "11490373", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1873", "question": "-249 * 632 - 201 + -949 * 778 ", "answer": "-895891", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1874", "question": "-583 + 320 + -768 * 441 - 800 ", "answer": "-339751", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1875", "question": "52 * -57 ", "answer": "-2964", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1876", "question": "14185 + 21797 * 66508 - -75981 - 13332 ", "answer": "1449751710", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1877", "question": "-7267 - 5751 * -4210 * -5950 ", "answer": "-144059681767", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1878", "question": "476 - 344 ", "answer": "132", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1879", "question": "-95919 * -56036 - 81832 - -24608 + -28597 ", "answer": "5374831263", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1880", "question": "99515 + -565412 - -857212 * 229426 ", "answer": "196666254415", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1881", "question": "467 * 522 + -435 ", "answer": "243339", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1882", "question": "-6164 * 3807 ", "answer": "-23466348", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1883", "question": "603776 + -834741 * 528379 * 209091 ", "answer": "-92221595925697573", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1884", "question": "-32 * -219 + 657 * -344 + 812 ", "answer": "-218188", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1885", "question": "-26147 + -47844 - -83192 * 65501 * -46569 ", "answer": "-253761894486239", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1886", "question": "-640817 - -502638 + -542904 - 290539 - -132877 ", "answer": "-838745", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1887", "question": "-62 * -81 - 98 + -49 - -31 ", "answer": "4906", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1888", "question": "-165 + -695 ", "answer": "-860", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1889", "question": "-60914 * -1553 + 55324 * -18151 * 7718 ", "answer": "-7750212361990", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1890", "question": "39249 + -13324 * -15444 + -15502 * -48732 ", "answer": "961258569", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1891", "question": "-58261 - 212325 * 206221 ", "answer": "-43785932086", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1892", "question": "-990 + -697 ", "answer": "-1687", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1893", "question": "65988 + 86752 * 56887 - 60934 * 82967 ", "answer": "-120384166", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1894", "question": "799798 * 758971 + -607599 * -496993 - -720241 ", "answer": "908996657906", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1895", "question": "-72483 - -17384 * -826 + 938916 ", "answer": "-13492751", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1896", "question": "-43 * 28 + 71 - 70 ", "answer": "-1203", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1897", "question": "771840 + 420733 ", "answer": "1192573", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1898", "question": "-3234 * -5810 + 239 + -401 ", "answer": "18789378", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1899", "question": "-70 * 78 + -38 - 60 + 50 ", "answer": "-5508", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1900", "question": "2627 * 9280 + -8841 - 7010 * -3699 ", "answer": "50299709", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1901", "question": "561 * -737 * -984 ", "answer": "406841688", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1902", "question": "-69865 + -743821 * 133588 ", "answer": "-99365629613", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1903", "question": "-588135 * -90411 + 592979 * -651979 ", "answer": "-333435981956", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1904", "question": "-7870 * 41 * -2474 * -5407 ", "answer": "-4316330131060", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1905", "question": "99628 - 974194 + -742 - -757752 + 740655 ", "answer": "623099", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1906", "question": "885304 + 710315 * -80815 ", "answer": "-57403221421", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1907", "question": "-54219 - -17486 - -585 + -5017 ", "answer": "-41165", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1908", "question": "-3248 + -86049 + -64018 ", "answer": "-153315", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1909", "question": "64780 + -41650 + 40879 ", "answer": "64009", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1910", "question": "-236412 + -979558 - 651568 ", "answer": "-1867538", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1911", "question": "835 + 641 + 259 ", "answer": "1735", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1912", "question": "255180 + -250107 ", "answer": "5073", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1913", "question": "-7948 + 2986 - -3243 + -4860 * 1058 ", "answer": "-5143599", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1914", "question": "62 + 67 * -87 - -30 - -8 ", "answer": "-5729", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1915", "question": "-31 * -20 * -58 * 95 ", "answer": "-3416200", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1916", "question": "66 + 2 + -50 - -85 ", "answer": "103", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1917", "question": "-47 - 39 + -82 - -81 ", "answer": "-87", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1918", "question": "62 + 48 * -25 ", "answer": "-1138", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1919", "question": "-663 - -777 - 537 ", "answer": "-423", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1920", "question": "4768 * 3344 + -2172 - -4363 ", "answer": "15946383", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1921", "question": "-44 + -42 ", "answer": "-86", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1922", "question": "-69268 + -67192 ", "answer": "-136460", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1923", "question": "-28612 - 14214 ", "answer": "-42826", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1924", "question": "-94749 * -31527 + 96198 ", "answer": "2987247921", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1925", "question": "9832 * -8257 ", "answer": "-81182824", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1926", "question": "-55334 - 81605 - 59914 - 79006 - 43557 ", "answer": "-319416", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1927", "question": "53662 + -38479 * -18745 * -37827 ", "answer": "-27284193464423", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1928", "question": "361 - -523 ", "answer": "884", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1929", "question": "457053 - 201459 - -688651 - 159886 + 823670 ", "answer": "1608029", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1930", "question": "23720 + 41263 ", "answer": "64983", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1931", "question": "9325 * 980 * 5405 ", "answer": "49393592500", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1932", "question": "81 - 84 + 4 ", "answer": "1", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1933", "question": "-32877 * -23282 * 67883 + 48687 ", "answer": "51960520649949", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1934", "question": "3133 * -9577 ", "answer": "-30004741", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1935", "question": "-5421 * 583 - 2753 - -8163 - -9275 ", "answer": "-3145758", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1936", "question": "679 * 916 ", "answer": "621964", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1937", "question": "3281 - 8112 + 5975 * 1752 + 6318 ", "answer": "10469687", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1938", "question": "7202 * -741627 ", "answer": "-5341197654", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1939", "question": "-231412 * -599623 + 319116 + -771831 * -68345 ", "answer": "191511066487", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1940", "question": "101401 * 467687 * -680260 * -327054 ", "answer": "10550959015737037377480", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1941", "question": "9329 + 682 ", "answer": "10011", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1942", "question": "57520 * 39199 ", "answer": "2254726480", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1943", "question": "-36537 * -82002 * -6493 + 28463 * 36179 ", "answer": "-19452693468605", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1944", "question": "88 + -45 * -91 ", "answer": "4183", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1945", "question": "-97 - 724 ", "answer": "-821", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1946", "question": "58797 - 81838 - -79184 - 94379 * 5717 ", "answer": "-539508600", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1947", "question": "190705 - 202935 - -590582 + 2405 ", "answer": "580757", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1948", "question": "689586 + 97935 - -570242 ", "answer": "1357763", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1949", "question": "8753 * -8232 * 9824 ", "answer": "-707865333504", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1950", "question": "-212 + 958 ", "answer": "746", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1951", "question": "-262780 * 329494 - 28170 * 496423 + -510648 ", "answer": "-100569179878", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1952", "question": "97358 - 691409 * -488565 - 991682 ", "answer": "337797343761", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1953", "question": "3835 + -7743 ", "answer": "-3908", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1954", "question": "-15751 - -11053 + -98284 - 31829 - 45961 ", "answer": "-180772", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1955", "question": "-283660 - -55997 + -741008 ", "answer": "-968671", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1956", "question": "9116 - 7400 * 4627 - 3860 ", "answer": "-34234544", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1957", "question": "-73 + 47 - -90 * 2 + 100 ", "answer": "254", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1958", "question": "83 - -12 - 76 * 67 * -44 ", "answer": "224143", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1959", "question": "821 + 247 ", "answer": "1068", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1960", "question": "-623 + -658 + 217 * -199 + 882 ", "answer": "-43582", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1961", "question": "20 * 41 * 33 ", "answer": "27060", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1962", "question": "-88964 * 25627 + 4475 - 54637 - 36172 ", "answer": "-2279966762", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1963", "question": "-813 * -460 ", "answer": "373980", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1964", "question": "857 - -14 - -681 - -322 - -851 ", "answer": "2725", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1965", "question": "-81 + 61 + 85 + -87 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1966", "question": "943499 * -379048 * -177163 * -829923 ", "answer": "-52583135595351015515448", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1967", "question": "477 * 608 + 555 * -693 ", "answer": "-94599", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1968", "question": "983 * 134 ", "answer": "131722", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1969", "question": "-5243 * -2128 - -875 * 7704 ", "answer": "17898104", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1970", "question": "84 - -20 + 68 * 44 * 71 ", "answer": "212536", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1971", "question": "-9308 + 3891 * -5143 - -2811 ", "answer": "-20017910", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1972", "question": "777700 + 430450 * -956237 * -194600 ", "answer": "80099737360867700", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1973", "question": "-14998 * -92691 + 28198 ", "answer": "1390207816", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1974", "question": "-2153 * 8550 + -9257 + -1315 ", "answer": "-18418722", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1975", "question": "894783 + -267761 - 165394 - -124371 * -681345 ", "answer": "-84739097367", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1976", "question": "-82 - 708 * -263 ", "answer": "186122", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1977", "question": "-2290 * -7976 + -830 + 2810 ", "answer": "18267020", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1978", "question": "6519 * -4289 * 6828 ", "answer": "-190910818548", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1979", "question": "-86807 - 52904 * 58501 + 19316 ", "answer": "-3095004395", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1980", "question": "-716 * 721 ", "answer": "-516236", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1981", "question": "-1000 - 534 + 973 + -828 ", "answer": "-1389", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1982", "question": "-1929 + -4967 ", "answer": "-6896", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1983", "question": "-92138 * -880971 * 771333 + -243380 ", "answer": "62609798435911954", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1984", "question": "-11894 + -96467 - -82518 + 80908 ", "answer": "55065", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1985", "question": "-39 - -78 * -86 - 44 * 40 ", "answer": "-8507", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1986", "question": "-60691 + 11841 * 88630 - 79938 ", "answer": "1049327201", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1987", "question": "170 - 6923 ", "answer": "-6753", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1988", "question": "-2638 + 8110 ", "answer": "5472", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "1989", "question": "577263 * 723336 * 342562 - -622939 - 55597 ", "answer": "143038513375888158", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1990", "question": "-592 * -451 ", "answer": "266992", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1991", "question": "93 - -62 + 79 * -72 ", "answer": "-5533", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1992", "question": "-588 + -531 ", "answer": "-1119", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1993", "question": "432 + -729 ", "answer": "-297", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1994", "question": "71 - -9 - -18 - 7 ", "answer": "91", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "1995", "question": "421601 - -479383 ", "answer": "900984", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "1996", "question": "-358 * -938 * -939 ", "answer": "-315319956", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1997", "question": "-66503 * -25745 - -29397 ", "answer": "1712149132", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "1998", "question": "-814 - 564 - -312 ", "answer": "-1066", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "1999", "question": "33 - -82 * -47 * 70 ", "answer": "-269747", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2000", "question": "-494 * 816 ", "answer": "-403104", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2001", "question": "-3290 - -4493 ", "answer": "1203", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2002", "question": "6683 - 5976 - 7983 * -1649 * 4114 ", "answer": "54156560945", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2003", "question": "-53 - -18 - -4 ", "answer": "-31", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2004", "question": "-657243 - 479404 * 884258 ", "answer": "-423917479475", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2005", "question": "839634 + -999480 * -735335 ", "answer": "734953465434", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2006", "question": "-2020 * 2514 * -8725 ", "answer": "44307993000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2007", "question": "5855 * 1552 * -6113 * 1931 ", "answer": "-107264320492880", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2008", "question": "-6892 - 577 + -7864 ", "answer": "-15333", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2009", "question": "3395 * -7449 - 3380 ", "answer": "-25292735", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2010", "question": "16 + -14 + 69 ", "answer": "71", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2011", "question": "13064 + 2944 - 80056 + 44448 ", "answer": "-19600", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2012", "question": "7729 * -2823 + 220 + 9971 * -8144 ", "answer": "-103022571", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2013", "question": "-4263 * -3653 ", "answer": "15572739", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2014", "question": "7385 * -3926 + -2040 * -8058 * 3251 ", "answer": "53411984810", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2015", "question": "227981 + 215597 * -525121 ", "answer": "-113214284256", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2016", "question": "-910712 * -4324 * 235175 * -424630 * 801729 ", "answer": "-315279812723711360935608000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2017", "question": "453 + -14 - 446 * -12 * 136 ", "answer": "728311", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2018", "question": "43 - -81 + 64 - 71 - -48 ", "answer": "165", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2019", "question": "-6982 * 2477 ", "answer": "-17294414", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2020", "question": "-34796 - -96867 + 78777 - 61053 * -94727 ", "answer": "5783508379", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2021", "question": "516 * 558 - -95 * 804 * 825 ", "answer": "63301428", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2022", "question": "619 - 179 + -682 - -545 ", "answer": "303", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2023", "question": "94 + 92 * -23 - 26 - 18 ", "answer": "-2066", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2024", "question": "-151445 + -461287 ", "answer": "-612732", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2025", "question": "-72 * -90 ", "answer": "6480", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2026", "question": "-164 + -7 + -722 * 111 ", "answer": "-80313", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2027", "question": "-3796 + -4270 * -734 + 4773 + -8454 ", "answer": "3126703", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2028", "question": "-3172 - -7007 * 9013 - -808 ", "answer": "63151727", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2029", "question": "23 - -28 * -68 - 85 ", "answer": "-1966", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2030", "question": "449 * -118 * -584 ", "answer": "30941488", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2031", "question": "-6588 - -9443 * 492 * 6019 ", "answer": "27964002576", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2032", "question": "-53 + 85 - 99 * -18 * -52 ", "answer": "-92632", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2033", "question": "797510 * -729715 + 227127 ", "answer": "-581954782523", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2034", "question": "8754 * -2324 + -5879 ", "answer": "-20350175", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2035", "question": "709893 - 977613 + -511634 - 537658 * 41923 ", "answer": "-22541015688", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2036", "question": "-6924 * -7454 + -7437 - 82 ", "answer": "51603977", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2037", "question": "481 + -2200 - -4984 * -1832 + 4524 ", "answer": "-9127883", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2038", "question": "-66566 - -610959 ", "answer": "544393", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2039", "question": "-2628 + -4430 + -7528 + 9942 ", "answer": "-4644", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2040", "question": "-500 + 2696 + 3479 * 3153 - -9861 ", "answer": "10981344", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2041", "question": "-339073 * -358071 - -703426 ", "answer": "121412911609", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2042", "question": "196879 - -578423 * -478550 - 506263 ", "answer": "-276804636034", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2043", "question": "114499 + -521445 - 978740 * 328005 * -92356 ", "answer": "29649195714470254", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2044", "question": "56 * -16 ", "answer": "-896", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2045", "question": "-67 + -31 - 5 - 77 + 1 ", "answer": "-179", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2046", "question": "-8178 - -12448 ", "answer": "4270", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2047", "question": "-490206 + 745070 * -486399 - -73398 ", "answer": "-362401719738", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2048", "question": "-890004 + 315810 * 491750 * -434862 ", "answer": "-67533880523075004", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2049", "question": "74514 * 310134 + 507866 - 896027 ", "answer": "23108936715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2050", "question": "-910006 * 664343 * -890475 ", "answer": "538342107446747550", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2051", "question": "-5418 + 42828 - -90007 * -88708 ", "answer": "-7984303546", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2052", "question": "-5055 * -7051 - 995 - -7014 + -7735 ", "answer": "35641089", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2053", "question": "-47608 - 93879 - -24769 + -60455 ", "answer": "-177173", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2054", "question": "-39 * -35 ", "answer": "1365", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2055", "question": "-69826 * 16780 ", "answer": "-1171680280", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2056", "question": "-6027 - -1787 ", "answer": "-4240", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2057", "question": "-23209 + -26108 * 51457 + -55773 ", "answer": "-1343518338", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2058", "question": "548 - 42761 + -53340 ", "answer": "-95553", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2059", "question": "-73584 - 18263 * 77490 - 7369 ", "answer": "-1415280823", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2060", "question": "10336 * -78856 ", "answer": "-815055616", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2061", "question": "73 + -40 - 45 ", "answer": "-12", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2062", "question": "439418 + 80522 - -31104 ", "answer": "551044", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2063", "question": "4895 - 360623 + 796237 ", "answer": "440509", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2064", "question": "-97 + 63 ", "answer": "-34", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2065", "question": "36 * -235 - -569 ", "answer": "-7891", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2066", "question": "870225 - 810775 ", "answer": "59450", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2067", "question": "-900 + 738 - -572 - 919 ", "answer": "-509", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2068", "question": "8534 + 3637 * -6334 ", "answer": "-23028224", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2069", "question": "19 - -14 * 96 ", "answer": "1363", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2070", "question": "-88 * 23 * -29 ", "answer": "58696", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2071", "question": "6554 + -189 - 2624 * 7683 + 7058 ", "answer": "-20146769", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2072", "question": "-286938 - -98530 - -500096 - 395622 - 375343 ", "answer": "-459277", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2073", "question": "8146 * 6423 * -3243 ", "answer": "-169679461194", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2074", "question": "49552 - -8480 * 27681 ", "answer": "234784432", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2075", "question": "-9 + 78 - 81 * -6 ", "answer": "555", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2076", "question": "-501012 + -881142 * -79211 * -537414 - -853410 ", "answer": "-37509422223771870", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2077", "question": "892 * -4635 * 3011 ", "answer": "-12448738620", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2078", "question": "31028 * 341465 - 709391 ", "answer": "10594266629", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2079", "question": "-26 + -74 - -33 - -39 ", "answer": "-28", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2080", "question": "-99 - -76 + 31 - 85 * -33 ", "answer": "2813", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2081", "question": "-479741 * -121156 ", "answer": "58123500596", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2082", "question": "-31 - 93 ", "answer": "-124", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2083", "question": "739 * -938 - -95 ", "answer": "-693087", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2084", "question": "20289 * 61532 - 51990 - 50594 + -63552 ", "answer": "1248256612", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2085", "question": "-8554 - -6096 - 6635 * -5436 ", "answer": "36065402", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2086", "question": "-9419 - 876 - -1462 ", "answer": "-8833", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2087", "question": "78925 - -52896 - 89930 - -70552 + -18859 ", "answer": "93584", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2088", "question": "-630222 + -883830 - -311353 ", "answer": "-1202699", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2089", "question": "786 * 552 ", "answer": "433872", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2090", "question": "-7901 * 8201 ", "answer": "-64796101", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2091", "question": "7820 * -5582 + -2864 + -7053 * -2171 ", "answer": "-28342041", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2092", "question": "539260 + -18499 * 112854 ", "answer": "-2087146886", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2093", "question": "49894 * 71919 * -79501 ", "answer": "-285275551913586", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2094", "question": "45 + 100 * 72 ", "answer": "7245", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2095", "question": "-675383 - 185577 - -691750 + 434412 ", "answer": "265202", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2096", "question": "847896 * -313186 ", "answer": "-265549156656", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2097", "question": "-1166 * -6399 + 435 ", "answer": "7461669", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2098", "question": "383348 * -902429 * 794745 - -462610 ", "answer": "-274937544261842930", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2099", "question": "-81379 * 76011 * 18745 ", "answer": "-115950930922905", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2100", "question": "83173 - -90430 ", "answer": "173603", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2101", "question": "587 - 482 * 188 + -613 - -161 ", "answer": "-90481", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2102", "question": "-65 + -90 - 51 ", "answer": "-206", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2103", "question": "-2762 + -2241 * 4808 * 3598 + 9131 ", "answer": "-38767464975", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2104", "question": "-311938 - 398427 ", "answer": "-710365", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2105", "question": "-629264 + 252577 + 818515 * 286734 ", "answer": "234695703323", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2106", "question": "758 + -48737 * -94820 + -95741 ", "answer": "4621147357", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2107", "question": "-7888 - -2647 - -5336 ", "answer": "95", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2108", "question": "355 * 746 ", "answer": "264830", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2109", "question": "562474 - -159554 + -816541 ", "answer": "-94513", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2110", "question": "230 + 768 ", "answer": "998", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2111", "question": "-1 - 4 + -4 - 48 * 47 ", "answer": "-2265", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2112", "question": "-65726 + -99831 - 44399 ", "answer": "-209956", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2113", "question": "419926 - 622791 * 405108 ", "answer": "-252297196502", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2114", "question": "2042 + -1556 ", "answer": "486", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2115", "question": "-76256 + 3465 - 87113 - -67206 ", "answer": "-92698", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2116", "question": "-130 - -170 ", "answer": "40", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2117", "question": "-664586 + 940686 * -168833 + 735944 ", "answer": "-158818768080", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2118", "question": "-398 + 685 + -830 + -644 + 905 ", "answer": "-282", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2119", "question": "3482 - 2879 + 8551 ", "answer": "9154", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2120", "question": "-22 - 57 - -44 - 42 * -46 ", "answer": "1897", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2121", "question": "700 + -870 + 7702 + -9076 ", "answer": "-1544", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2122", "question": "-848 + 901 ", "answer": "53", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2123", "question": "-4045 - -1445 - 1790 + -9406 * 9263 ", "answer": "-87132168", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2124", "question": "-1406 - -3968 ", "answer": "2562", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2125", "question": "772 - 993 ", "answer": "-221", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2126", "question": "281 - 614 ", "answer": "-333", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2127", "question": "-138474 * 281399 - -581798 - -766466 ", "answer": "-38965096862", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2128", "question": "-4561 - 9633 - 5404 ", "answer": "-19598", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2129", "question": "-562157 - 441981 + 267311 - -74620 ", "answer": "-662207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2130", "question": "-39973 + -16699 + 99928 + -69774 ", "answer": "-26518", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2131", "question": "3589 - -2018 - 7549 - 1969 + 2258 ", "answer": "-1653", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2132", "question": "-40422 + 35021 * 50537 ", "answer": "1769815855", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2133", "question": "76 - 31 + -21 * -89 - 34 ", "answer": "1880", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2134", "question": "74811 * -7793 ", "answer": "-583002123", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2135", "question": "-57385 - 75742 * 64085 * -2273 * -98042 ", "answer": "-1081694832703036005", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2136", "question": "-62178 - -73770 - 16398 + 93449 - 63622 ", "answer": "25021", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2137", "question": "64095 - 93006 * -36730 * -19052 ", "answer": "-65083734895665", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2138", "question": "-5736 - 3880 ", "answer": "-9616", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2139", "question": "78 + -24 ", "answer": "54", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2140", "question": "-742741 + -268608 - 615548 + 507885 - -380605 ", "answer": "-738407", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2141", "question": "647 - 985 ", "answer": "-338", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2142", "question": "-97 + -82 * 0 * -83 ", "answer": "-97", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2143", "question": "-75304 * 66404 - -721594 ", "answer": "-4999765222", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2144", "question": "533909 - 415816 * 739377 ", "answer": "-307444252723", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2145", "question": "984485 + -81517 ", "answer": "902968", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2146", "question": "-605561 + 483318 ", "answer": "-122243", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2147", "question": "-269 - -25 * 432 ", "answer": "10531", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2148", "question": "692 - 6 ", "answer": "686", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2149", "question": "-89 + 60 ", "answer": "-29", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2150", "question": "-21980 + 23323 * 61457 + 47793 ", "answer": "1433387424", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2151", "question": "59 - 39 ", "answer": "20", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2152", "question": "74 * -94 * 3 * -6 + 99 ", "answer": "125307", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2153", "question": "77646 * 63050 - -53264 * 23138 ", "answer": "6128002732", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2154", "question": "449 - -106 * 734 ", "answer": "78253", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2155", "question": "4624 - 46770 ", "answer": "-42146", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2156", "question": "-54 + 6 * -23 - -15 ", "answer": "-177", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2157", "question": "6924 * 48555 * -5340 * -1066 ", "answer": "1913768841160800", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2158", "question": "91054 * -29800 ", "answer": "-2713409200", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2159", "question": "471 * -292 - -593 + 693 + 716 ", "answer": "-135530", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2160", "question": "232 + 68 - 870 ", "answer": "-570", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2161", "question": "27675 - 89251 * -99819 ", "answer": "8908973244", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2162", "question": "-66 + 88 - 99 + -19 ", "answer": "-96", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2163", "question": "-15345 + 15606 - 36418 ", "answer": "-36157", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2164", "question": "-182 - 241 * -433 * 142 + 0 ", "answer": "14817944", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2165", "question": "5784 * 9897 + -1375 - 5990 * -9983 ", "answer": "117041043", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2166", "question": "-83 + -59 + -23 - -40 + -44 ", "answer": "-169", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2167", "question": "223 * 123 + 708 - -221 ", "answer": "28358", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2168", "question": "93 + -13 * 99 - 67 - 49 ", "answer": "-1310", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2169", "question": "-676 + -284 * -168 * 13 * -544 ", "answer": "-337419940", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2170", "question": "76 + 31 + 76 * 59 + 47 ", "answer": "4638", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2171", "question": "9334 - -427 + -6771 + 7563 ", "answer": "10553", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2172", "question": "1089 + 9555 * 3029 ", "answer": "28943184", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2173", "question": "-110 * -816 - -477 + -965 + -653 ", "answer": "88619", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2174", "question": "-67 + -7 * 4 ", "answer": "-95", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2175", "question": "-40 - 88 * 16 - -45 ", "answer": "-1403", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2176", "question": "-36 - -62 ", "answer": "26", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2177", "question": "217 + -63 * 600 ", "answer": "-37583", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2178", "question": "29 - -100 - 45 + 56 + -26 ", "answer": "114", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2179", "question": "-72957 + -47532 ", "answer": "-120489", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2180", "question": "372 + 906 - 3 + 1 ", "answer": "1276", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2181", "question": "-34 * 5401 + -4494 ", "answer": "-188128", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2182", "question": "97 + -61 + -41 - 82 ", "answer": "-87", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2183", "question": "93 * 12 + -7 ", "answer": "1109", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2184", "question": "-7 * -2 + -41 * 55 + 37 ", "answer": "-2204", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2185", "question": "1307 - 95594 - -97470 * 77146 - 8477 ", "answer": "7519317856", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2186", "question": "921 - 78 + -315 ", "answer": "528", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2187", "question": "-10262 * 47554 ", "answer": "-487999148", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2188", "question": "327118 + 988057 * -807811 + -891512 * 776493 ", "answer": "-1490415813525", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2189", "question": "-818 - -173 + 403 + -683 - 63 ", "answer": "-988", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2190", "question": "-532 - 764 ", "answer": "-1296", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2191", "question": "-5191 * 6882 * -7012 ", "answer": "250499927544", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2192", "question": "60133 - -414662 ", "answer": "474795", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2193", "question": "447 * 4377 * -6744 * -8909 + -4358 ", "answer": "117552153683266", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2194", "question": "-532043 - -626753 - 336610 ", "answer": "-241900", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2195", "question": "5 - -17 * 55 * -81 * -39 ", "answer": "2953670", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2196", "question": "77568 * -44195 - -58369 ", "answer": "-3428059391", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2197", "question": "1825 * -186 - -5331 + 7463 * 6334 ", "answer": "46936523", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2198", "question": "-8418 - 1401 * 1469 * -5857 ", "answer": "12054101715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2199", "question": "-149495 * -476178 ", "answer": "71186230110", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2200", "question": "48 * -66 - -67 ", "answer": "-3101", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2201", "question": "8448 - -6320 * 1793 - 1060 ", "answer": "11339148", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2202", "question": "900617 + -130185 - 335033 + 71479 - -848671 ", "answer": "1355549", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2203", "question": "-89 * 39 ", "answer": "-3471", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2204", "question": "151 * -148 * -743 ", "answer": "16604564", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2205", "question": "-99 * -55 * -76 ", "answer": "-413820", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2206", "question": "-535156 + -426524 + -139334 * -480259 + -555563 ", "answer": "66914890263", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2207", "question": "-720196 * 783899 - 379192 * 324438 - -945588 ", "answer": "-687584272712", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2208", "question": "3029 + 3894 + 1231 ", "answer": "8154", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2209", "question": "332 + 339 ", "answer": "671", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2210", "question": "24 - 39 * -63 * 67 ", "answer": "164643", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2211", "question": "53 * -8 ", "answer": "-424", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2212", "question": "-129345 - -887417 * 621085 * -931815 ", "answer": "-513580448242192020", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2213", "question": "505 + 5 ", "answer": "510", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2214", "question": "9887 - -7196 + 1700 + 1373 ", "answer": "20156", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2215", "question": "517816 - 422364 ", "answer": "95452", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2216", "question": "-36341 - -96976 ", "answer": "60635", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2217", "question": "46 + -20 * 67 - -79 * 55 ", "answer": "3051", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2218", "question": "-8721 - 4679 * -8503 * 7056 ", "answer": "280726740351", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2219", "question": "91306 * -59968 + 65764 * 41477 * 67616 ", "answer": "184430243389440", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2220", "question": "8229 * -8217 * -1248 ", "answer": "84386880864", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2221", "question": "-59280 * -57633 ", "answer": "3416484240", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2222", "question": "21 + 58 + -19 ", "answer": "60", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2223", "question": "14801 * -24494 * 92464 ", "answer": "-33521500410016", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2224", "question": "-261990 - -39564 + 224149 * 53394 ", "answer": "11967989280", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2225", "question": "-43 + 13 ", "answer": "-30", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2226", "question": "-26 - -2 - 38 * -43 * 87 ", "answer": "142134", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2227", "question": "4608 + -1453 * 904 ", "answer": "-1308904", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2228", "question": "-800491 - 440897 * 909371 * 378129 - -566762 ", "answer": "-151606642631726252", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2229", "question": "-899 - -911 - -951 ", "answer": "963", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2230", "question": "4078 * 100 - -8631 * -3670 - 2976 ", "answer": "-31270946", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2231", "question": "-275 * 766 ", "answer": "-210650", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2232", "question": "-4459 + -1184 ", "answer": "-5643", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2233", "question": "676091 - -56632 * 596035 - -539161 ", "answer": "33755869372", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2234", "question": "-9629 * -14255 + 93403 ", "answer": "137354798", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2235", "question": "74 + -42 - -80 * 94 - 8 ", "answer": "7544", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2236", "question": "315601 * 472452 ", "answer": "149106323652", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2237", "question": "-14035 - 61399 - 60262 ", "answer": "-135696", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2238", "question": "-96 * 24 ", "answer": "-2304", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2239", "question": "-29 + -75 - -82 + 13 * -68 ", "answer": "-906", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2240", "question": "589 - 876 ", "answer": "-287", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2241", "question": "34860 - -83271 * 63489 - -64323 ", "answer": "5286891702", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2242", "question": "-328 + -1072 - 7026 ", "answer": "-8426", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2243", "question": "-506 * -354 * -51 - 398 * -823 ", "answer": "-8807770", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2244", "question": "-27074 - -74003 - 41432 + -65554 ", "answer": "-60057", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2245", "question": "9076 - -8284 ", "answer": "17360", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2246", "question": "97308 * -63559 * -69923 - 95040 - 92867 ", "answer": "432459712315849", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2247", "question": "-35 + -96 - -55 + 86 - -70 ", "answer": "80", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2248", "question": "93668 + -66517 * -23724 - 46577 + 52220 ", "answer": "1578148619", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2249", "question": "-73746 + 73459 - -18689 - 36886 - 12838 ", "answer": "-31322", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2250", "question": "-9114 * 2115 * -5203 ", "answer": "100293600330", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2251", "question": "-915 - 181 + 435 ", "answer": "-661", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2252", "question": "-1286 + 7391 ", "answer": "6105", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2253", "question": "-147987 + 60422 + 770252 + -307904 ", "answer": "374783", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2254", "question": "29270 - 13903 ", "answer": "15367", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2255", "question": "4 * 33 ", "answer": "132", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2256", "question": "-25770 * -93444 - -62526 ", "answer": "2408114406", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2257", "question": "44477 - 58605 + -84422 + 65008 ", "answer": "-33542", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2258", "question": "-7803 + -44710 ", "answer": "-52513", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2259", "question": "-529 + 373 ", "answer": "-156", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2260", "question": "9124 * -9021 - 9281 ", "answer": "-82316885", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2261", "question": "-96962 * -64410 * -13866 ", "answer": "-86597640675720", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2262", "question": "-4965 * -31151 * 15170 - 28682 ", "answer": "2346263697868", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2263", "question": "-702 - -450 * -239 + -583 ", "answer": "-108835", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2264", "question": "8647 * 6822 + -5 ", "answer": "58989829", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2265", "question": "-378 - -320 * -996 + -14 + -104 ", "answer": "-319216", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2266", "question": "8563 - 6305 - 4353 - 55 ", "answer": "-2150", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2267", "question": "-54273 + 82223 - 61407 ", "answer": "-33457", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2268", "question": "86498 + -52027 + 1993 ", "answer": "36464", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2269", "question": "44 * 6 - -50 + -80 ", "answer": "234", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2270", "question": "95 + 22 * -24 ", "answer": "-433", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2271", "question": "-651337 - 286529 + 695018 + -232744 + -224513 ", "answer": "-700105", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2272", "question": "130834 - 643758 - 614894 * 228479 ", "answer": "-140490879150", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2273", "question": "-9581 + -8279 ", "answer": "-17860", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2274", "question": "709365 + -632816 - 822184 ", "answer": "-745635", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2275", "question": "559163 + -216076 * 433414 ", "answer": "-93649804301", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2276", "question": "-6 * 73 - -72 * 55 + -73 ", "answer": "3449", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2277", "question": "-964256 - 131587 * 153332 ", "answer": "-20177462140", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2278", "question": "188 - -126 + 316 ", "answer": "630", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2279", "question": "27 - 89 ", "answer": "-62", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2280", "question": "-6588 + 5335 + 690 + 5339 - -6005 ", "answer": "10781", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2281", "question": "97346 + 81876 - -65397 ", "answer": "244619", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2282", "question": "433 + -276 * 158 - 985 + -3 ", "answer": "-44163", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2283", "question": "-86529 * -812933 - -97236 ", "answer": "70342376793", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2284", "question": "-8977 * 3471 ", "answer": "-31159167", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2285", "question": "71329 + 95776 ", "answer": "167105", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2286", "question": "83 - 94 ", "answer": "-11", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2287", "question": "26 * 60 * -67 * 68 + -75 ", "answer": "-7107435", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2288", "question": "988386 * -386455 + 131375 * -230603 - 363268 ", "answer": "-412262544023", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2289", "question": "-661 + -425 * -453 - 171 * 83 ", "answer": "177671", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2290", "question": "97 - -29 - 70 - 63 + 50 ", "answer": "43", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2291", "question": "-91716 * -57483 * -88 + 72414 ", "answer": "-463945680450", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2292", "question": "-787 * 913 ", "answer": "-718531", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2293", "question": "347 - -16 ", "answer": "363", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2294", "question": "8579 + -74282 - 52364 ", "answer": "-118067", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2295", "question": "-436808 * 747982 ", "answer": "-326724521456", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2296", "question": "98933 - -43831 - 27270 ", "answer": "115494", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2297", "question": "-19 - -51 + -34 ", "answer": "-2", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2298", "question": "-82 + -34 * -37 ", "answer": "1176", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2299", "question": "6171 + 56176 + -29197 * 41728 * 48324 ", "answer": "-58874695608437", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2300", "question": "-29933 + 59671 ", "answer": "29738", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2301", "question": "-81638 + 59874 - -44371 - -60961 - -11732 ", "answer": "95300", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2302", "question": "968 - -786 * 316 ", "answer": "249344", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2303", "question": "7087 * 8274 - 9073 + 452 ", "answer": "58629217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2304", "question": "-95 + -28 * 32 - -90 ", "answer": "-901", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2305", "question": "1249 - 3297 ", "answer": "-2048", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2306", "question": "-3620 - -71314 ", "answer": "67694", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2307", "question": "25 + 87 - 7 ", "answer": "105", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2308", "question": "-615 + -170 * -195 + -272 * 398 ", "answer": "-75721", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2309", "question": "-3630 - 5503 ", "answer": "-9133", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2310", "question": "-78 + -43 ", "answer": "-121", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2311", "question": "-722 - -584 * -793 * 677 ", "answer": "-313527546", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2312", "question": "322 - -726 - 90 ", "answer": "958", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2313", "question": "-378246 - 353926 * -489707 ", "answer": "173319661436", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2314", "question": "-894 * -413 + 410 ", "answer": "369632", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2315", "question": "404 * 745 ", "answer": "300980", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2316", "question": "6 + -82 ", "answer": "-76", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2317", "question": "-625944 + 888250 ", "answer": "262306", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2318", "question": "940532 + 438970 + -999391 ", "answer": "380111", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2319", "question": "139188 * -858986 + -249271 * 967571 * 268905 ", "answer": "-64856614867751973", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2320", "question": "-17129 + -270124 * 450601 * 599160 * 24580 ", "answer": "-1792586056566336084329", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2321", "question": "85 * -25 + -18 + 31 ", "answer": "-2112", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2322", "question": "-8547 * -1063 - -4719 * -9596 ", "answer": "-36198063", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2323", "question": "151 * 99 + -712 + -537 ", "answer": "13700", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2324", "question": "-6678 + -369 * 2984 - -859 - 938 ", "answer": "-1107853", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2325", "question": "2449 * -1279 ", "answer": "-3132271", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2326", "question": "2631 - 5258 - 6456 ", "answer": "-9083", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2327", "question": "-1451 + 6927 * 298 - 698 ", "answer": "2062097", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2328", "question": "-2237 * -751 * -5623 + -6705 ", "answer": "-9446573606", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2329", "question": "60840 * -71166 + 85828 + -21346 * 67779 ", "answer": "-5776464146", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2330", "question": "980 + -288 ", "answer": "692", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2331", "question": "9711 + -6575 + -2394 ", "answer": "742", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2332", "question": "926145 + -804582 * 563006 + 462658 ", "answer": "-452983104689", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2333", "question": "-20 + -427 - 721 - -379 ", "answer": "-789", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2334", "question": "-54 * -43 - 86 * 55 ", "answer": "-2408", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2335", "question": "-160 * 3876 + 1935 * -3781 ", "answer": "-7936395", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2336", "question": "31 * 91 - 41 ", "answer": "2780", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2337", "question": "-166176 - 813732 * 869381 * -632842 ", "answer": "447699731535366888", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2338", "question": "-698 + 965 - 42 - 996 ", "answer": "-771", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2339", "question": "-72142 - 61399 + -7330 * -44407 - -51492 ", "answer": "325421261", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2340", "question": "57980 * -31142 ", "answer": "-1805613160", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2341", "question": "-12621 - 13386 * 65515 - -70848 - 90295 ", "answer": "-877015858", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2342", "question": "468877 - -66347 - 878078 * -804573 ", "answer": "706478385918", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2343", "question": "602877 + -742343 * 547845 * -987383 ", "answer": "401557706973767682", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2344", "question": "-48032 + 10002 ", "answer": "-38030", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2345", "question": "69 + -61 - -71 ", "answer": "79", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2346", "question": "52145 * 99318 ", "answer": "5178937110", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2347", "question": "-881 * 109 ", "answer": "-96029", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2348", "question": "802 + -665 ", "answer": "137", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2349", "question": "-63 + -72 + 51 ", "answer": "-84", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2350", "question": "317360 * 490994 * -127726 - -946618 + -222109 ", "answer": "-19902502358295331", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2351", "question": "67723 * 81639 + -52750 ", "answer": "5528785247", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2352", "question": "-57 - 39 ", "answer": "-96", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2353", "question": "33 + 83 + 26 + 32 ", "answer": "174", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2354", "question": "765235 - 46034 + -282973 ", "answer": "436228", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2355", "question": "800991 - -306325 * 208179 - 384775 ", "answer": "63770848391", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2356", "question": "9067 - -8746 ", "answer": "17813", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2357", "question": "-1791 - -1905 ", "answer": "114", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2358", "question": "-93324 + -72761 ", "answer": "-166085", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2359", "question": "77351 * -95103 + -43398 - -77500 ", "answer": "-7356278051", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2360", "question": "-542 * 964 * 941 ", "answer": "-491661208", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2361", "question": "-1913 - -171 ", "answer": "-1742", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2362", "question": "15 + 91 ", "answer": "106", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2363", "question": "-9360 * -462 ", "answer": "4324320", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2364", "question": "23 + 48 * -72 + 32 + -58 ", "answer": "-3459", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2365", "question": "-79 - -230 ", "answer": "151", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2366", "question": "-84 + 17 + 81 ", "answer": "14", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2367", "question": "-78960 * 18900 + -60200 ", "answer": "-1492404200", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2368", "question": "-287 + 680 * -640 - 304 ", "answer": "-435791", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2369", "question": "83 * 286 + 354 * -820 - 236 ", "answer": "-266778", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2370", "question": "3538 + -2110 * -6538 ", "answer": "13798718", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2371", "question": "473 + -855 ", "answer": "-382", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2372", "question": "-17 + -68 ", "answer": "-85", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2373", "question": "-436866 - 507354 - 379742 - 152392 * 560632 ", "answer": "-85437155706", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2374", "question": "-56 + -35 + 35 * 50 + 12 ", "answer": "1671", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2375", "question": "8386 + -5927 * -3233 * 5842 * -2638 ", "answer": "-295309199042850", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2376", "question": "958 + 831 - -273 ", "answer": "2062", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2377", "question": "-60864 + -28517 * 33299 ", "answer": "-949648447", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2378", "question": "-8464 + -7205 ", "answer": "-15669", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2379", "question": "87 - 541 ", "answer": "-454", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2380", "question": "-195 + 95 * -607 - 521 - 471 ", "answer": "-58852", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2381", "question": "-1445 - -6084 + -4411 + -7326 ", "answer": "-7098", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2382", "question": "-848 - -576 - 29 + -265 + 39 ", "answer": "-527", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2383", "question": "-15 + -23 - -5 - 57 ", "answer": "-90", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2384", "question": "538573 * 596735 * 567765 ", "answer": "182471358440638575", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2385", "question": "-63 * -3638 - -4691 + -7142 + 561 ", "answer": "227304", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2386", "question": "6383 + 3442 - 6782 - -5192 ", "answer": "8235", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2387", "question": "44850 * -98210 - -74269 ", "answer": "-4404644231", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2388", "question": "83120 * -76350 ", "answer": "-6346212000", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2389", "question": "-999 * -241 + 387 - -933 * -337 ", "answer": "-73275", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2390", "question": "-610831 + -951907 ", "answer": "-1562738", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2391", "question": "-596309 * -106602 - -653518 ", "answer": "63568385536", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2392", "question": "269556 * 40417 ", "answer": "10894644852", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2393", "question": "-6465 * -5892 + -7110 ", "answer": "38084670", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2394", "question": "575472 * -886061 - -214416 ", "answer": "-509903081376", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2395", "question": "-5278 * 2276 + -1259 ", "answer": "-12013987", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2396", "question": "68350 - 371619 ", "answer": "-303269", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2397", "question": "-83004 * -52453 + -53941 + -82613 + 94378 ", "answer": "4353766636", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2398", "question": "-4927 * -5586 - -2927 - -8341 - 6022 ", "answer": "27527468", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2399", "question": "396 * 382 - 939 - 951 - -109 ", "answer": "149491", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2400", "question": "-989 - -257 + 870 - -674 + 951 ", "answer": "1763", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2401", "question": "-17 - -27 * 32 + 32 ", "answer": "879", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2402", "question": "82901 - 63363 - -11056 - 31204 * -6374 ", "answer": "198924890", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2403", "question": "-986 - 801 - 670 * 863 ", "answer": "-579997", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2404", "question": "17 + -81 ", "answer": "-64", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2405", "question": "-588466 + -140728 ", "answer": "-729194", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2406", "question": "-682 + -61 * 790 - 917 + 398 ", "answer": "-49391", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2407", "question": "108 - -660 * 296 * 543 ", "answer": "106080588", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2408", "question": "-13 * 26 * -16 + -73 ", "answer": "5335", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2409", "question": "-42 * 63 * -71 - -92 ", "answer": "187958", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2410", "question": "54 - 30 ", "answer": "24", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2411", "question": "84 * -86 - 79 - -100 + 94 ", "answer": "-7109", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2412", "question": "-12 + -148 ", "answer": "-160", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2413", "question": "308 * -740 + -265 + 371 + -647 ", "answer": "-228461", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2414", "question": "-4085 - -8003 + -2153 - 8209 ", "answer": "-6444", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2415", "question": "5522 + -38644 + -21964 - 22591 - -84176 ", "answer": "6499", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2416", "question": "2858 * 4853 * 758 + -6365 ", "answer": "10513358127", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2417", "question": "176 - 97 * 200 - 135 - -196 ", "answer": "-19163", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2418", "question": "-13236 * -679461 * -316015 + 778949 ", "answer": "-2842032170943991", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2419", "question": "824 * 211 ", "answer": "173864", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2420", "question": "32672 + 31939 + -199 - -22882 + -55045 ", "answer": "32249", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2421", "question": "24334 - 92872 ", "answer": "-68538", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2422", "question": "-18 - -82 - -86 - -62 + -85 ", "answer": "127", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2423", "question": "43345 * 15884 * -13497 - 57243 * 15847 ", "answer": "-9293483383881", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2424", "question": "18435 * 99114 + 64690 ", "answer": "1827231280", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2425", "question": "-2393 + -64975 ", "answer": "-67368", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2426", "question": "702021 - -900190 * 304677 + 409223 * -172525 ", "answer": "203666692576", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2427", "question": "-93 - -75 ", "answer": "-18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2428", "question": "675 + 563 - 805 ", "answer": "433", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2429", "question": "-731 - 7576 + 7066 - 6799 * 8084 ", "answer": "-54964357", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2430", "question": "-18 - -3 + 47 + 78 + -49 ", "answer": "61", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2431", "question": "-910 + -913 ", "answer": "-1823", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2432", "question": "82 - -83 ", "answer": "165", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2433", "question": "325830 - -51705 - 278622 - 222326 ", "answer": "-123413", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2434", "question": "302964 - -618832 * -619778 * 661951 + -783480 ", "answer": "-253883666669927012", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2435", "question": "-4358 * -2161 + -5148 - -4405 + 6433 ", "answer": "9423328", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2436", "question": "-56377 - 45458 * 32364 * -95253 + -49744 ", "answer": "140136471820015", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2437", "question": "429 - -523 ", "answer": "952", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2438", "question": "399 * -272 + 965 - -640 ", "answer": "-106923", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2439", "question": "62 + -80 + -18 * -67 ", "answer": "1188", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2440", "question": "12469 + -11518 - 91130 * 46553 + -71737 ", "answer": "-4242445676", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2441", "question": "27 - -68 ", "answer": "95", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2442", "question": "27 - 216 - -520 * -401 * -733 ", "answer": "152844971", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2443", "question": "633 + -768 * -489 * 99 ", "answer": "37180281", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2444", "question": "59 * -76 + 82 + 60 ", "answer": "-4342", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2445", "question": "-721424 * 609927 - -570530 + -949906 ", "answer": "-440016355424", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2446", "question": "-617865 + -720547 ", "answer": "-1338412", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2447", "question": "9461 * -371 ", "answer": "-3510031", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2448", "question": "958 + 243 - 437 * 568 * 822 ", "answer": "-204032351", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2449", "question": "6000 + -392 * -8414 + -3013 ", "answer": "3301275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2450", "question": "-8109 + -24143 - -85003 - 21940 - -94429 ", "answer": "125240", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2451", "question": "-12 * -45 * 20 + 92 * 46 ", "answer": "15032", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2452", "question": "-47 + -28 * 36 - 36 ", "answer": "-1091", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2453", "question": "-765 * -364 * -604 ", "answer": "-168189840", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2454", "question": "-26559 - 12286 * 22347 + 99650 * -5610 ", "answer": "-833618301", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2455", "question": "96 - 12 - 77 + 35 ", "answer": "42", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2456", "question": "-5840 + 2585 ", "answer": "-3255", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2457", "question": "757855 - 777637 - -394432 ", "answer": "374650", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2458", "question": "293 * -979 ", "answer": "-286847", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2459", "question": "-6042 - 2545 + 7273 * -1899 ", "answer": "-13820014", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2460", "question": "94621 - -18428 ", "answer": "113049", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2461", "question": "-97 + -41 - 21 - 8 * -38 ", "answer": "145", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2462", "question": "-534075 * 886982 * -426637 + -421661 - 81760 ", "answer": "202104308761117629", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2463", "question": "736 + -493 ", "answer": "243", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2464", "question": "186 - -1046 * 4363 ", "answer": "4563884", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2465", "question": "-4892 * 2649 - 8803 + 5644 + -6810 ", "answer": "-12968877", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2466", "question": "69 - 85 - -41 + 48 - -3 ", "answer": "76", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2467", "question": "-3204 + -821 * -2717 - -5154 * -7352 ", "answer": "-35664755", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2468", "question": "-12 - -1 + 2 + 44 - -42 ", "answer": "77", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2469", "question": "740 - 507 ", "answer": "233", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2470", "question": "11890 * -56936 ", "answer": "-676969040", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2471", "question": "-178337 - -734118 + 825448 - 632318 ", "answer": "748911", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2472", "question": "732555 - 804294 ", "answer": "-71739", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2473", "question": "21 - -301 * 11 + -914 * 881 ", "answer": "-801902", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2474", "question": "-889139 * 712226 ", "answer": "-633267913414", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2475", "question": "6505 * -867 ", "answer": "-5639835", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2476", "question": "-5702 - 67935 ", "answer": "-73637", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2477", "question": "-69667 - -64823 - -97583 + -80522 ", "answer": "12217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2478", "question": "12343 * -21162 * -52304 + -82994 * -71418 ", "answer": "13667866277556", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2479", "question": "-97 - -5 + -93 ", "answer": "-185", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2480", "question": "-1666 - -3371 ", "answer": "1705", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2481", "question": "63837 - 85657 + 82891 - 6855 ", "answer": "54216", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2482", "question": "-648045 - -329686 - -788125 * -535600 + 140181 ", "answer": "-422119928178", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2483", "question": "18 + 25 ", "answer": "43", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2484", "question": "568278 - 669887 - 623808 ", "answer": "-725417", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2485", "question": "-523 * 937 - 346 + 538 * 419 ", "answer": "-264975", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2486", "question": "2408 * -6297 + 1102 ", "answer": "-15162074", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2487", "question": "936 * -908 ", "answer": "-849888", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2488", "question": "-42268 * 82658 - -37866 * 46684 ", "answer": "-1726052000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2489", "question": "-998 + 531 * 653 + -621 ", "answer": "345124", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2490", "question": "-7425 + -9711 + -4135 - 7465 ", "answer": "-28736", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2491", "question": "-3587 - -4537 + 9594 + 8905 * -5047 ", "answer": "-44932991", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2492", "question": "59007 - 94223 * -64553 * -82559 ", "answer": "-502154989020314", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2493", "question": "11 * -27 ", "answer": "-297", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2494", "question": "-8496 + -5770 ", "answer": "-14266", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2495", "question": "-925998 - 394003 + 69603 + 930053 ", "answer": "-320345", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2496", "question": "-59199 * -74989 + 18838 - 96958 ", "answer": "4439195691", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2497", "question": "-343 * -587 ", "answer": "201341", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2498", "question": "961 * 717 + 990 - 484 ", "answer": "689543", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2499", "question": "-1488 * 2585 ", "answer": "-3846480", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2500", "question": "599 + -508 + 573 - 654 - -53 ", "answer": "63", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2501", "question": "43 * 1 * 22 ", "answer": "946", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2502", "question": "-260224 * 643378 * -166232 ", "answer": "27830959843579904", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2503", "question": "40 - -75 + 87 + -40 ", "answer": "162", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2504", "question": "-437660 * -948385 - -50240 ", "answer": "415070229340", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2505", "question": "-6086 * 2057 + 5646 - -4143 ", "answer": "-12509113", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2506", "question": "7034 + -1869 ", "answer": "5165", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2507", "question": "86839 * -77415 + 1789 ", "answer": "-6722639396", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2508", "question": "-52042 - -29659 + -7020 + 77902 * -34734 ", "answer": "-2705877471", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2509", "question": "95 * -5 + 74 ", "answer": "-401", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2510", "question": "78 - -29 ", "answer": "107", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2511", "question": "42545 * -2742 - 96244 - 79112 - 22268 ", "answer": "-116856014", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2512", "question": "-87 + -17 + -56 ", "answer": "-160", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2513", "question": "7845 + 8443 + -947 * 9060 ", "answer": "-8563532", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2514", "question": "-2316 * -6253 ", "answer": "14481948", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2515", "question": "-23 - 26 - 33 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2516", "question": "939 + -892 * 380 ", "answer": "-338021", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2517", "question": "-41068 * -45671 - -97527 - -46878 ", "answer": "1875761033", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2518", "question": "67022 + 11600 ", "answer": "78622", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2519", "question": "97592 * 564064 - 352009 + -40269 - -121154 ", "answer": "55047862764", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2520", "question": "9683 + -2382 + 5770 ", "answer": "13071", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2521", "question": "-713 - -377 - 810 + -42 * -294 ", "answer": "11202", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2522", "question": "2612 - 9580 ", "answer": "-6968", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2523", "question": "66 + 84 + 20 + -41 ", "answer": "129", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2524", "question": "379 + -474 * 901 ", "answer": "-426695", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2525", "question": "-51008 + -66950 - -46452 ", "answer": "-71506", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2526", "question": "-93077 - 42874 + 10209 ", "answer": "-125742", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2527", "question": "-294956 + -785985 + -988251 * -804520 ", "answer": "795066613579", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2528", "question": "-8 + -100 ", "answer": "-108", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2529", "question": "-394 - 166 * -105 + 976 * -412 ", "answer": "-385076", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2530", "question": "1538 * 7613 - -1001 - -3080 ", "answer": "11712875", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2531", "question": "89949 - -56572 * 53624 ", "answer": "3033706877", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2532", "question": "-199 * -133 * -822 * 365 * -591 ", "answer": "4693068359910", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2533", "question": "-2930 - 847649 - -269467 - 55145 ", "answer": "-636257", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2534", "question": "-86653 - 4160 + 12089 + 51249 * -83028 ", "answer": "-4255180696", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2535", "question": "-26 + 32 + 33 - 21 + 42 ", "answer": "60", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2536", "question": "-577536 + 201483 + 117497 - 259888 * -884032 ", "answer": "229749049860", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2537", "question": "962755 + 996523 + 351296 + 464084 - 257168 ", "answer": "2517490", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2538", "question": "-8 * 66 + 19 + 63 * -21 ", "answer": "-1832", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2539", "question": "333 - -7600 ", "answer": "7933", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2540", "question": "688 * 361 - 754 * -107 * -608 ", "answer": "-48803856", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2541", "question": "-58 + 34 ", "answer": "-24", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2542", "question": "288567 * 142022 ", "answer": "40982862474", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2543", "question": "-258795 * 280460 * 898510 ", "answer": "-65215334477907000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2544", "question": "195015 - 23195 * 236037 ", "answer": "-5474683200", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2545", "question": "13742 - 44090 ", "answer": "-30348", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2546", "question": "-64738 - -33445 ", "answer": "-31293", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2547", "question": "77989 - -81604 ", "answer": "159593", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2548", "question": "-562 + 128 * -522 - -158 - -215 ", "answer": "-67005", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2549", "question": "11 + -65 + -8 ", "answer": "-62", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2550", "question": "-64576 * -69930 ", "answer": "4515799680", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2551", "question": "-52079 * -10763 + -18002 ", "answer": "560508275", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2552", "question": "-42866 * 14006 - 66375 + -82858 ", "answer": "-600530429", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2553", "question": "7761 * 86912 ", "answer": "674524032", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2554", "question": "7961 * 3535 ", "answer": "28142135", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2555", "question": "140039 - -286366 - -728482 - 692751 ", "answer": "462136", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2556", "question": "2321 - 1578 + -4590 * 6416 * 4854 ", "answer": "-142947581017", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2557", "question": "-7869 + -773171 + -647630 + -591718 ", "answer": "-2020388", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2558", "question": "2 + 0 * -42 ", "answer": "2", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2559", "question": "-47 * -93 + 38 ", "answer": "4409", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2560", "question": "50302 - 24718 * 48494 ", "answer": "-1198624390", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2561", "question": "-30 - -61 * -87 + 1 + -4 ", "answer": "-5340", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2562", "question": "-342 + 820 * -376 - 994 ", "answer": "-309656", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2563", "question": "8646 - -2360 + -57 - 70 ", "answer": "10879", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2564", "question": "88804 - 97885 + -93882 - 81667 * 13815 ", "answer": "-1128332568", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2565", "question": "-34143 - -87297 ", "answer": "53154", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2566", "question": "-46 * -58 * -96 ", "answer": "-256128", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2567", "question": "3998 * 6116 ", "answer": "24451768", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2568", "question": "50 + -35 * -72 * 70 ", "answer": "176450", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2569", "question": "50971 + -54791 ", "answer": "-3820", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2570", "question": "-90887 * 32411 ", "answer": "-2945738557", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2571", "question": "-5679 - -2825 ", "answer": "-2854", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2572", "question": "-698350 * -92189 - 829608 * 358666 ", "answer": "-233171994778", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2573", "question": "99751 * 89816 * -71127 ", "answer": "-637243565884632", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2574", "question": "-6342 - 829637 + -310881 ", "answer": "-1146860", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2575", "question": "-972 * 103 + -368 ", "answer": "-100484", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2576", "question": "6760 + 83041 - 51267 + -2606 ", "answer": "35928", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2577", "question": "765 - -567 - -351 + 884 ", "answer": "2567", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2578", "question": "515 * 6802 + -2421 - -8346 * -204 ", "answer": "1798025", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2579", "question": "-2972 * -4770 + -7573 * -56 ", "answer": "14600528", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2580", "question": "16568 * -82224 ", "answer": "-1362287232", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2581", "question": "-693874 - -421526 * -385030 * 841622 + -174058 ", "answer": "-136595381708743092", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2582", "question": "-90 * 73 * 36 - 99 ", "answer": "-236619", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2583", "question": "27 + -85 + -79 + -69 ", "answer": "-206", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2584", "question": "-280 - -538 * 148 ", "answer": "79344", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2585", "question": "904080 * -166496 ", "answer": "-150525703680", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2586", "question": "382681 - 68853 * -945250 ", "answer": "65083680931", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2587", "question": "-13 * 745 + 704 + -129 ", "answer": "-9110", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2588", "question": "56 - -29 + -22 * -67 ", "answer": "1559", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2589", "question": "-124978 * -388812 * -389629 ", "answer": "-18933221010023544", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2590", "question": "-74740 + -73153 ", "answer": "-147893", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2591", "question": "23 * -62 + 14 ", "answer": "-1412", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2592", "question": "85961 + 7993 ", "answer": "93954", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2593", "question": "-168 + 857 + -78 + -6 + 164 ", "answer": "769", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2594", "question": "704291 - -143991 + 434046 - -984684 ", "answer": "2267012", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2595", "question": "-59 * -57 ", "answer": "3363", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2596", "question": "-79388 * 75895 * 1702 - 4849 ", "answer": "-10254809151369", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2597", "question": "-545623 * -888394 - -916772 ", "answer": "484729116234", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2598", "question": "-776 - 172 + 196 - -610 ", "answer": "-142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2599", "question": "565929 + -866663 ", "answer": "-300734", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2600", "question": "-64499 + 74473 + -90470 + 59881 ", "answer": "-20615", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2601", "question": "-532176 - 315123 * 634878 ", "answer": "-200065192170", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2602", "question": "3796 * 229 - 5196 ", "answer": "864088", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2603", "question": "-66771 + 29943 - -38368 * -45829 - -65980 ", "answer": "-1758337920", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2604", "question": "-644522 * 567587 + -186150 * -378710 + -701509 ", "answer": "-295326143423", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2605", "question": "-91 * 61 ", "answer": "-5551", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2606", "question": "-8306 * 8138 - -9951 + 5831 ", "answer": "-67578446", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2607", "question": "6931 + -4504 * -7794 * 3773 ", "answer": "132448062979", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2608", "question": "97 + -10 + -39 + 55 ", "answer": "103", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2609", "question": "-565373 - 38684 * 643048 - -244347 * -109246 ", "answer": "-51570166567", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2610", "question": "-240 + -5042 + 3845 * -6773 * 1916 ", "answer": "-49896831742", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2611", "question": "-74 + -88 - 61 + -78 ", "answer": "-301", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2612", "question": "-218005 * -56127 ", "answer": "12235966635", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2613", "question": "-5152 * 9067 ", "answer": "-46713184", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2614", "question": "-14811 + -76105 ", "answer": "-90916", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2615", "question": "512 * -745 + 237 + -900 ", "answer": "-382103", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2616", "question": "-70 - 43 + 38 * 10 * -73 ", "answer": "-27853", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2617", "question": "375 + 541 - 149 - 899 * -581 ", "answer": "523086", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2618", "question": "-1600 * -61777 + 42451 ", "answer": "98885651", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2619", "question": "364978 - 910965 - -950693 * 305242 - 652153 ", "answer": "290190234566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2620", "question": "91861 + -58219 - 4037 * -24634 + 81479 ", "answer": "99562579", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2621", "question": "595860 - -26035 - -609486 - -461220 ", "answer": "1692601", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2622", "question": "-5060 + -3368 - 58 + -9189 - 8766 ", "answer": "-26441", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2623", "question": "-32 + -73 + 20 ", "answer": "-85", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2624", "question": "46 + 29 + -45 - 70 ", "answer": "-40", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2625", "question": "66970 * -48084 - -65164 + -7362 + 12261 ", "answer": "-3220115417", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2626", "question": "-448015 * -699588 + -782620 + -8413 - 204219 ", "answer": "313424922568", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2627", "question": "-13 - -892 * -534 + 140 * 891 ", "answer": "-351601", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2628", "question": "969 + -499 ", "answer": "470", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2629", "question": "-499890 - -723933 * -812116 ", "answer": "-587918072118", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2630", "question": "-51 - -55 - 81 ", "answer": "-77", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2631", "question": "-59 + 67 * 0 ", "answer": "-59", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2632", "question": "858 - -7402 ", "answer": "8260", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2633", "question": "45 - -54 - -32 ", "answer": "131", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2634", "question": "-16635 - 77457 * -6634 - 25626 * 9761 ", "answer": "263697717", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2635", "question": "-91 * -29 + -92 * 32 ", "answer": "-305", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2636", "question": "-645052 - 689474 * -897082 ", "answer": "618514069816", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2637", "question": "-8532 * -8983 * -6356 ", "answer": "-487142628336", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2638", "question": "-98747 + -78155 * -7259 - 83237 ", "answer": "567145161", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2639", "question": "935 + 143 ", "answer": "1078", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2640", "question": "-2175 + -2024 * 1693 ", "answer": "-3428807", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2641", "question": "-9666 + 2471 ", "answer": "-7195", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2642", "question": "-969 - -812 + 189 - -988 ", "answer": "1020", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2643", "question": "-441 - -38 - 77 * -261 ", "answer": "19694", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2644", "question": "397 - -9155 * -5574 - -4618 ", "answer": "-51024955", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2645", "question": "83 * 15 * 94 * -25 ", "answer": "-2925750", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2646", "question": "-6260 - -8363 + -6538 * -7361 * -1931 ", "answer": "-92931724855", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2647", "question": "-90436 - -22163 + -57444 * 8866 ", "answer": "-509366777", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2648", "question": "-729526 + -531550 - -342235 - -819749 + -625128 ", "answer": "-724220", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2649", "question": "-36 - 52 - 32 * 15 - -58 ", "answer": "-510", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2650", "question": "-8839 * 7450 - -4220 ", "answer": "-65846330", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2651", "question": "-4718 + -7562 - -5730 - 2792 ", "answer": "-9342", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2652", "question": "-4 - 54 + 68 ", "answer": "10", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2653", "question": "3535 - -9737 * 8817 - 2770 ", "answer": "85851894", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2654", "question": "-951771 + -540007 ", "answer": "-1491778", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2655", "question": "-6762 - 1660 ", "answer": "-8422", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2656", "question": "9 + 73 - 3 ", "answer": "79", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2657", "question": "-4464 + -4040 - -2239 ", "answer": "-6265", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2658", "question": "-763091 * 323662 ", "answer": "-246983559242", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2659", "question": "54 + -86 ", "answer": "-32", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2660", "question": "40391 * 90416 - 95257 * -33277 * 72253 ", "answer": "229036065999473", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2661", "question": "-660665 - -9487 ", "answer": "-651178", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2662", "question": "18 + -61 + 0 * 41 + -95 ", "answer": "-138", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2663", "question": "6640 + 7338 + -573 + 1139 * 6600 ", "answer": "7530805", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2664", "question": "-68 - 61 ", "answer": "-129", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2665", "question": "851 + 775 * 968 * 990 * 724 ", "answer": "537713352851", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2666", "question": "9009 - 5591 * 6700 + 6391 ", "answer": "-37444300", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2667", "question": "303725 - 420387 + 599607 + -900567 - 985684 ", "answer": "-1403306", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2668", "question": "452190 + -509549 + 91054 + 773366 + 591982 ", "answer": "1399043", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2669", "question": "-20674 + -392706 ", "answer": "-413380", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2670", "question": "-418206 + -830615 + 783530 * 333227 - 538154 ", "answer": "261091564335", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2671", "question": "684922 * 512046 * 900207 * 190061 * 274467 ", "answer": "16469318371678654677275311308", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2672", "question": "12 * 87 + 68 + -50 + 15 ", "answer": "1077", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2673", "question": "2408 - 6085 - -5053 + -9432 + -1121 ", "answer": "-9177", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2674", "question": "-21566 * -96700 ", "answer": "2085432200", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2675", "question": "-223 + 681 * -245 - 415 ", "answer": "-167483", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2676", "question": "9496 * 2881 + 2599 ", "answer": "27360575", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2677", "question": "-51808 + 61682 ", "answer": "9874", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2678", "question": "48 * 56 * -91 * 52 ", "answer": "-12719616", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2679", "question": "13251 - -26022 ", "answer": "39273", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2680", "question": "-175170 - 90509 - 657349 + 550264 * 768250 ", "answer": "422739394972", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2681", "question": "-116984 + 693599 + 964977 ", "answer": "1541592", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2682", "question": "-3794 + 3771 ", "answer": "-23", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2683", "question": "-7391 - -3423 * 3235 ", "answer": "11066014", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2684", "question": "4487 + 3572 ", "answer": "8059", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2685", "question": "-5982 + 6065 ", "answer": "83", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2686", "question": "-18414 * 22288 - 23327 - -75211 + -16277 ", "answer": "-410375625", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2687", "question": "56 - 79 ", "answer": "-23", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2688", "question": "-83 + -53 ", "answer": "-136", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2689", "question": "-532 - -876 * 724 ", "answer": "633692", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2690", "question": "100 * -90 - -67 + -10 * 93 ", "answer": "-9863", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2691", "question": "-449 * -848 * 185 + 420 ", "answer": "70439540", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2692", "question": "268480 * -27352 - 635098 + -649440 ", "answer": "-7344749498", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2693", "question": "242 + 48301 + 91745 + -67881 - 79925 ", "answer": "-7518", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2694", "question": "580 * 692 - -416 * 649 * 835 ", "answer": "225838000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2695", "question": "929 * 28 ", "answer": "26012", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2696", "question": "761394 * 128019 * -152926 ", "answer": "-14906140473870036", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2697", "question": "-136 * 556 - -677 - 124 - 408 ", "answer": "-75471", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2698", "question": "-7192 - -6473 * 6185 + -9635 ", "answer": "40018678", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2699", "question": "92 + 36 + -25 + -22 ", "answer": "81", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2700", "question": "4390 + -8234 ", "answer": "-3844", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2701", "question": "5476 * 9510 + 24590 ", "answer": "52101350", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2702", "question": "-312540 + -574712 + 756442 ", "answer": "-130810", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2703", "question": "8663 + -51501 * 60993 + 28365 - 30195 ", "answer": "-3141193660", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2704", "question": "212 * -248 * -848 * -660 ", "answer": "-29425735680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2705", "question": "-433209 + -443281 ", "answer": "-876490", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2706", "question": "573 + -620 + 441 + 996 ", "answer": "1390", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2707", "question": "24 * 79 + -3 * -100 + -34 ", "answer": "2162", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2708", "question": "6351 - 6359 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2709", "question": "62 * 80 + -12 * -66 + 65 ", "answer": "5817", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2710", "question": "-570 + 793 * -362 * 911 * -746 ", "answer": "195091775426", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2711", "question": "-6009 * 2988 - -2834 + -1026 ", "answer": "-17953084", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2712", "question": "-966523 + 203606 * -951623 + 138261 + -816138 ", "answer": "-193757796938", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2713", "question": "6922 * -4795 + -5818 + -8066 ", "answer": "-33204874", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2714", "question": "738 * 143 + 720 + 860 * -939 ", "answer": "-701286", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2715", "question": "995 - -158 - -737 - -192 ", "answer": "2082", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2716", "question": "-292197 + 856447 - -701221 ", "answer": "1265471", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2717", "question": "-566 - 197 + -105 ", "answer": "-868", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2718", "question": "880427 * 476228 * 160004 * -2173 ", "answer": "-145780301835729562352", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2719", "question": "41866 + -86737 - 92177 + 16995 - 19992 ", "answer": "-140045", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2720", "question": "28678 - 9514 * -49152 * -7619 + -29124 ", "answer": "-3562889183678", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2721", "question": "-21979 - -63037 - -7688 + -96636 - 48670 ", "answer": "-96560", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2722", "question": "-3700 + 8856 + 7704 ", "answer": "12860", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2723", "question": "634823 - -771439 ", "answer": "1406262", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2724", "question": "-3781 + -1152 ", "answer": "-4933", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2725", "question": "17 - 34 + -72 * -96 ", "answer": "6895", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2726", "question": "-808 - 856 + 628 - 746 ", "answer": "-1782", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2727", "question": "897 + 283 + 711 ", "answer": "1891", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2728", "question": "9932 - -8290 * 1406 - -5691 + 4168 ", "answer": "11675531", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2729", "question": "-58595 + -48742 + 5902 + -97836 * 6385 ", "answer": "-624784295", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2730", "question": "-8565 + 5307 * 8707 - -1216 ", "answer": "46200700", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2731", "question": "3726 * -32377 + 76826 ", "answer": "-120559876", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2732", "question": "650489 + -237936 * -373204 + 373956 * -2916 ", "answer": "87708861737", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2733", "question": "641 - 11 + -299 - 770 ", "answer": "-439", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2734", "question": "-11419 - -72212 ", "answer": "60793", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2735", "question": "93201 * -83434 ", "answer": "-7776132234", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2736", "question": "80 - -46 - -29 - -68 ", "answer": "223", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2737", "question": "860 + 905 * 368 ", "answer": "333900", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2738", "question": "70 + -92 - -86 ", "answer": "64", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2739", "question": "-82784 * -9267 + 86093 ", "answer": "767245421", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2740", "question": "-9764 - 7130 * -5823 - -2462 - -8643 ", "answer": "41519331", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2741", "question": "-3591 * 8275 ", "answer": "-29715525", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2742", "question": "-12 - -14 ", "answer": "2", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2743", "question": "-3648 * -9277 - -5996 ", "answer": "33848492", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2744", "question": "-19 * 67 ", "answer": "-1273", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2745", "question": "-57 - -25 * -59 - -61 - 37 ", "answer": "-1508", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2746", "question": "-92775 + -146512 ", "answer": "-239287", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2747", "question": "170913 - 775898 - 314223 ", "answer": "-919208", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2748", "question": "804 + -680 * 865 ", "answer": "-587396", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2749", "question": "70 + 749 * -150 ", "answer": "-112280", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2750", "question": "-93433 * -63149 ", "answer": "5900200517", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2751", "question": "380 - -496 - -899 ", "answer": "1775", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2752", "question": "87710 * 95059 ", "answer": "8337624890", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2753", "question": "-166 - -770 * 604 ", "answer": "464914", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2754", "question": "-992 + 172 + 540 ", "answer": "-280", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2755", "question": "-9833 * -53586 + 66981 - 9949 ", "answer": "526968170", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2756", "question": "10531 - 40649 - 18918 + -98144 ", "answer": "-147180", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2757", "question": "0 * 66 - -32 - -99 ", "answer": "131", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2758", "question": "43086 + -26130 + 50374 * 40268 * 22744 ", "answer": "46135299533564", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2759", "question": "283 * -655 - 163 ", "answer": "-185528", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2760", "question": "-399 - 522 - 571 * 947 ", "answer": "-541658", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2761", "question": "-508402 + -672263 * 648301 ", "answer": "-435829283565", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2762", "question": "-4336 - -768 + 8221 ", "answer": "4653", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2763", "question": "-675 - -309 ", "answer": "-366", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2764", "question": "149 * -545 * 381 + -60 * 454 ", "answer": "-30966345", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2765", "question": "20 + 73 + 51 ", "answer": "144", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2766", "question": "-826 * -545 - -88 * -847 * -679 ", "answer": "51060114", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2767", "question": "-460585 - 735884 ", "answer": "-1196469", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2768", "question": "-114 + -455 + -644 + -349 - -758 ", "answer": "-804", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2769", "question": "-59180 + -49927 - -73232 + 51511 * -87332 ", "answer": "-4498594527", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2770", "question": "6082 * -3316 - -8419 * -7678 ", "answer": "-84808994", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2771", "question": "-20 - -68 + 93 * 53 ", "answer": "4977", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2772", "question": "79944 - -48559 * 91517 - 78319 ", "answer": "4443975628", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2773", "question": "138 - 316 - 900 - -462 - -608 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2774", "question": "30934 * 78354 * -32732 * 15726 ", "answer": "-1247636487345286752", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2775", "question": "36 + 31 + -34 ", "answer": "33", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2776", "question": "791367 - -505840 ", "answer": "1297207", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2777", "question": "-663675 * -514170 - 61213 ", "answer": "341241713537", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2778", "question": "-784538 + 229019 - 498674 * -265487 ", "answer": "132390908719", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2779", "question": "234 * -563 ", "answer": "-131742", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2780", "question": "-56 * -16 + 21 ", "answer": "917", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2781", "question": "4117 + 6420 - 8946 * 947 ", "answer": "-8461325", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2782", "question": "-7406 - 2842 + -4273 + -2162 ", "answer": "-16683", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2783", "question": "497807 - -646943 - -381507 ", "answer": "1526257", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2784", "question": "699 - -329 + -724 - -620 ", "answer": "924", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2785", "question": "612834 * 143417 - -763315 * 987875 - -557662 ", "answer": "841951177065", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2786", "question": "21613 * 66118 + 10530 ", "answer": "1429018864", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2787", "question": "-96 + -98 + 24 ", "answer": "-170", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2788", "question": "-806779 - -369248 ", "answer": "-437531", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2789", "question": "-717348 + 683605 ", "answer": "-33743", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2790", "question": "-62 - 53 + 66 + 85 - 53 ", "answer": "-17", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2791", "question": "-763831 - 324696 + -346235 * -202175 ", "answer": "69998972598", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2792", "question": "70966 - -21950 * 38798 - -43976 * -18790 ", "answer": "25378026", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2793", "question": "6783 + -5149 ", "answer": "1634", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2794", "question": "-464 * -252 ", "answer": "116928", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2795", "question": "59222 - 94894 * -1601 + 31557 ", "answer": "152016073", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2796", "question": "-47159 - 82366 + -50194 ", "answer": "-179719", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2797", "question": "6285 - 5397 * -541 ", "answer": "2926062", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2798", "question": "-476 + 905 * -887 ", "answer": "-803211", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2799", "question": "-8344 * 2733 ", "answer": "-22804152", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2800", "question": "-934 - -78 * -390 * 534 - 808 ", "answer": "-16246022", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2801", "question": "34467 - -28945 * 68507 ", "answer": "1982969582", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2802", "question": "-59261 - 40925 - -70040 * -41825 + 91298 ", "answer": "-2929431888", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2803", "question": "-45231 - -28219 ", "answer": "-17012", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2804", "question": "0 * 66 ", "answer": "0", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2805", "question": "9650 * -8195 - 9426 + 1383 ", "answer": "-79089793", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2806", "question": "-47 - -9 ", "answer": "-38", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2807", "question": "-662160 + -607805 ", "answer": "-1269965", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2808", "question": "-42386 + -35763 ", "answer": "-78149", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2809", "question": "-6601 * -1416 - -2683 + 4315 ", "answer": "9354014", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2810", "question": "9242 + -3481 * -1845 * 1278 ", "answer": "8207893952", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2811", "question": "-55 * -55 * 6 * 59 ", "answer": "1070850", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2812", "question": "13736 - -93446 ", "answer": "107182", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2813", "question": "-95 * 14 * 5 * 91 ", "answer": "-605150", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2814", "question": "-435 * -163 ", "answer": "70905", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2815", "question": "-62 + 823 - 466 - -955 * 910 ", "answer": "869345", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2816", "question": "-83434 - 23148 - 81977 ", "answer": "-188559", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2817", "question": "12264 + -74482 ", "answer": "-62218", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2818", "question": "482855 + 312356 * 522961 + 439469 + 555866 ", "answer": "163351484306", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2819", "question": "-591 * 8850 + 6163 ", "answer": "-5224187", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2820", "question": "-9987 * 76745 - 98288 * 85258 + -83546 ", "answer": "-9146374165", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2821", "question": "-610 + -5379 ", "answer": "-5989", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2822", "question": "64685 + -21591 ", "answer": "43094", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2823", "question": "426 * 897 + -846 - -764 - 69 ", "answer": "381971", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2824", "question": "387 * -319 ", "answer": "-123453", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2825", "question": "-345 * -802 * 181 - 681 ", "answer": "50080209", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2826", "question": "-904205 + -210103 - -348560 ", "answer": "-765748", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2827", "question": "-3599 + -2899 + -3990 ", "answer": "-10488", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2828", "question": "-476118 - 853078 * 235135 ", "answer": "-200588971648", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2829", "question": "-133 - -374 * -356 + 693 ", "answer": "-132584", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2830", "question": "3166 + 3683 + -3217 * 727 ", "answer": "-2331910", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2831", "question": "3632 + 3955 * -546 * -2909 ", "answer": "6281785502", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2832", "question": "2468 - 14921 - 57735 ", "answer": "-70188", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2833", "question": "-451 - -391 + 924 ", "answer": "864", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2834", "question": "311196 + 745973 * -402124 - 719406 - -28607 ", "answer": "-299974026255", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2835", "question": "3516 - 5708 ", "answer": "-2192", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2836", "question": "-47 - -7 - 95 + 34 * -28 ", "answer": "-1087", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2837", "question": "90 + -570 * 625 - -22 ", "answer": "-356138", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2838", "question": "60 - 86 + -71 * 10 ", "answer": "-736", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2839", "question": "303348 + 586361 ", "answer": "889709", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2840", "question": "772259 * 757776 ", "answer": "585199335984", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2841", "question": "-535 + 614 * -720 + 826 - -195 ", "answer": "-441594", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2842", "question": "-14 + 800 ", "answer": "786", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2843", "question": "353 - -884 + -303 + -479 * 473 ", "answer": "-225633", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2844", "question": "-11 * -11 ", "answer": "121", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2845", "question": "-730 * 1675 ", "answer": "-1222750", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2846", "question": "90 * -89 - -82 ", "answer": "-7928", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2847", "question": "-554285 + 888801 ", "answer": "334516", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2848", "question": "805 - -6 * 217 + 334 ", "answer": "2441", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2849", "question": "-62372 + -73206 ", "answer": "-135578", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2850", "question": "-28 - -31 * 69 ", "answer": "2111", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2851", "question": "42940 - 9047 + 22608 ", "answer": "56501", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2852", "question": "-53 * 81 - -65 + 59 * -26 ", "answer": "-5762", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2853", "question": "-690 * -898 ", "answer": "619620", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2854", "question": "-31924 - 9937 - 65962 ", "answer": "-107823", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2855", "question": "70 * 36 * -96 + 5 - -13 ", "answer": "-241902", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2856", "question": "70558 - 37055 + -78481 * 6692 ", "answer": "-525161349", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2857", "question": "4931 - 1751 ", "answer": "3180", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2858", "question": "812207 * 191685 + -518076 * 574635 ", "answer": "-142016703465", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2859", "question": "2 - 35 - -24 * -66 ", "answer": "-1617", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2860", "question": "112054 * 978148 * 699322 ", "answer": "76649464735917424", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2861", "question": "-670294 - 288853 * 689300 ", "answer": "-199107043194", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2862", "question": "81430 * -79009 ", "answer": "-6433702870", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2863", "question": "-3535 * -8838 ", "answer": "31242330", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2864", "question": "28318 - -11450 + -10263 ", "answer": "29505", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2865", "question": "42 * -72 ", "answer": "-3024", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2866", "question": "12 * -98 - -18 ", "answer": "-1158", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2867", "question": "704 + -654 - 653 ", "answer": "-603", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2868", "question": "141 * -278 - 5913 ", "answer": "-45111", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2869", "question": "492 + 614 + 558 ", "answer": "1664", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2870", "question": "1003 - -6809 ", "answer": "7812", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2871", "question": "-98 + 13 - 10 - -27 - -25 ", "answer": "-43", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2872", "question": "541139 * -72540 - -6105 ", "answer": "-39254216955", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2873", "question": "5251 + 34438 - -43696 + 93514 + -45620 ", "answer": "131279", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2874", "question": "574 + -460 ", "answer": "114", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2875", "question": "-350091 - -27942 + 916201 * 153768 ", "answer": "140882073219", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2876", "question": "271 * 911 + 838 - 945 ", "answer": "246774", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2877", "question": "-626138 * 855934 * -203446 ", "answer": "109033385017165832", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2878", "question": "153778 * 2407 + 729199 * 284401 ", "answer": "207755068445", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2879", "question": "-3276 * -4634 + 8014 ", "answer": "15188998", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2880", "question": "999001 * -311348 - -51483 + -31832 ", "answer": "-311036943697", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2881", "question": "314 - -6364 * 5380 - -6281 ", "answer": "34244915", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2882", "question": "10 * 50 * 0 ", "answer": "0", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2883", "question": "1008 * -3591 * -2946 ", "answer": "10663718688", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2884", "question": "-12 - 60 - -97 - -26 ", "answer": "51", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2885", "question": "-6754 * -9560 ", "answer": "64568240", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2886", "question": "69 + 39 * -32 ", "answer": "-1179", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2887", "question": "3866 * -2542 * 4951 - -1960 ", "answer": "-48655316812", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2888", "question": "-11521 * -98506 ", "answer": "1134887626", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2889", "question": "-93351 - 6107 ", "answer": "-99458", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2890", "question": "660 * -241 * -283 ", "answer": "45013980", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2891", "question": "68 + -44 ", "answer": "24", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2892", "question": "7173 + -9468 * 3301 * 7341 * 9490 ", "answer": "-2177334780928947", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2893", "question": "-80601 * 30382 * 7836 - 47797 + -74487 ", "answer": "-19188950366836", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2894", "question": "2840 + -6421 - -8921 ", "answer": "5340", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2895", "question": "616 - -796 ", "answer": "1412", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2896", "question": "-4918 * 4448 * 8042 ", "answer": "-175920873088", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2897", "question": "-4147 * -1910 + 4314 + 7110 * 463 ", "answer": "11217014", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2898", "question": "-16 + 65 - -61 - -12 ", "answer": "122", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2899", "question": "9374 - -4569 + -9368 * 7674 - 8881 ", "answer": "-71884970", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2900", "question": "5766 + -2209 * -7224 ", "answer": "15963582", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2901", "question": "939847 + 881427 + -293733 + -957050 * -624748 ", "answer": "597916600941", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2902", "question": "605 + -69 * 984 ", "answer": "-67291", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2903", "question": "-517 + -725 * -980 * 563 - 529 ", "answer": "400010454", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2904", "question": "100 - 50 * 16 ", "answer": "-700", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2905", "question": "-35 * 49 * -34 - 50 - -48 ", "answer": "58308", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2906", "question": "7872 - 4711 - 1437 + -6940 * 249 ", "answer": "-1726336", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2907", "question": "262 + -858 - -292 * 190 ", "answer": "54884", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2908", "question": "54 - 62 - 116 * -105 ", "answer": "12172", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2909", "question": "-38672 - 25174 + 89781 + 36274 ", "answer": "62209", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2910", "question": "190 - 773 - 181 - -448 * -851 ", "answer": "-382012", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2911", "question": "-576423 - 424947 + 694402 - 842964 ", "answer": "-1149932", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2912", "question": "369180 - -175584 + 963511 - 283807 * -514164 ", "answer": "145924850623", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2913", "question": "-23 + -617 - -794 - -775 ", "answer": "929", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2914", "question": "971657 - -804853 - 302355 - -137308 + 93845 ", "answer": "1705308", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2915", "question": "-208875 * -815778 - 363060 + 39791 - 144731 ", "answer": "170395161750", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2916", "question": "959 + -878 ", "answer": "81", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2917", "question": "-3078 + 1809 + 7675 ", "answer": "6406", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2918", "question": "6455 - 4793 * 2563 ", "answer": "-12278004", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2919", "question": "-909503 - -243437 - -499457 ", "answer": "-166609", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2920", "question": "89773 + 250472 + -990683 + 640546 - -99802 ", "answer": "89910", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2921", "question": "-68940 + 25945 - 63103 - 95373 * 39423 ", "answer": "-3759995877", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2922", "question": "3207 - 6948 * 5034 + 1730 ", "answer": "-34971295", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2923", "question": "-846 * 708 - -315 + 746 * -179 ", "answer": "-732187", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2924", "question": "8657 + -6322 ", "answer": "2335", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2925", "question": "39615 - -51746 + 69470 * -32284 + 68856 ", "answer": "-2242609263", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2926", "question": "-4074 + -3082 + 5692 ", "answer": "-1464", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2927", "question": "-21 * -7 * 62 ", "answer": "9114", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2928", "question": "52 * -68 * -348 + 166 * -891 ", "answer": "1082622", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2929", "question": "37480 + 20036 * 35930 - 15410 + 72848 ", "answer": "719988398", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2930", "question": "-64 - -58 - 64 ", "answer": "-70", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2931", "question": "5363 + -1915 + 5518 * 7240 ", "answer": "39953768", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2932", "question": "-35 * 31 ", "answer": "-1085", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2933", "question": "-69 * 1 + -61 * -73 - 34 ", "answer": "4350", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2934", "question": "-641 + -493 * 826 - 53 + -677 ", "answer": "-408589", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2935", "question": "891442 * -757295 + -54135 * 356755 ", "answer": "-694397501315", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2936", "question": "-84 + 14 - 4 * 84 * -23 ", "answer": "7658", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2937", "question": "-8438 + 2166 ", "answer": "-6272", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2938", "question": "-129368 - -600927 - 465325 - 252705 ", "answer": "-246471", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2939", "question": "-48 * 10 * 86 ", "answer": "-41280", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2940", "question": "-445272 * -259463 ", "answer": "115531608936", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2941", "question": "-27 + 674 - 145 - 856 - -787 ", "answer": "433", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2942", "question": "-94 + 37 - 48 - 68 ", "answer": "-173", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2943", "question": "-379 - -153 ", "answer": "-226", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2944", "question": "-77 - -9 - -70 + -88 + 26 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2945", "question": "-378749 - -970653 ", "answer": "591904", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2946", "question": "37413 * 34674 ", "answer": "1297258362", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2947", "question": "37525 - 27139 + -42356 - -91362 * -9446 ", "answer": "-863037422", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2948", "question": "-85901 - -47906 ", "answer": "-37995", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2949", "question": "-1747 * 17213 - 77646 + 80804 + -91921 ", "answer": "-30159874", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2950", "question": "50523 + -11629 ", "answer": "38894", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2951", "question": "290 * -482 ", "answer": "-139780", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2952", "question": "-76211 * 94508 ", "answer": "-7202549188", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2953", "question": "4970 * 5480 + -73669 - -94788 - 60874 ", "answer": "27195845", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2954", "question": "-89464 - -43770 + -56432 - 21299 - 13753 ", "answer": "-137178", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2955", "question": "-755749 * 433113 + -823849 - 375178 - -456525 ", "answer": "-327325459139", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2956", "question": "-7639 + -9138 - -3943 - 2795 ", "answer": "-15629", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2957", "question": "774 - -240 - -536 ", "answer": "1550", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2958", "question": "-468048 + 571931 * 262487 ", "answer": "150123984349", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2959", "question": "7719 * 8764 * -9021 + 2567 ", "answer": "-610264477069", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2960", "question": "-84205 + -11474 + 84881 + 63429 - 41073 ", "answer": "11558", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2961", "question": "-44990 * 9109 * 96844 ", "answer": "-39688018300040", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2962", "question": "45687 - 16808 ", "answer": "28879", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2963", "question": "4 + -22 * -39 ", "answer": "862", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2964", "question": "91030 + 84068 - -37613 - -77840 + -11449 ", "answer": "279102", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2965", "question": "30356 * -33874 + 24717 - 80136 ", "answer": "-1028334563", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2966", "question": "10 * 27 - 88 + -78 ", "answer": "104", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2967", "question": "20 + -4 + 44 - 86 - 56 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2968", "question": "-92258 + -5760 - 5416 * -96897 ", "answer": "524696134", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2969", "question": "-8175 + -7747 ", "answer": "-15922", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2970", "question": "524 - -1424 * -9606 ", "answer": "-13678420", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2971", "question": "-3503 + -3254 - -507 ", "answer": "-6250", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2972", "question": "487 + 353 - 731 - 675 - -596 ", "answer": "30", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2973", "question": "8095 - -3769 + 409 + -9521 - 8127 ", "answer": "-5375", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2974", "question": "-2167 * -4201 - 2982 - 3791 ", "answer": "9096794", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2975", "question": "-926 + 280 - -704 - -917 + 154 ", "answer": "1129", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2976", "question": "56614 - -46886 + -12412 + -33705 ", "answer": "57383", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2977", "question": "-7947 * -6791 - -4337 - 5375 ", "answer": "53967039", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2978", "question": "2307 * 3962 - 9366 * 5437 + -8392 ", "answer": "-41791000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2979", "question": "-981 + 172 + -795 + -618 * -980 ", "answer": "604036", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2980", "question": "633559 - -158073 - 96500 + -108529 ", "answer": "586603", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2981", "question": "4492 * -7865 - 3298 + -1301 + -5950 ", "answer": "-35340129", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2982", "question": "-76 * -74 * 56 ", "answer": "314944", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2983", "question": "30 - 30 + 36 - -2 ", "answer": "38", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2984", "question": "-9783 + -5543 * -3815 * -7778 ", "answer": "-164477836793", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2985", "question": "-15 + -41 ", "answer": "-56", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2986", "question": "-86 - -72 * 17 ", "answer": "1138", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2987", "question": "-96415 - -52449 ", "answer": "-43966", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2988", "question": "361567 + 945384 ", "answer": "1306951", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2989", "question": "13465 * -411564 * 988052 * 614134 ", "answer": "-3362688824092553323680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2990", "question": "-115141 + -312013 ", "answer": "-427154", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2991", "question": "2252 * -926 - -1884 - 2010 ", "answer": "-2085478", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "2992", "question": "116 * 217 + 295 + -78 - 337 ", "answer": "25052", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2993", "question": "-49 + -35 * -11 ", "answer": "336", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "2994", "question": "30246 - 30970 ", "answer": "-724", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2995", "question": "57904 + -79341 ", "answer": "-21437", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2996", "question": "882 - -101 - 111 * 635 ", "answer": "-69502", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "2997", "question": "155892 - -438523 ", "answer": "594415", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "2998", "question": "-32481 * -27467 * 76357 ", "answer": "68122327210839", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "2999", "question": "-844042 * -135265 ", "answer": "114169341130", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3000", "question": "673 + -6 + -389 * 800 + -305 ", "answer": "-310838", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3001", "question": "470 * 520 * -303 - -831 + -729 ", "answer": "-74053098", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3002", "question": "7611 + -8383 ", "answer": "-772", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3003", "question": "95 - -15 ", "answer": "110", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3004", "question": "-692480 - 790072 * 833347 ", "answer": "-658404823464", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3005", "question": "4954 + 767 - 2738 * -3931 ", "answer": "10768799", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3006", "question": "19222 + 46087 * -54212 + -558 + -94048 ", "answer": "-2498543828", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3007", "question": "303 * 876 ", "answer": "265428", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3008", "question": "-38742 + 900943 * 800687 * 420104 ", "answer": "303051828921356722", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3009", "question": "-94 - 7 ", "answer": "-101", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3010", "question": "8217 + -6663 - 9416 + 6555 ", "answer": "-1307", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3011", "question": "-10 - -80 * 12 + 39 - 93 ", "answer": "896", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3012", "question": "94 * 57 * -15 ", "answer": "-80370", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3013", "question": "845332 * 692972 + -954573 + 264994 ", "answer": "585790717125", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3014", "question": "-37 + -4 * -66 * 85 * 24 ", "answer": "538523", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3015", "question": "809917 * 538476 ", "answer": "436120866492", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3016", "question": "-56 - -93 + 48 + -33 * -74 ", "answer": "2527", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3017", "question": "-57 * 100 + -86 ", "answer": "-5786", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3018", "question": "125 * 279 + 725 ", "answer": "35600", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3019", "question": "997 * 60 + -634 * -112 ", "answer": "130828", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3020", "question": "4425 * -6380 ", "answer": "-28231500", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3021", "question": "7 * 27 + 6 - 57 * 78 ", "answer": "-4251", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3022", "question": "675 * -8813 + -9401 * 217 ", "answer": "-7988792", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3023", "question": "-776 * -214 * 86 + -356 ", "answer": "14281148", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3024", "question": "-901 + -915 * 149 * 573 ", "answer": "-78120856", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3025", "question": "3383 - -5186 * -8435 * 814 ", "answer": "-35607539357", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3026", "question": "-107 * -607 + -825 * -541 - -886 ", "answer": "512160", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3027", "question": "55 * 1 * -6 + -62 ", "answer": "-392", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3028", "question": "55 + 54 - 19 ", "answer": "90", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3029", "question": "-79499 * 69631 + 70035 ", "answer": "-5535524834", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3030", "question": "4994 * 4493 * -8260 * 8843 ", "answer": "-1638945940653560", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3031", "question": "174091 * -791302 ", "answer": "-137758556482", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3032", "question": "-8251 - -6953 ", "answer": "-1298", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3033", "question": "1726 - 806 + -1726 + -8077 * -5026 ", "answer": "40594196", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3034", "question": "-76788 + 94402 + 54717 + -20501 * 76961 ", "answer": "-1577705130", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3035", "question": "279675 + -356771 + 718095 + -522529 ", "answer": "118470", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3036", "question": "265884 - 835656 * 861080 ", "answer": "-719566402596", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3037", "question": "166114 + -209850 + 964357 * -76230 ", "answer": "-73512977846", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3038", "question": "-971213 + 467744 * 466844 ", "answer": "218362508723", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3039", "question": "291678 - 877758 - 266506 + 255817 ", "answer": "-596769", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3040", "question": "1891 - -6235 * 2560 + -2624 - -570 ", "answer": "15961437", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3041", "question": "-3522 + 5324 - -5751 * 3420 ", "answer": "19670222", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3042", "question": "292 + 642 - 216 ", "answer": "718", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3043", "question": "1912 + -6979 - 9111 * 6505 - 449 ", "answer": "-59272571", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3044", "question": "-338 - -255 + 695 + 632 - -977 ", "answer": "2221", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3045", "question": "-44 * -909 - -135 * -988 ", "answer": "-93384", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3046", "question": "92811 * -85448 - 1414 ", "answer": "-7930515742", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3047", "question": "-61 + -72 ", "answer": "-133", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3048", "question": "48 * 15 - 85 ", "answer": "635", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3049", "question": "-863 * -781 ", "answer": "674003", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3050", "question": "45146 - -41134 ", "answer": "86280", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3051", "question": "-56 * 6 ", "answer": "-336", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3052", "question": "31640 + 29509 ", "answer": "61149", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3053", "question": "-132 + -6135 ", "answer": "-6267", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3054", "question": "215 + 266 + -622 - 820 + 561 ", "answer": "-400", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3055", "question": "785 + -14 ", "answer": "771", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3056", "question": "-875 * 113 - 55 ", "answer": "-98930", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3057", "question": "-90 - 37 * -60 - -65 - -36 ", "answer": "2231", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3058", "question": "8039 - -1167 ", "answer": "9206", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3059", "question": "425 + -46 - -537 ", "answer": "916", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3060", "question": "-63 * -39 * -55 ", "answer": "-135135", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3061", "question": "8808 * 8533 - 2294 - -7402 ", "answer": "75163772", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3062", "question": "-506 + -503 - 471 * -617 ", "answer": "289598", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3063", "question": "56 + 51 * 74 * -92 ", "answer": "-347152", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3064", "question": "-71424 + 584767 + 933766 ", "answer": "1447109", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3065", "question": "-26 * 48 ", "answer": "-1248", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3066", "question": "-181600 * 501347 ", "answer": "-91044615200", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3067", "question": "-928118 * -862006 * -661054 + -78974 - 137796 ", "answer": "-528871813529579002", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3068", "question": "-38 + -44 * 14 + -64 - 58 ", "answer": "-776", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3069", "question": "-26 - -68 + -39 * -89 * -79 ", "answer": "-274167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3070", "question": "517653 - -851380 * 442610 - -115634 ", "answer": "376829935087", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3071", "question": "-264 + 914 - -416 * -560 ", "answer": "-232310", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3072", "question": "862 + 1466 + -8054 - -864 * 5779 ", "answer": "4987330", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3073", "question": "14440 * -79990 * 15741 + -82879 * 11651 ", "answer": "-18182695822829", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3074", "question": "-3 - 16 ", "answer": "-19", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3075", "question": "977636 * -779065 * -46123 * -593881 ", "answer": "-20862572454739447313420", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3076", "question": "852 * 253 ", "answer": "215556", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3077", "question": "-94248 + -58439 + -58610 ", "answer": "-211297", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3078", "question": "-6429 * 22 + 3476 ", "answer": "-137962", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3079", "question": "-21990 * -61454 ", "answer": "1351373460", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3080", "question": "493 - -346 + 1000 ", "answer": "1839", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3081", "question": "5482 * 7079 ", "answer": "38807078", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3082", "question": "-951 - 436 ", "answer": "-1387", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3083", "question": "-42556 - 898909 * -751775 - 73411 ", "answer": "675777197508", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3084", "question": "-220728 * -112269 + -575030 - -664009 + -630624 ", "answer": "24780370187", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3085", "question": "5557 - -1508 * -892 + 6706 - 5537 ", "answer": "-1338410", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3086", "question": "26694 + 46716 ", "answer": "73410", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3087", "question": "4408 + 9665 - -6511 + -7711 * 3609 ", "answer": "-27808415", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3088", "question": "-7 * -71 ", "answer": "497", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3089", "question": "-401 - -443 * -182 - 538 + -211 ", "answer": "-81776", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3090", "question": "61 - 32 - 33 ", "answer": "-4", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3091", "question": "-8836 * -5109 * -2760 - 8472 ", "answer": "-124595030712", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3092", "question": "-883310 - -381799 ", "answer": "-501511", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3093", "question": "-338892 + 480437 + 206487 ", "answer": "348032", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3094", "question": "81779 - 30959 - 25634 - -71658 - 10403 ", "answer": "86441", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3095", "question": "-674649 + 658890 - -512734 * 546565 + 332388 ", "answer": "280242775339", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3096", "question": "-94064 - 21231 ", "answer": "-115295", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3097", "question": "-56 + 31 - -28 + -57 ", "answer": "-54", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3098", "question": "5982 - 9720 - 390 ", "answer": "-4128", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3099", "question": "-7391 * -4139 * -4975 - 1308 - 7362 ", "answer": "-152191969945", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3100", "question": "-9244 + -3242 * -5013 - 1700 * -8 ", "answer": "16256502", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3101", "question": "-6429 * 5435 - 8087 ", "answer": "-34949702", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3102", "question": "-9867 + -98086 ", "answer": "-107953", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3103", "question": "-90917 - -40685 * 58894 + 8640 ", "answer": "2396020113", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3104", "question": "-90 * 90 ", "answer": "-8100", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3105", "question": "-43 * -99 - 55 + 68 - 50 ", "answer": "4220", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3106", "question": "-21 + 26 - 1 - -82 * -9 ", "answer": "-734", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3107", "question": "-423414 * 752155 - -519015 ", "answer": "-318472438155", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3108", "question": "-385 - -566 - 975 ", "answer": "-794", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3109", "question": "-42 * -32 + -40 * -18 ", "answer": "2064", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3110", "question": "-24 * 934 + -921 ", "answer": "-23337", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3111", "question": "33046 + 44537 ", "answer": "77583", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3112", "question": "2264 - -5009 * -5222 ", "answer": "-26154734", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3113", "question": "928 * 856 + 311 ", "answer": "794679", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3114", "question": "443 - 8815 ", "answer": "-8372", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3115", "question": "9748 - 5603 - 5799 + 7965 + -2388 ", "answer": "3923", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3116", "question": "42 - -31 ", "answer": "73", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3117", "question": "-9110 * -1385 * -5504 - 2942 ", "answer": "-69445897342", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3118", "question": "-57 * -81 * 44 + 82 * 13 ", "answer": "204214", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3119", "question": "21 + 23 + 55 + 41 * -100 ", "answer": "-4001", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3120", "question": "-37 + 58 * 46 * 19 * -9 ", "answer": "-456265", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3121", "question": "398521 - 480959 + 33501 ", "answer": "-48937", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3122", "question": "84 - -60 * 4 ", "answer": "324", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3123", "question": "18550 * -35817 ", "answer": "-664405350", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3124", "question": "614358 - 887477 + 971519 - 737492 * 352054 ", "answer": "-259636310168", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3125", "question": "-960091 - -145763 + -997584 * -384358 - -7251 ", "answer": "383428583995", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3126", "question": "-1405 * 5378 * -4845 + 7004 * -9012 ", "answer": "36546136002", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3127", "question": "433959 - 741502 + -668634 ", "answer": "-976177", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3128", "question": "63 + -98 - 90 ", "answer": "-125", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3129", "question": "440 - -986 - 37 ", "answer": "1389", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3130", "question": "2072 - -62926 + 46811 ", "answer": "111809", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3131", "question": "-491 * -438 - -909 * -982 * -640 ", "answer": "571503378", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3132", "question": "90 - -72 * -27 * -46 - -40 ", "answer": "89554", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3133", "question": "-326151 - -745922 - -395986 ", "answer": "815757", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3134", "question": "613 + 562 * -627 ", "answer": "-351761", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3135", "question": "7252 * 9367 * -9080 + -6735 ", "answer": "-616799721455", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3136", "question": "-65 * 704 - -238 ", "answer": "-45522", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3137", "question": "31637 + -34441 ", "answer": "-2804", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3138", "question": "31 - -573 - -596 * 821 * 928 ", "answer": "454085852", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3139", "question": "415375 * 220557 + -951820 - 516860 ", "answer": "91612395195", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3140", "question": "-699 - 23 ", "answer": "-722", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3141", "question": "-10582 * 81185 ", "answer": "-859099670", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3142", "question": "56044 * -88571 + 249 ", "answer": "-4963872875", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3143", "question": "-5840 - 9230 + -1674 - -9879 - 3199 ", "answer": "-10064", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3144", "question": "-893 * 765 ", "answer": "-683145", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3145", "question": "7089 * 839 * -8766 + -5211 - 3078 ", "answer": "-52137292275", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3146", "question": "-224901 - 123665 * 150484 ", "answer": "-18609828761", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3147", "question": "33 - 81 + 66 * 95 ", "answer": "6222", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3148", "question": "-93376 + 85902 + -55511 * -60299 ", "answer": "3347250315", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3149", "question": "4 - -80 - -78 ", "answer": "162", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3150", "question": "-81512 - 68383 - 62461 ", "answer": "-212356", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3151", "question": "4 + 95 + -93 ", "answer": "6", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3152", "question": "99707 + 61332 + 26638 * -52441 - 5077 ", "answer": "-1396767396", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3153", "question": "-37662 * -67816 * -97430 - -81158 + 88034 ", "answer": "-248844617517368", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3154", "question": "-76869 - 62874 * 95604 * 43779 - 66380 ", "answer": "-263155827264233", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3155", "question": "-94 * 21 ", "answer": "-1974", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3156", "question": "28667 * 15560 + -39121 ", "answer": "446019399", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3157", "question": "93987 + -271384 + -253722 - 431397 + 577880 ", "answer": "-284636", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3158", "question": "-61 * -58 + 24 * 55 ", "answer": "4858", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3159", "question": "9668 - -3026 - 9711 + 511 - 8135 ", "answer": "-4641", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3160", "question": "-44173 - -23159 - -59447 * 89401 ", "answer": "5314600233", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3161", "question": "62227 + -82884 - 43943 * -17525 ", "answer": "770080418", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3162", "question": "833 + 5322 + 8494 * 5246 ", "answer": "44565679", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3163", "question": "-72 + 33 + -53 - -18 ", "answer": "-74", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3164", "question": "-283 + -816 - 762 * -16 - -39 ", "answer": "11132", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3165", "question": "468720 * 366788 * -607869 ", "answer": "-104505368152731840", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3166", "question": "71 - -47 - -54 ", "answer": "172", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3167", "question": "31933 * 54186 - -80958 * -63240 ", "answer": "-3389462382", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3168", "question": "63 * 43 + 47 - 36 + 11 ", "answer": "2731", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3169", "question": "4977 * 747 ", "answer": "3717819", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3170", "question": "-13248 * -48297 - -88733 - 86582 * 31659 ", "answer": "-2101172149", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3171", "question": "501319 - 285343 ", "answer": "215976", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3172", "question": "4746 - -5236 * 6666 ", "answer": "34907922", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3173", "question": "77780 - -48589 * -21268 ", "answer": "-1033313072", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3174", "question": "451 - -22 * -394 ", "answer": "-8217", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3175", "question": "157 * -866 - -388 - -163 + -566 ", "answer": "-135977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3176", "question": "-809 - -624 ", "answer": "-185", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3177", "question": "-5039 * -9201 - -43 ", "answer": "46363882", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3178", "question": "-99 * 58 ", "answer": "-5742", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3179", "question": "966 - 363 ", "answer": "603", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3180", "question": "866 + 239 * -196 * -334 ", "answer": "15646762", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3181", "question": "-88197 + 432363 + -570473 + -553473 + -936357 ", "answer": "-1716137", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3182", "question": "514 * 325 - -776 ", "answer": "167826", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3183", "question": "-815966 - 473272 + 865499 ", "answer": "-423739", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3184", "question": "-673975 + 128347 ", "answer": "-545628", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3185", "question": "-11 - -65 * -11 - -38 ", "answer": "-688", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3186", "question": "-54676 * -66995 ", "answer": "3663018620", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3187", "question": "-78 * 63 - -31 ", "answer": "-4883", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3188", "question": "5621 + 2037 * 2569 ", "answer": "5238674", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3189", "question": "-516 + -693 ", "answer": "-1209", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3190", "question": "347 - -442 + -871 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3191", "question": "2782 * 58603 ", "answer": "163033546", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3192", "question": "-883 * -148 ", "answer": "130684", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3193", "question": "-62 - -99 - -23 ", "answer": "60", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3194", "question": "15 - 14 * 93 * -48 - 3 ", "answer": "62508", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3195", "question": "-618697 + -612309 + -984070 ", "answer": "-2215076", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3196", "question": "557781 - 270249 - -527170 + -73980 ", "answer": "740722", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3197", "question": "169850 + -501458 + -228628 - 373952 ", "answer": "-934188", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3198", "question": "-7251 - -6700 + -4981 ", "answer": "-5532", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3199", "question": "-249165 - 383765 ", "answer": "-632930", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3200", "question": "21 + 76 + 35 ", "answer": "132", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3201", "question": "76 * -40 + -32 + 27 ", "answer": "-3045", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3202", "question": "-31442 * 25602 - 41667 - 36221 ", "answer": "-805055972", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3203", "question": "-32760 + -96302 + -84020 + -74546 ", "answer": "-287628", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3204", "question": "-27717 + 570 + 99447 - 4509 * -95957 ", "answer": "432742413", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3205", "question": "56525 * -9045 - -23096 + 85215 + 65776 ", "answer": "-511094538", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3206", "question": "288 - 393 ", "answer": "-105", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3207", "question": "15 * 25 ", "answer": "375", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3208", "question": "141 - 72 ", "answer": "69", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3209", "question": "-77495 * -53820 ", "answer": "4170780900", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3210", "question": "209 + -761 * 909 + -287 * -394 ", "answer": "-578462", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3211", "question": "-89 - 57 ", "answer": "-146", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3212", "question": "-81229 + 50773 ", "answer": "-30456", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3213", "question": "-713757 - 189978 - -789607 + -572546 + 984620 ", "answer": "297946", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3214", "question": "-38096 - -73009 - -9044 ", "answer": "43957", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3215", "question": "463 * 204 * -740 - -616 * -394 ", "answer": "-70137184", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3216", "question": "45798 - 81585 - 50428 * 40746 ", "answer": "-2054775075", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3217", "question": "9473 + -4786 + -534 ", "answer": "4153", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3218", "question": "-702 + -6703 + 2095 ", "answer": "-5310", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3219", "question": "-900510 * 383429 - -259040 ", "answer": "-345281389750", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3220", "question": "5715 * -1193 ", "answer": "-6817995", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3221", "question": "-266 - 124 + 780 * 805 - -927 ", "answer": "628437", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3222", "question": "-100 * 13 * -38 + -6 ", "answer": "49394", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3223", "question": "-19894 - -6973 * 66891 * 48431 ", "answer": "22589716980539", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3224", "question": "59 + 3 - 31 + -85 * -59 ", "answer": "5046", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3225", "question": "136620 * -908428 + -261987 + 408956 * -539623 ", "answer": "-344791758935", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3226", "question": "3049 + -4867 * -1261 ", "answer": "6140336", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3227", "question": "-250313 * 587571 ", "answer": "-147076659723", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3228", "question": "39 + 65 - 94 ", "answer": "10", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3229", "question": "5637 + -76 + -6891 + 7168 - 3076 ", "answer": "2762", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3230", "question": "-80337 * -59685 + 35009 + -78765 + -71137 ", "answer": "4794798952", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3231", "question": "36 - 84 * -16 + 91 ", "answer": "1471", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3232", "question": "-167 - -718 + -83 + 969 + -77 ", "answer": "1360", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3233", "question": "-946948 * -144196 + -269139 ", "answer": "136545844669", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3234", "question": "-4005 + 763 * 980 + 6474 ", "answer": "750209", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3235", "question": "-59005 - 68991 - -98848 - 83972 - 67506 ", "answer": "-180626", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3236", "question": "-53710 + -4282 - 856279 + -716514 * -410888 ", "answer": "294406090161", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3237", "question": "-950 * 935 * -263 ", "answer": "233609750", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3238", "question": "-32 - 316 ", "answer": "-348", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3239", "question": "-23 * -22 ", "answer": "506", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3240", "question": "286 - 374 - -565 * 455 ", "answer": "256987", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3241", "question": "-545383 * 906287 * -81125 ", "answer": "40097939546966125", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3242", "question": "-8780 * -2754 + 6485 * 9069 ", "answer": "82992585", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3243", "question": "-354766 * 94348 - -891066 + 755433 ", "answer": "-33469816069", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3244", "question": "-442 * 517 - 511 - 288 ", "answer": "-229313", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3245", "question": "44 - 22 + 2 + 12 ", "answer": "36", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3246", "question": "-293649 * 424781 ", "answer": "-124736515869", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3247", "question": "-164 + 829 * 719 ", "answer": "595887", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3248", "question": "-2 * -35 * 34 ", "answer": "2380", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3249", "question": "-75816 - -70761 + 2495 - 25920 ", "answer": "-28480", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3250", "question": "-7173 - 42860 ", "answer": "-50033", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3251", "question": "22 * -99 ", "answer": "-2178", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3252", "question": "-74 + -27 ", "answer": "-101", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3253", "question": "-29401 + -90643 ", "answer": "-120044", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3254", "question": "-336 - 682 * -884 - 610 * 102 ", "answer": "540332", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3255", "question": "-92 + -49 + 9 ", "answer": "-132", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3256", "question": "-21 + -97 - -94 - -75 - -79 ", "answer": "130", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3257", "question": "-569482 + 696751 ", "answer": "127269", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3258", "question": "-39661 + -41623 ", "answer": "-81284", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3259", "question": "742 - -624 - 348 ", "answer": "1018", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3260", "question": "5505 - 9972 + -5973 - 6801 ", "answer": "-17241", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3261", "question": "569679 - -271920 ", "answer": "841599", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3262", "question": "2 - -20 - -28 * -15 ", "answer": "-398", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3263", "question": "-6140 * -8520 * -4186 ", "answer": "-218981380800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3264", "question": "-354168 - 893095 ", "answer": "-1247263", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3265", "question": "430670 + 772927 + -504541 * -996626 ", "answer": "502839882263", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3266", "question": "-3464 - 2866 + -3683 * -3445 - -8880 ", "answer": "12690485", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3267", "question": "80 - 48 + 30 - 90 + 40 ", "answer": "12", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3268", "question": "-4634 - 1548 ", "answer": "-6182", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3269", "question": "-99980 + -10066 + 62656 + -11451 ", "answer": "-58841", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3270", "question": "39 * 29 * -15 - 86 * -40 ", "answer": "-13525", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3271", "question": "-3429 + 9112 * -2581 + -6265 ", "answer": "-23527766", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3272", "question": "-579066 - 870176 * -395379 - 81843 ", "answer": "344048655795", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3273", "question": "11199 * 68776 + -10494 ", "answer": "770211930", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3274", "question": "69922 + -78847 * 15417 - -44289 * 71612 ", "answer": "1956109591", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3275", "question": "312300 - 607946 + 255656 * 574509 * -748041 ", "answer": "-109869773276076710", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3276", "question": "10 * -3 * -20 - -36 ", "answer": "636", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3277", "question": "-259 + 7819 ", "answer": "7560", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3278", "question": "-26381 * -15551 * 84353 - -82867 ", "answer": "34605896865510", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3279", "question": "-678 + -703 ", "answer": "-1381", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3280", "question": "-832579 + 146596 - -981978 * 923858 ", "answer": "907207545141", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3281", "question": "-30 - -40 * -55 * -2 * -81 ", "answer": "-356430", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3282", "question": "116 + -550 - -535 ", "answer": "101", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3283", "question": "-61640 - -52556 ", "answer": "-9084", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3284", "question": "-13 - 887 * 722 ", "answer": "-640427", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3285", "question": "-172013 - 693740 + -624772 ", "answer": "-1490525", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3286", "question": "423908 - -540218 + 319406 ", "answer": "1283532", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3287", "question": "77 - -74 - -22 - 2 - -77 ", "answer": "248", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3288", "question": "-268990 + 291015 - -945829 - 207930 ", "answer": "759924", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3289", "question": "30200 * -60339 - -68179 + 63443 ", "answer": "-1822106178", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3290", "question": "1222 - 66984 - 87959 - 99826 ", "answer": "-253547", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3291", "question": "1946 - 1487 * 4997 + 9613 ", "answer": "-7418980", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3292", "question": "-171 + 998 * 624 + -814 ", "answer": "621767", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3293", "question": "7010 + 7063 * -8064 + -7951 ", "answer": "-56956973", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3294", "question": "1920 * 5805 * 1260 ", "answer": "14043456000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3295", "question": "61270 + -32401 - 6272 ", "answer": "22597", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3296", "question": "8776 + 2401 - 3034 + 795 ", "answer": "8938", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3297", "question": "5371 * -2655 * -649 ", "answer": "9254743245", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3298", "question": "-1462 * -5118 - -239 - -3058 ", "answer": "7485813", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3299", "question": "-20 * -78 - -53 * -29 - -2 ", "answer": "25", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3300", "question": "-87774 - 65022 - -13553 ", "answer": "-139243", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3301", "question": "95 + 11 + 60 - -4 ", "answer": "170", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3302", "question": "-4069 + 2966 - 6591 - 2551 * 6175 ", "answer": "-15760119", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3303", "question": "2296 + 6800 - 4215 + -8373 - -856 ", "answer": "-2636", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3304", "question": "-246056 - 669254 * -928725 * -239286 - -343425 ", "answer": "-148728912290201531", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3305", "question": "889 - -35 ", "answer": "924", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3306", "question": "678300 + 765312 ", "answer": "1443612", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3307", "question": "-2994 - -8397 ", "answer": "5403", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3308", "question": "27979 + -34790 - 88472 - -18010 * 97621 ", "answer": "1758058927", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3309", "question": "-2254 + -1647 ", "answer": "-3901", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3310", "question": "593 + -768 + 965 + 457 ", "answer": "1247", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3311", "question": "-1728 * -1343 + 1021 ", "answer": "2321725", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3312", "question": "-67 + 31 - 11 ", "answer": "-47", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3313", "question": "1379 - 2926 ", "answer": "-1547", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3314", "question": "-9030 - 8151 - 5347 ", "answer": "-22528", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3315", "question": "-668 * 287 + 263 * -6 + 58 ", "answer": "-193236", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3316", "question": "5645 * -9060 - 7711 + 8 ", "answer": "-51151403", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3317", "question": "42 + 65 ", "answer": "107", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3318", "question": "-852 * 822 + -218 ", "answer": "-700562", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3319", "question": "25218 + 94413 ", "answer": "119631", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3320", "question": "2 - 76 ", "answer": "-74", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3321", "question": "-312563 - 138177 + 295897 - 147425 * 253626 ", "answer": "-37390967893", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3322", "question": "875770 + 438494 + -690556 * 90330 - -72441 ", "answer": "-62376536775", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3323", "question": "92 - -82 - -4 + 38 ", "answer": "216", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3324", "question": "-51 - -6 * 97 ", "answer": "531", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3325", "question": "-23 * -99 ", "answer": "2277", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3326", "question": "-245 - 770 - 217 ", "answer": "-1232", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3327", "question": "766 + -32 + -279 ", "answer": "455", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3328", "question": "-875902 * 75582 - 8028 + 159335 + 500045 ", "answer": "-66201773612", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3329", "question": "43369 * 327262 ", "answer": "14193025678", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3330", "question": "-41206 * -75430 * -64747 - 20896 * -75128 ", "answer": "-201243021174572", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3331", "question": "-86 - -71 + 62 - 16 ", "answer": "31", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3332", "question": "-813768 * -328935 * 878114 + -563090 - -942830 ", "answer": "235050725429206860", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3333", "question": "55589 * 57177 - 47399 - 99192 * 11178 ", "answer": "2069596678", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3334", "question": "-519 - -177 * -810 - -505 ", "answer": "-143384", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3335", "question": "-6193 * -6552 - -6078 ", "answer": "40582614", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3336", "question": "9245 + 7084 ", "answer": "16329", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3337", "question": "-3565 + 71582 ", "answer": "68017", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3338", "question": "856 + -797 ", "answer": "59", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3339", "question": "761 + 786 * 44 ", "answer": "35345", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3340", "question": "86 + -31 + -73 ", "answer": "-18", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3341", "question": "-79095 - 93352 - 41627 - -4543 - -46915 ", "answer": "-162616", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3342", "question": "6203 + -357 - 7727 * 5673 ", "answer": "-43829425", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3343", "question": "-8811 + 8338 - 6528 + -2691 + 7347 ", "answer": "-2345", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3344", "question": "4518 * 9723 + 9732 ", "answer": "43938246", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3345", "question": "21958 - 8418 ", "answer": "13540", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3346", "question": "-17565 - -44225 + -26044 + -37010 ", "answer": "-36394", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3347", "question": "92 + 72 ", "answer": "164", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3348", "question": "-902941 * 124131 * 308856 - -451039 ", "answer": "-34617497556712937", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3349", "question": "-10275 + -21058 + 13978 - 16989 ", "answer": "-34344", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3350", "question": "-76 * -26 - 28 + 33 ", "answer": "1981", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3351", "question": "-58375 + -99435 * 30068 * -99610 * -16822 ", "answer": "-5009846141820541975", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3352", "question": "609866 + 929759 + 76846 + -160997 * -692379 ", "answer": "111472558334", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3353", "question": "438062 - -410969 - -327208 ", "answer": "1176239", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3354", "question": "358 * 644 - -619 * -16 - 277 ", "answer": "220371", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3355", "question": "-391 + -3733 * -3462 * 3275 ", "answer": "42324940259", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3356", "question": "-3119 - 1873 ", "answer": "-4992", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3357", "question": "85 - -8 + -71 + -35 ", "answer": "-13", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3358", "question": "808039 - -965811 * -834678 + -366841 - -571576 ", "answer": "-806140181084", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3359", "question": "7527 - 7987 - 961 - 504 ", "answer": "-1925", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3360", "question": "207 * -960 + 69 ", "answer": "-198651", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3361", "question": "222909 - -188774 * -323055 + 65155 + -740830 ", "answer": "-60984837336", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3362", "question": "-24 - 97 + 99 - -98 * 32 ", "answer": "3114", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3363", "question": "-585 * 815 + 45 * -2007 ", "answer": "-567090", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3364", "question": "-211676 * -286041 + 86947 + -364135 ", "answer": "60547737528", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3365", "question": "16 + 80 + 86 + -88 ", "answer": "94", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3366", "question": "-39566 - -57775 ", "answer": "18209", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3367", "question": "348927 + -783508 - 10988 + 507813 - -128071 ", "answer": "190315", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3368", "question": "-4727 - -6999 - -1524 + 4743 - -4801 ", "answer": "13340", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3369", "question": "-93 * 90 + -51 + 67 + -56 ", "answer": "-8410", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3370", "question": "65 - -67 + 9 - 79 ", "answer": "62", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3371", "question": "586 + 210 ", "answer": "796", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3372", "question": "-46 + -80 - -40 + 11 ", "answer": "-75", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3373", "question": "-571 + 778 ", "answer": "207", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3374", "question": "-580257 * 146358 ", "answer": "-84925254006", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3375", "question": "-97625 - 19854 ", "answer": "-117479", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3376", "question": "-744 + -915 - 689 * -983 * 133 ", "answer": "90077512", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3377", "question": "-67 * -61 - 8 ", "answer": "4079", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3378", "question": "26940 - 40927 + -45300 ", "answer": "-59287", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3379", "question": "-976 + -223 * -259 ", "answer": "56781", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3380", "question": "27269 + 13093 * -48438 + -61821 + -35452 ", "answer": "-634268738", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3381", "question": "10110 * 82625 - -75663 + -98394 ", "answer": "835316019", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3382", "question": "-94 * 18 ", "answer": "-1692", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3383", "question": "402 * 65 ", "answer": "26130", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3384", "question": "-80070 + -4252 * 13462 ", "answer": "-57320494", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3385", "question": "-600 * -952 - -560 * -767 + -296 ", "answer": "141384", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3386", "question": "156 * -431 + -988 * -177 ", "answer": "107640", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3387", "question": "-823644 + -688073 - 800739 ", "answer": "-2312456", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3388", "question": "-9167 + -4708 ", "answer": "-13875", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3389", "question": "-8088 * -5397 - -6613 + -4230 ", "answer": "43653319", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3390", "question": "-337 - 497 ", "answer": "-834", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3391", "question": "4723 * -3677 * -9969 + 9996 + 3107 ", "answer": "173126362502", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3392", "question": "606 - 543 + 506 + 966 + 303 ", "answer": "1838", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3393", "question": "-8922 - -554 ", "answer": "-8368", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3394", "question": "785147 + 204711 * -861498 ", "answer": "-176357331931", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3395", "question": "-16 - 31 ", "answer": "-47", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3396", "question": "914 + -853 - 550 + 409 + 725 ", "answer": "645", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3397", "question": "-948430 - -436418 - -156462 * 378738 + 617207 ", "answer": "59258210151", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3398", "question": "-23848 * 20872 + 53680 ", "answer": "-497701776", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3399", "question": "-75307 * -577619 + -480330 * 176281 ", "answer": "-41174298697", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3400", "question": "-6 + 43 - 60 * -19 ", "answer": "1177", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3401", "question": "60 - -82 - 26 - -80 + 27 ", "answer": "223", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3402", "question": "683 + 785 ", "answer": "1468", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3403", "question": "-299899 + 897753 * 963454 * 639441 * 563817 ", "answer": "311836175037314074774115", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3404", "question": "4885 + -5197 ", "answer": "-312", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3405", "question": "797774 * 242181 + 452339 - -432866 ", "answer": "193206590299", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3406", "question": "155334 + 648784 - -884313 ", "answer": "1688431", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3407", "question": "-449078 + 511250 - -152923 ", "answer": "215095", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3408", "question": "-849836 - -87947 + -429133 + -897792 ", "answer": "-2088814", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3409", "question": "2841 + -3953 - -8635 * -2129 ", "answer": "-18385027", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3410", "question": "71 - 39 ", "answer": "32", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3411", "question": "283 - -863 - -410 + 879 ", "answer": "2435", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3412", "question": "90983 - 8957 - 75804 * 12887 + -85895 ", "answer": "-976890017", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3413", "question": "-94 - 73 - -60 + 82 ", "answer": "-25", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3414", "question": "13 * 26 + 56 + -72 - -55 ", "answer": "377", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3415", "question": "60 * -88 * 19 ", "answer": "-100320", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3416", "question": "1669 + -565 + -9733 ", "answer": "-8629", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3417", "question": "381617 - -334422 * -863980 - 393235 + 153033 ", "answer": "-288933778145", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3418", "question": "684 - -537 ", "answer": "1221", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3419", "question": "8147 + 3295 - -1518 + -3569 - 8463 ", "answer": "928", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3420", "question": "-137 + -21 + 893 + -980 + 51 ", "answer": "-194", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3421", "question": "-30274 + -28063 * -78083 + 26897 - 64089 ", "answer": "2191175763", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3422", "question": "-81 * -16 ", "answer": "1296", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3423", "question": "246 - -2685 * 8020 + 3823 * 4429 ", "answer": "38466013", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3424", "question": "-9223 - 775 - 1477 ", "answer": "-11475", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3425", "question": "-431197 - 12881 * 812380 ", "answer": "-10464697977", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3426", "question": "7429 * 542 ", "answer": "4026518", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3427", "question": "787675 * 910447 ", "answer": "717136340725", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3428", "question": "2343 - -3774 ", "answer": "6117", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3429", "question": "-13534 - 21255 ", "answer": "-34789", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3430", "question": "-954 - -2470 ", "answer": "1516", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3431", "question": "-34821 * 10403 + 23555 ", "answer": "-362219308", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3432", "question": "-9391 - 1621 - -4849 + -3671 ", "answer": "-9834", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3433", "question": "56557 * -54093 + 33979 - 77694 * -44057 ", "answer": "363660736", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3434", "question": "-2744 - 2920 ", "answer": "-5664", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3435", "question": "22 * -50 + -78 * 80 * 29 ", "answer": "-182060", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3436", "question": "78 * 33 - 86 - 29 ", "answer": "2459", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3437", "question": "257 * -7599 - 5242 * 445 ", "answer": "-4285633", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3438", "question": "493023 + -308776 + -862527 + -409826 - -98639 ", "answer": "-989467", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3439", "question": "82 * 14 - 55 * 99 - -33 ", "answer": "-4264", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3440", "question": "320311 + 49059 * 646644 + -864439 ", "answer": "31723163868", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3441", "question": "726 + 508 * -955 + 98 ", "answer": "-484316", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3442", "question": "13015 + -672340 * 273965 - -179236 * -629815 ", "answer": "-297083136425", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3443", "question": "-6613 * -4990 - 1520 ", "answer": "32997350", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3444", "question": "-92 - -96 * 87 + 32 ", "answer": "8292", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3445", "question": "24328 + -39650 ", "answer": "-15322", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3446", "question": "-819214 - -977872 ", "answer": "158658", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3447", "question": "-269 - 683 - -667 + 261 ", "answer": "-24", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3448", "question": "728953 - 61188 * 995340 * 904173 ", "answer": "-55066725178409207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3449", "question": "47894 - -95898 ", "answer": "143792", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3450", "question": "-52629 * -17449 - -7847 ", "answer": "918331268", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3451", "question": "49844 + 27202 - 46211 - -14940 * -72425 ", "answer": "-1081998665", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3452", "question": "829 * 354 ", "answer": "293466", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3453", "question": "99855 - -48542 * 96407 * -70971 + -67893 ", "answer": "-332129276272812", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3454", "question": "35493 + -85599 - -52519 ", "answer": "2413", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3455", "question": "9 + -32 - 48 ", "answer": "-71", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3456", "question": "-802472 * 226318 ", "answer": "-181613858096", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3457", "question": "74 + 11 ", "answer": "85", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3458", "question": "-667833 * 30522 * -411396 - -66587 ", "answer": "8385731022687683", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3459", "question": "-82 - -1 + -39 ", "answer": "-120", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3460", "question": "-5496 + 9178 ", "answer": "3682", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3461", "question": "1864 + 8566 + 5381 * 9073 + 9582 ", "answer": "48841825", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3462", "question": "-562826 + 156505 ", "answer": "-406321", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3463", "question": "89 + -74 ", "answer": "15", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3464", "question": "-339 * -876 ", "answer": "296964", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3465", "question": "2104 - -64476 * -6302 + 28751 ", "answer": "-406296897", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3466", "question": "-22 - 36 ", "answer": "-58", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3467", "question": "409 + 15 ", "answer": "424", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3468", "question": "-769 * 7772 * -1275 - 5514 ", "answer": "7620246186", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3469", "question": "354 * -810 ", "answer": "-286740", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3470", "question": "-185 + 860 * 716 ", "answer": "615575", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3471", "question": "10428 - -10839 ", "answer": "21267", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3472", "question": "611 * -620 + -172 + 763 - 532 ", "answer": "-378761", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3473", "question": "-351 - 98 ", "answer": "-449", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3474", "question": "-36 * 27 ", "answer": "-972", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3475", "question": "-518648 + -724776 + -620481 + 148381 ", "answer": "-1715524", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3476", "question": "-484 + -86 ", "answer": "-570", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3477", "question": "-81 - -15 * 57 ", "answer": "774", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3478", "question": "-167811 - 48465 + 373463 + -681542 + -35756 ", "answer": "-560111", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3479", "question": "-273 * -306 * -971 + 338 * 885 ", "answer": "-80816268", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3480", "question": "-33523 * -74200 ", "answer": "2487406600", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3481", "question": "202978 + 63851 ", "answer": "266829", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3482", "question": "42 * 166 ", "answer": "6972", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3483", "question": "214 * 570 - -764 + 650 * -487 ", "answer": "-193806", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3484", "question": "8884 + -5174 ", "answer": "3710", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3485", "question": "-186194 - 54948 + -519522 + 183078 + 747451 ", "answer": "169865", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3486", "question": "-883139 * 185965 - 803520 - -179891 ", "answer": "-164233567764", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3487", "question": "-3966 * -669 * 105 * 2847 - -2918 ", "answer": "793150487408", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3488", "question": "75 + -78 ", "answer": "-3", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3489", "question": "415 * -728 * 3230 ", "answer": "-975847600", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3490", "question": "105 + -252 ", "answer": "-147", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3491", "question": "355 * 388 * 127 * -668 * -146 ", "answer": "1706055353440", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3492", "question": "-31347 + 56510 ", "answer": "25163", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3493", "question": "96 * -33 ", "answer": "-3168", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3494", "question": "-109 + -875 + -301 * -213 ", "answer": "63129", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3495", "question": "85760 * 9053 ", "answer": "776385280", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3496", "question": "-45755 + -26584 ", "answer": "-72339", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3497", "question": "-4063 - 9006 ", "answer": "-13069", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3498", "question": "-6109 - -1881 ", "answer": "-4228", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3499", "question": "828 + -351 ", "answer": "477", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3500", "question": "34 * -40 * 13 - 5 - -77 ", "answer": "-17608", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3501", "question": "39319 + -36474 * 98393 - -67632 ", "answer": "-3588679331", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3502", "question": "-23 + -49 * -87 - -44 ", "answer": "4284", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3503", "question": "-24548 - -66705 ", "answer": "42157", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3504", "question": "-2190 * -8902 - -8528 ", "answer": "19503908", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3505", "question": "18006 - -20592 - 51904 ", "answer": "-13306", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3506", "question": "-322 * -5278 ", "answer": "1699516", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3507", "question": "-53 + 5 - 36 + 37 ", "answer": "-47", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3508", "question": "885 * 1956 + -6169 - -1450 + 3131 ", "answer": "1729472", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3509", "question": "11 * 12 - -29 - -92 * 54 ", "answer": "5129", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3510", "question": "366 + -876 + -896 - 438 ", "answer": "-1844", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3511", "question": "-84 - 13 ", "answer": "-97", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3512", "question": "-426238 - -921015 + 848477 ", "answer": "1343254", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3513", "question": "9217 * 9125 * -2295 - -8220 ", "answer": "-193021253655", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3514", "question": "27 - -48 ", "answer": "75", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3515", "question": "499588 * 49045 + 606180 ", "answer": "24502899640", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3516", "question": "497752 * 573946 + 876747 - -375185 ", "answer": "285684021324", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3517", "question": "-70 - 68 ", "answer": "-138", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3518", "question": "-785 - 88 * -326 - -102 * 869 ", "answer": "116541", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3519", "question": "219 * 637 - 818 ", "answer": "138685", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3520", "question": "6849 + -211 ", "answer": "6638", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3521", "question": "178357 - 662815 + 33326 - -639514 ", "answer": "188382", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3522", "question": "-740 * 986 - -899 - 497 + -717 ", "answer": "-729955", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3523", "question": "-828064 * 896883 + 715120 ", "answer": "-742675809392", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3524", "question": "4660 - 4903 ", "answer": "-243", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3525", "question": "-503143 + -540936 ", "answer": "-1044079", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3526", "question": "-80 * 747 ", "answer": "-59760", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3527", "question": "20134 - 93678 ", "answer": "-73544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3528", "question": "8569 - 67072 * -57742 * 43644 + 73544 ", "answer": "169027600511169", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3529", "question": "61542 - -47799 ", "answer": "109341", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3530", "question": "-3787 - -8541 * 4983 - -4499 ", "answer": "42560515", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3531", "question": "-68701 * 46148 ", "answer": "-3170413748", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3532", "question": "70 * -922 + -632 * -260 * 231 ", "answer": "37893380", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3533", "question": "-42 * -65 + -91 * -68 ", "answer": "8918", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3534", "question": "1897 + -8688 * -6193 * -8352 ", "answer": "-449377554071", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3535", "question": "-471 - -238 + -335 ", "answer": "-568", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3536", "question": "1498 - 2613 ", "answer": "-1115", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3537", "question": "100 - -80 - 69 + 85 * -52 ", "answer": "-4309", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3538", "question": "-9685 + -7001 - -8019 - -7522 ", "answer": "-1145", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3539", "question": "-31065 - 12904 + 14148 ", "answer": "-29821", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3540", "question": "-65764 * 23611 * -43364 - 90288 + 75857 ", "answer": "67333615942225", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3541", "question": "732 - 647 + 152 - 166 + -982 ", "answer": "-911", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3542", "question": "639587 + -88082 + -678877 - -916759 + 925586 ", "answer": "1714973", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3543", "question": "147 * 271 ", "answer": "39837", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3544", "question": "-468 * -576 ", "answer": "269568", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3545", "question": "-911080 * -492815 ", "answer": "448993890200", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3546", "question": "-723088 * 483079 + -159316 - 468930 * -80564 ", "answer": "-311529910748", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3547", "question": "-30 - -37 * 89 ", "answer": "3263", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3548", "question": "201 + 8 * -369 + 996 ", "answer": "-1755", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3549", "question": "-647 + 306 ", "answer": "-341", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3550", "question": "-8763 * -93383 ", "answer": "818315229", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3551", "question": "656322 + 660558 - 286763 + 119338 - -950931 ", "answer": "2100386", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3552", "question": "206 - -996 - 677 * 882 * 814 ", "answer": "-486049594", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3553", "question": "465 * -517 ", "answer": "-240405", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3554", "question": "-295 - 29 - -331 - 285 - -27 ", "answer": "-251", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3555", "question": "-926467 * -689122 - -999128 + -939696 ", "answer": "638448851406", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3556", "question": "-15255 - 93561 - 63326 - 2762 ", "answer": "-174904", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3557", "question": "-675 * -136 - 524 + 4 + -841 ", "answer": "90439", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3558", "question": "861123 + 539980 * 742313 + -874653 * 51688 ", "answer": "355625970599", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3559", "question": "80851 - 78172 ", "answer": "2679", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3560", "question": "44908 - -47502 - 12624 ", "answer": "79786", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3561", "question": "-52 - -34 ", "answer": "-18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3562", "question": "48609 - -349724 + -674358 - 115923 ", "answer": "-391948", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3563", "question": "99 * 43 + -20 ", "answer": "4237", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3564", "question": "-95 + -78 - -55 ", "answer": "-118", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3565", "question": "8757 * -9226 - 7222 - 9910 ", "answer": "-80809214", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3566", "question": "-1 + 95 * -16 ", "answer": "-1521", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3567", "question": "71 - -24 ", "answer": "95", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3568", "question": "619 + 3035 ", "answer": "3654", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3569", "question": "525 - -134 + -703 ", "answer": "-44", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3570", "question": "-30064 * -5849 - -54173 + 93281 * -99953 ", "answer": "-9147817284", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3571", "question": "-391 - -74 - -174 * -512 ", "answer": "-89405", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3572", "question": "321429 * 538491 ", "answer": "173086623639", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3573", "question": "-558447 - -157981 - 171898 - -775025 - 276815 ", "answer": "-74154", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3574", "question": "212 + -288 ", "answer": "-76", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3575", "question": "-691 + -313 - -973 + -648 ", "answer": "-679", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3576", "question": "-77 * -33 + -43 - 14 - 87 ", "answer": "2397", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3577", "question": "24668 - -19229 * 44193 ", "answer": "849811865", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3578", "question": "30060 * 29102 ", "answer": "874806120", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3579", "question": "35 * -45 * 88 + -84 + -17 ", "answer": "-138701", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3580", "question": "109 + 640 - 845 + -610 + -623 ", "answer": "-1329", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3581", "question": "-8964 - -4927 + -5183 * 9510 + -3028 ", "answer": "-49297395", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3582", "question": "-5692 - 2764 ", "answer": "-8456", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3583", "question": "-883 - 66 * -744 - 984 ", "answer": "47237", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3584", "question": "-9935 - -7471 * -3176 ", "answer": "-23737831", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3585", "question": "-624 + -597 ", "answer": "-1221", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3586", "question": "97452 - 48864 ", "answer": "48588", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3587", "question": "270 * -4266 ", "answer": "-1151820", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3588", "question": "2858 + 3593 ", "answer": "6451", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3589", "question": "23 - 51 ", "answer": "-28", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3590", "question": "-978 - -927 ", "answer": "-51", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3591", "question": "-961 * 924 ", "answer": "-887964", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3592", "question": "-516 + -2878 ", "answer": "-3394", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3593", "question": "-951 * 844 * 834 - -400 ", "answer": "-669404696", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3594", "question": "-346497 * 42952 + 486978 ", "answer": "-14882252166", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3595", "question": "-312850 * -273736 - -385965 ", "answer": "85638693565", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3596", "question": "7066 - 8232 * 2848 ", "answer": "-23437670", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3597", "question": "-93 - 66 + 81 ", "answer": "-78", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3598", "question": "-2991 * 3068 + -249 * 9046 * 5252 ", "answer": "-11839064796", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3599", "question": "72479 + 78798 + 15948 ", "answer": "167225", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3600", "question": "2640 + 1274 + -3674 - 8133 ", "answer": "-7893", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3601", "question": "283 - 922 * 577 ", "answer": "-531711", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3602", "question": "897 - -549 ", "answer": "1446", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3603", "question": "-85331 - 77245 + -81421 + 75094 - -29339 ", "answer": "-139564", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3604", "question": "-25321 * -87147 - -18871 + 42421 ", "answer": "2206710479", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3605", "question": "-9852 * -9297 ", "answer": "91594044", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3606", "question": "-57191 + -53389 ", "answer": "-110580", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3607", "question": "-29330 - 38888 ", "answer": "-68218", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3608", "question": "-9838 - 1944 - 4852 - -3921 ", "answer": "-12713", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3609", "question": "-695 + -892 - 101 * -580 ", "answer": "56993", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3610", "question": "-10186 + -57031 * -31664 ", "answer": "1805819398", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3611", "question": "-320221 * 381353 ", "answer": "-122117239013", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3612", "question": "55 * 16 + 15 - -54 ", "answer": "949", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3613", "question": "-55309 - 31954 + -50031 - -92708 ", "answer": "-44586", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3614", "question": "65 + -66 + -82 ", "answer": "-83", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3615", "question": "-7 + -88 ", "answer": "-95", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3616", "question": "382 + 344 - 983 - 886 - 701 ", "answer": "-1844", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3617", "question": "634933 * -474896 ", "answer": "-301527141968", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3618", "question": "-463 + 278 ", "answer": "-185", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3619", "question": "-67243 - -84700 * 64426 + -6603 ", "answer": "5456808354", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3620", "question": "53209 * -93529 * -60635 ", "answer": "301755204856235", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3621", "question": "98 * 250 - 213 ", "answer": "24287", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3622", "question": "-4726 + -7222 - -7605 ", "answer": "-4343", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3623", "question": "-474655 + -119814 * 850215 - 898508 + 791405 ", "answer": "-101868241768", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3624", "question": "28828 - 28143 ", "answer": "685", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3625", "question": "-56 - -15 * 89 * -46 ", "answer": "-61466", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3626", "question": "-53963 - -14540 * -2084 + -66490 ", "answer": "-30421813", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3627", "question": "18 * -70 + -4 ", "answer": "-1264", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3628", "question": "168253 - 770409 * -984587 - 98450 * -867202 ", "answer": "843910891236", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3629", "question": "3979 - 3964 - 6235 * 3020 ", "answer": "-18829685", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3630", "question": "29 - -26 - 78 * 82 * 51 ", "answer": "-326141", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3631", "question": "67 * 65 * 90 + 67 * -29 ", "answer": "390007", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3632", "question": "-92884 * 89373 - -88145 + -25957 + -90743 ", "answer": "-8301350287", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3633", "question": "596315 * -985766 * 349027 * -640744 + -746360 ", "answer": "131459852680317209095160", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3634", "question": "187280 + 952913 - -151451 ", "answer": "1291644", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3635", "question": "92 - -53 + 95 - -13 ", "answer": "253", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3636", "question": "-790 - 137 + 175 ", "answer": "-752", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3637", "question": "-5347 + -4139 ", "answer": "-9486", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3638", "question": "-1406 - -12878 - 83230 * -50862 * 29522 ", "answer": "124973837055192", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3639", "question": "-7268 * -9458 + -6137 - -4041 - -4463 ", "answer": "68743111", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3640", "question": "-249 * 250 * -397 * 603 * -910 ", "answer": "-13560901672500", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3641", "question": "91 * -39 ", "answer": "-3549", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3642", "question": "68116 - -35985 * -60658 + -84715 - 23709 ", "answer": "-2182818438", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3643", "question": "820 + -832 + -615 ", "answer": "-627", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3644", "question": "10381 + -9986 ", "answer": "395", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3645", "question": "24 * -31 + -7 * 46 ", "answer": "-1066", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3646", "question": "-4887 + 7256 * -7932 + 82528 * -40988 ", "answer": "-3440217143", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3647", "question": "880 - 296 ", "answer": "584", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3648", "question": "920658 + -229288 ", "answer": "691370", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3649", "question": "331 + -791 * -421 ", "answer": "333342", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3650", "question": "19644 + -9366 * 79965 ", "answer": "-748932546", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3651", "question": "-38 * 93 + 57 - 38 ", "answer": "-3515", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3652", "question": "883 * 457 * 27 - 239 ", "answer": "10895098", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3653", "question": "-41231 - -85842 * -42170 - 72500 * -77943 ", "answer": "2030869129", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3654", "question": "342708 + -189252 * -810481 ", "answer": "153385492920", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3655", "question": "-66 - 75 * 63 - -16 - 55 ", "answer": "-4830", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3656", "question": "5379 - 8663 - 1438 + 1118 * -260 ", "answer": "-295402", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3657", "question": "-549095 + -748628 ", "answer": "-1297723", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3658", "question": "124 + -202 + -305 - -39 + 154 ", "answer": "-190", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3659", "question": "-455987 + 570403 * -108521 ", "answer": "-61901159950", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3660", "question": "177656 - -586711 - -529082 * 856168 ", "answer": "452983842143", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3661", "question": "-362692 - 208559 * -664561 - -51586 ", "answer": "138599866493", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3662", "question": "-382405 * 802450 - -121814 + -354068 ", "answer": "-306861124504", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3663", "question": "318 - 666 ", "answer": "-348", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3664", "question": "7229 * 32582 * -35526 * -51920 + -96535 ", "answer": "434447156780861225", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3665", "question": "-689292 - -308409 * -119666 + 958706 + 775572 ", "answer": "-36905026408", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3666", "question": "7944 - 729 * -3033 * 815 ", "answer": "1802019399", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3667", "question": "-359607 * -916981 - 262579 + -150404 - -545460 ", "answer": "329752918944", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3668", "question": "734 - 911 * -881 * -947 ", "answer": "-760052943", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3669", "question": "435114 - 564771 ", "answer": "-129657", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3670", "question": "1655 * -5966 + -2173 + 6137 ", "answer": "-9869766", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3671", "question": "-5574 + -4778 - 1079 ", "answer": "-11431", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3672", "question": "6728 + -3852 ", "answer": "2876", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3673", "question": "612 * -203 + 475 + 488 ", "answer": "-123273", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3674", "question": "743119 - -862906 ", "answer": "1606025", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3675", "question": "86511 * 41976 + -52524 * 91383 ", "answer": "-1168414956", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3676", "question": "2157 + -465 * -9405 - 9290 - -5315 ", "answer": "4371507", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3677", "question": "837298 - -617146 ", "answer": "1454444", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3678", "question": "48275 * -45731 * 55624 + 18400 + 58106 ", "answer": "-122799103650094", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3679", "question": "-73468 + 39939 ", "answer": "-33529", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3680", "question": "9291 + 3078 ", "answer": "12369", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3681", "question": "-32 * -477 ", "answer": "15264", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3682", "question": "-7334 * 3321 - -8811 - 6112 ", "answer": "-24353515", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3683", "question": "-89 * 3 + 93 - -100 - 45 ", "answer": "-119", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3684", "question": "-4905 * -276 + -6728 * 9677 * 6219 ", "answer": "-404898183684", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3685", "question": "-5 - -25 * -88 * 80 ", "answer": "-176005", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3686", "question": "734 + -206 ", "answer": "528", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3687", "question": "61 * -4 ", "answer": "-244", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3688", "question": "1487 - 7006 - 3343 ", "answer": "-8862", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3689", "question": "-46499 + -82898 + -55735 ", "answer": "-185132", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3690", "question": "-10 + -10 + 87 ", "answer": "67", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3691", "question": "623 + -703 * 417 ", "answer": "-292528", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3692", "question": "-2966 * -7206 + -8522 + -6057 + 1107 ", "answer": "21359524", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3693", "question": "107421 + -710173 * -253854 + -439785 ", "answer": "180279924378", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3694", "question": "-41806 * 56806 + -21420 ", "answer": "-2374853056", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3695", "question": "85 + 60 * -71 ", "answer": "-4175", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3696", "question": "-40358 * 61809 * -54669 ", "answer": "136371143807118", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3697", "question": "2393 - 67993 + -24367 - -69989 + -5995 ", "answer": "-25973", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3698", "question": "35 + 69 + 43 * 79 - -94 ", "answer": "3595", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3699", "question": "501 + -677 * -423 + -794 ", "answer": "286078", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3700", "question": "-29213 * 28804 ", "answer": "-841451252", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3701", "question": "-552825 + -776179 + -120959 - 758580 ", "answer": "-2208543", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3702", "question": "57 * 90 * -31 + -89 + -59 ", "answer": "-159178", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3703", "question": "7812 - -1328 ", "answer": "9140", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3704", "question": "14 - 60 + 56 ", "answer": "10", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3705", "question": "869 + -468 ", "answer": "401", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3706", "question": "98082 * 710478 ", "answer": "69685103196", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3707", "question": "251757 + -585792 + 625861 ", "answer": "291826", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3708", "question": "-489366 + 743128 * 490667 - -549002 * 151384 ", "answer": "447738015778", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3709", "question": "-797591 - -390307 + 863091 - 88203 ", "answer": "367604", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3710", "question": "58839 * 59707 * 57904 + -17254 - -98728 ", "answer": "203422552498866", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3711", "question": "5204 * 6406 ", "answer": "33336824", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3712", "question": "450 * -672 + 487 + 60 - -20 ", "answer": "-301833", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3713", "question": "-30 * -48 - 27 ", "answer": "1413", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3714", "question": "-184913 + -731200 * -995893 * 820746 + -863748 ", "answer": "597664743444304939", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3715", "question": "300 - -206 + 306 + 883 ", "answer": "1695", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3716", "question": "-704 * -441 + 273 ", "answer": "310737", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3717", "question": "97 + -65 - 45 ", "answer": "-13", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3718", "question": "17 * 49 * -26 - 16 ", "answer": "-21674", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3719", "question": "83 + -97 + 85 + -90 ", "answer": "-19", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3720", "question": "-686409 * 667986 - 219887 ", "answer": "-458511822161", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3721", "question": "7829 * -4088 + 747 * 500 - -4052 ", "answer": "-31627400", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3722", "question": "9468 * 4607 - -6289 ", "answer": "43625365", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3723", "question": "538255 * 639449 + 331649 * -344803 ", "answer": "229833051348", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3724", "question": "-90730 - -2543 - -90210 ", "answer": "2023", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3725", "question": "393871 + -825131 + 951981 ", "answer": "520721", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3726", "question": "-100 - 67 + -72 + 43 - -11 ", "answer": "-185", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3727", "question": "-58 - -94 ", "answer": "36", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3728", "question": "70 * 75 - -55 ", "answer": "5305", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3729", "question": "-32933 - 97558 + -7016 ", "answer": "-137507", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3730", "question": "-43 + -5401 - 2709 + 3962 - 2419 ", "answer": "-6610", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3731", "question": "218 - -880 * 857 ", "answer": "754378", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3732", "question": "880 - -15 ", "answer": "895", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3733", "question": "3413 - 2495 ", "answer": "918", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3734", "question": "8306 + -3273 + -2124 ", "answer": "2909", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3735", "question": "-6201 - 4914 ", "answer": "-11115", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3736", "question": "773 * 206 - -730 - -381 ", "answer": "160349", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3737", "question": "319 * -876 + -947 + 116 * -644 ", "answer": "-355095", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3738", "question": "-91534 - 20150 ", "answer": "-111684", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3739", "question": "-68683 - 774226 + -287460 ", "answer": "-1130369", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3740", "question": "486297 + 898294 * -297204 ", "answer": "-266976083679", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3741", "question": "228731 + 95608 ", "answer": "324339", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3742", "question": "-131558 * 662652 * -753690 + 192141 ", "answer": "65704562626193181", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3743", "question": "-780 + -247 ", "answer": "-1027", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3744", "question": "92972 * 66177 + 26884 ", "answer": "6152634928", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3745", "question": "76276 + -97199 ", "answer": "-20923", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3746", "question": "-294 * -884 * 916 + 658 ", "answer": "238065394", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3747", "question": "-49 * -56 * -32 * 51 ", "answer": "-4478208", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3748", "question": "4663 - -5563 ", "answer": "10226", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3749", "question": "-89696 + -23863 ", "answer": "-113559", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3750", "question": "-13375 + -80597 + -95099 ", "answer": "-189071", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3751", "question": "-122 - -682 + 942 + -192 ", "answer": "1310", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3752", "question": "-8403 * 384 - -5927 - 4156 + 3418 ", "answer": "-3221563", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3753", "question": "-64828 * -88496 - -11123 ", "answer": "5737029811", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3754", "question": "-2196 * -2628 + 4353 - -221 ", "answer": "5775662", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3755", "question": "444949 - 256835 - 594035 - 175143 ", "answer": "-581064", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3756", "question": "23807 - -28078 ", "answer": "51885", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3757", "question": "-997 - -3140 * 8206 + -5577 + -211 ", "answer": "25760055", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3758", "question": "-345 * -672 - 21 ", "answer": "231819", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3759", "question": "-823 * 328 - -1602 + 1759 ", "answer": "-266583", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3760", "question": "270 + -179 + -407 - 868 ", "answer": "-1184", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3761", "question": "-215 + 134 - 550 ", "answer": "-631", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3762", "question": "-1100 * -6011 + 9310 * -8654 ", "answer": "-73956640", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3763", "question": "-45989 * -19240 ", "answer": "884828360", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3764", "question": "607 * 247 - 278 * -119 ", "answer": "183011", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3765", "question": "-5756 * -9646 + -7633 * -2565 ", "answer": "75101021", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3766", "question": "-769899 - -609370 - -984280 * 472607 ", "answer": "465177457431", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3767", "question": "-780 - 939 ", "answer": "-1719", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3768", "question": "41955 + -18821 + -21696 * 2149 ", "answer": "-46601570", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3769", "question": "718570 - -935285 ", "answer": "1653855", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3770", "question": "-602072 * -359683 ", "answer": "216555063176", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3771", "question": "4169 + -9376 ", "answer": "-5207", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3772", "question": "-17929 * -7458 - 61378 ", "answer": "133653104", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3773", "question": "-507659 - -798743 ", "answer": "291084", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3774", "question": "93 - 20 ", "answer": "73", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3775", "question": "-7759 + -1377 * -1916 * -349 ", "answer": "-920785627", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3776", "question": "-40118 + 846316 + 397228 - 184444 + 39510 ", "answer": "1058492", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3777", "question": "-522805 + -282460 - 625280 ", "answer": "-1430545", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3778", "question": "-267647 * 477332 * 716575 + -695400 + 419071 ", "answer": "-91547098082677629", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3779", "question": "746806 - -39634 + -699157 ", "answer": "87283", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3780", "question": "-63 * -3 ", "answer": "189", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3781", "question": "-847141 + -517060 + 951866 - -792713 ", "answer": "380378", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3782", "question": "-486906 - 149608 + 977886 * 507742 - 140753 ", "answer": "496513016145", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3783", "question": "-884401 + -181471 + 221906 * 13596 + 715287 ", "answer": "3016683391", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3784", "question": "-85 + -13 * -88 ", "answer": "1059", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3785", "question": "-730119 * -182975 - 381010 * -356574 ", "answer": "269451783765", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3786", "question": "-28 * -13 + 58 ", "answer": "422", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3787", "question": "98023 + -67689 ", "answer": "30334", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3788", "question": "289583 - 10727 + -342829 + 418608 ", "answer": "354635", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3789", "question": "-57 * 5 - -34 * -90 ", "answer": "-3345", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3790", "question": "-9291 - 5078 + 139 - 9161 ", "answer": "-23391", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3791", "question": "71838 + 94025 * 61005 + -87156 - -12827 ", "answer": "5735992634", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3792", "question": "-48 + 26 * 70 ", "answer": "1772", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3793", "question": "71760 - -88972 - -91613 + -23755 ", "answer": "228590", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3794", "question": "39 * 58 ", "answer": "2262", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3795", "question": "-116 - -227 ", "answer": "111", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3796", "question": "571 - 18 * 764 ", "answer": "-13181", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3797", "question": "459043 + -974836 - -183101 * -249356 - -603031 ", "answer": "-45657245718", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3798", "question": "71472 * 5420 - 87613 - 41815 ", "answer": "387248812", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3799", "question": "291330 + -705628 - 370290 - 508513 + -832964 ", "answer": "-2126065", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3800", "question": "632 * -469 - 220 - 940 ", "answer": "-297568", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3801", "question": "706 + 386 - 609 + 493 ", "answer": "976", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3802", "question": "-369049 + -882594 - 777020 ", "answer": "-2028663", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3803", "question": "-667 - 213 ", "answer": "-880", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3804", "question": "-867526 + 295419 + 926705 + -377598 + -789234 ", "answer": "-812234", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3805", "question": "355895 + -860267 * -692803 + 535009 ", "answer": "595996449305", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3806", "question": "-62641 * 26005 * -36675 * -13892 ", "answer": "-829947149074165500", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3807", "question": "374 * -24 + -904 ", "answer": "-9880", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3808", "question": "88806 * -15917 ", "answer": "-1413525102", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3809", "question": "55 * -39 + 8 - -38 ", "answer": "-2099", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3810", "question": "51430 + 73821 + 86856 ", "answer": "212107", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3811", "question": "-55077 * -20037 + 47925 ", "answer": "1103625774", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3812", "question": "312 + 263 * 511 + 5 * 905 ", "answer": "139230", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3813", "question": "8461 + 4097 - -2045 + -7657 ", "answer": "6946", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3814", "question": "3 - -7 - -91 + 95 * -96 ", "answer": "-9019", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3815", "question": "81476 - 86521 + -56338 * -19190 - 54665 ", "answer": "1081066510", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3816", "question": "-20878 - 45462 - 48482 - -65726 + 708 ", "answer": "-48388", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3817", "question": "-8 - -15 - -92 * 72 ", "answer": "6631", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3818", "question": "777 * -2469 + -6300 + 7530 ", "answer": "-1917183", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3819", "question": "887911 - -724201 + -992821 ", "answer": "619291", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3820", "question": "923266 + -658569 - -534747 * 216281 * 196237 ", "answer": "22695911099006656", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3821", "question": "251 - 93 ", "answer": "158", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3822", "question": "-162836 + -580730 ", "answer": "-743566", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3823", "question": "-77067 + 20340 + 14511 + -25220 ", "answer": "-67436", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3824", "question": "-56801 * -36578 * -13096 - -59235 * 58233 ", "answer": "-27205677312133", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3825", "question": "-1431 - 120 + -9823 * 8526 - -358 ", "answer": "-83752091", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3826", "question": "5953 + 3543 ", "answer": "9496", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3827", "question": "-8791 - 1525 - -9821 + -1527 ", "answer": "-2022", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3828", "question": "440482 + 659988 ", "answer": "1100470", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3829", "question": "4661 * 3506 - -2197 - -3450 + 2463 ", "answer": "16349576", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3830", "question": "72 * 19 ", "answer": "1368", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3831", "question": "4375 * 909 - -2661 + 9019 ", "answer": "3988555", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3832", "question": "24 + -73 * -98 * 17 ", "answer": "121642", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3833", "question": "17829 * 80377 * -53684 + -99856 - 19535 ", "answer": "-76931401776963", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3834", "question": "-875996 * 780646 ", "answer": "-683842773416", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3835", "question": "85891 - 60418 * -48125 * 53554 - -30110 ", "answer": "155714480768501", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3836", "question": "66300 + 520991 ", "answer": "587291", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3837", "question": "151 + -991 * 605 ", "answer": "-599404", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3838", "question": "36 - 30 * -91 ", "answer": "2766", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3839", "question": "447 * -673 - -78 ", "answer": "-300753", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3840", "question": "498 + 767 - -563 ", "answer": "1828", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3841", "question": "4285 + -28115 ", "answer": "-23830", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3842", "question": "22 * 21 + -139 ", "answer": "323", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3843", "question": "47485 + -67124 + 64066 + 42636 ", "answer": "87063", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3844", "question": "4947 + -6540 ", "answer": "-1593", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3845", "question": "740 - -883 - -986 ", "answer": "2609", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3846", "question": "844 + 294 * -665 ", "answer": "-194666", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3847", "question": "-74 * -86 * -18 ", "answer": "-114552", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3848", "question": "-8077 + -16276 ", "answer": "-24353", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3849", "question": "84 + 54 * 73 + -34 * 30 ", "answer": "3006", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3850", "question": "-74613 - -73024 - 13586 ", "answer": "-15175", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3851", "question": "-5406 - -8487 ", "answer": "3081", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3852", "question": "638 * -193 ", "answer": "-123134", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3853", "question": "332793 * 567946 ", "answer": "189008453178", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3854", "question": "390 - -144 + 698 ", "answer": "1232", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3855", "question": "-8089 * 2998 ", "answer": "-24250822", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3856", "question": "3730 * 6057 * 481 + -1852 - 8193 ", "answer": "10867035365", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3857", "question": "770036 - -603271 + -492597 ", "answer": "880710", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3858", "question": "-70644 + -13724 ", "answer": "-84368", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3859", "question": "-5 + 18 + 54 - -87 * 19 ", "answer": "1720", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3860", "question": "-403336 - 986360 - -889984 ", "answer": "-499712", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3861", "question": "834590 * 58158 ", "answer": "48538085220", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3862", "question": "-12 + 525 ", "answer": "513", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3863", "question": "-499 - 682 * 935 + 750 ", "answer": "-637419", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3864", "question": "751 - 923 + -367 - 827 ", "answer": "-1366", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3865", "question": "-341 + -103 * -303 ", "answer": "30868", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3866", "question": "2809 + 519 * -7716 ", "answer": "-4001795", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3867", "question": "12095 + 9792 * 19503 * -97106 ", "answer": "-18544660637761", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3868", "question": "-410303 + -403980 ", "answer": "-814283", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3869", "question": "-884 - 837 ", "answer": "-1721", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3870", "question": "-8857 - -7809 + -8459 + -2749 ", "answer": "-12256", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3871", "question": "53 * 1 - 59 ", "answer": "-6", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3872", "question": "-95984 * -888579 * 726814 - -806383 ", "answer": "61989505795665487", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3873", "question": "-386 + -308 - 714 + -420 ", "answer": "-1828", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3874", "question": "76 * -93 ", "answer": "-7068", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3875", "question": "8921 + -2257 - 7402 + -7614 - -1217 ", "answer": "-7135", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3876", "question": "-7007 - 3287 + 889 ", "answer": "-9405", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3877", "question": "-33128 - -22226 ", "answer": "-10902", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3878", "question": "-39940 + 72539 - -37585 * -74324 ", "answer": "-2793434941", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3879", "question": "-599373 * -407018 + 254819 * -721485 + 163614 ", "answer": "60107677113", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3880", "question": "7704 + -6011 + 8589 - -2035 ", "answer": "12317", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3881", "question": "44598 + -75098 * -90367 + 21195 ", "answer": "6786446759", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3882", "question": "14113 + -97650 * -38259 ", "answer": "3736005463", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3883", "question": "-83 + -69 + 93 * -92 ", "answer": "-8708", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3884", "question": "-17994 + 64247 + 47220 ", "answer": "93473", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3885", "question": "-97 * -76 - -68 + 38 * 95 ", "answer": "11050", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3886", "question": "156 * -90 * -667 * -151 ", "answer": "-1414066680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3887", "question": "-407 + -54 + -743 * -350 ", "answer": "259589", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3888", "question": "293 * 428 * 365 * 55 ", "answer": "2517485300", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3889", "question": "433 + 970 + 23 * -640 + 861 ", "answer": "-12456", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3890", "question": "69 - 810 - 268 - 796 + -678 ", "answer": "-2483", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3891", "question": "-74312 + 91054 ", "answer": "16742", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3892", "question": "-63529 + -95954 ", "answer": "-159483", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3893", "question": "55659 + 250260 * 396503 ", "answer": "99228896439", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3894", "question": "-60620 - -17797 - -14087 * -1958 ", "answer": "-27625169", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3895", "question": "374328 * 997650 + -337460 ", "answer": "373447991740", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3896", "question": "18513 * 33015 + -78496 ", "answer": "611128199", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3897", "question": "8772 - 5711 + -6585 * -6699 - -4113 ", "answer": "44120089", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3898", "question": "4864 + 4277 - 8610 ", "answer": "531", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3899", "question": "283740 + -546583 + 917731 * -363841 - -717749 ", "answer": "-333907709865", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3900", "question": "-1728 * 1782 ", "answer": "-3079296", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3901", "question": "161377 - 847330 ", "answer": "-685953", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3902", "question": "670 - 832 + 521 ", "answer": "359", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3903", "question": "730707 + -252346 - 120493 ", "answer": "357868", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3904", "question": "543 * 233 ", "answer": "126519", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3905", "question": "-573 - 244 * -507 ", "answer": "123135", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3906", "question": "-94 * 34 - -99 - 2 ", "answer": "-3099", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3907", "question": "-38 * -7 ", "answer": "266", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3908", "question": "8052 + -7370 * 3286 + 4199 * 4981 ", "answer": "-3294549", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3909", "question": "23346 * -42587 * -8991 - -62882 ", "answer": "8939176855964", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3910", "question": "109 * 946 + 881 ", "answer": "103995", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3911", "question": "967559 + -265673 + 198919 - 845786 ", "answer": "55019", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3912", "question": "-1426 - -6638 ", "answer": "5212", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3913", "question": "548548 + 399442 + -95400 ", "answer": "852590", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3914", "question": "57069 - -85463 * -59651 - 79665 ", "answer": "-5097976009", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3915", "question": "746 - 704 + 85 + 15 ", "answer": "142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3916", "question": "-687 - -374 * 207 + 688 * -817 ", "answer": "-485365", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3917", "question": "437 - 495 ", "answer": "-58", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3918", "question": "5624 - 2041 * 1497 * 2670 + -8013 ", "answer": "-8157858979", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3919", "question": "-52423 + 5562 - 46403 * -5037 + -17619 ", "answer": "233667431", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3920", "question": "46323 - -83363 ", "answer": "129686", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3921", "question": "63650 * 70871 * -87909 * 2044 - -74449 ", "answer": "-810552594063068951", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3922", "question": "-656 * -778 - 917 - 773 ", "answer": "508678", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3923", "question": "-1519 + -7184 - -75569 ", "answer": "66866", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3924", "question": "83962 * -18390 + 34642 - 38088 + -26911 ", "answer": "-1544091537", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3925", "question": "2350 - -2380 + -4443 + -6656 * -2616 ", "answer": "17412383", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3926", "question": "35816 * -69814 - -99352 - -64853 ", "answer": "-2500294019", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3927", "question": "-238924 * -733528 + 530274 ", "answer": "175257974146", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3928", "question": "1959 + 7250 ", "answer": "9209", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3929", "question": "95144 * -14863 * -72844 * -95579 ", "answer": "-9845644528209515872", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3930", "question": "13 + 37 + 33 * 20 ", "answer": "710", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3931", "question": "-87495 + 3580 * 75442 ", "answer": "269994865", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3932", "question": "705 - 952 - -430 - 540 ", "answer": "-357", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3933", "question": "-460739 * -704449 - 965848 ", "answer": "324566161963", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3934", "question": "-683921 - 720923 ", "answer": "-1404844", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3935", "question": "2482 - 1011 ", "answer": "1471", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3936", "question": "-61 + -19 - 71 ", "answer": "-151", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3937", "question": "60 - 82 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3938", "question": "-306 - -729 - -390 * 222 ", "answer": "87003", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3939", "question": "-89330 + -38920 ", "answer": "-128250", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3940", "question": "53 + -851 * 995 + -687 ", "answer": "-847379", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3941", "question": "-2938 * -8311 ", "answer": "24417718", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3942", "question": "-942 + -202 + 642 - 997 ", "answer": "-1499", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3943", "question": "84817 * 27398 - -14039 ", "answer": "2323830205", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3944", "question": "-695 + 602 - -264 - -346 + 373 ", "answer": "890", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3945", "question": "-3806 - 7152 * 2709 + 319 * -3336 ", "answer": "-20442758", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3946", "question": "-308 - 33 - -763 ", "answer": "422", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3947", "question": "-250 - -833 - -630 - 832 * -449 ", "answer": "374781", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3948", "question": "-930129 + -202007 ", "answer": "-1132136", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3949", "question": "7501 - 51694 + 15392 - -13282 ", "answer": "-15519", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3950", "question": "-614060 * -121793 + 955497 ", "answer": "74789165077", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3951", "question": "9726 - -9657 * -1612 - 2125 ", "answer": "-15559483", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3952", "question": "-394 * -40176 + -76856 - -96617 + 60892 ", "answer": "15909997", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3953", "question": "128 - -555 * 746 - 6 * -160 ", "answer": "415118", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3954", "question": "15 * 46 + 7 + 56 ", "answer": "753", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3955", "question": "432 - -810 - -127 ", "answer": "1369", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3956", "question": "-3975 * 4563 + -7018 ", "answer": "-18144943", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3957", "question": "598 - 374 - -48 - -124 + 696 ", "answer": "1092", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3958", "question": "-52803 * 88197 + -72613 * -59724 + 94902 ", "answer": "-320232477", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3959", "question": "623 + -4467 + 7729 - 3668 ", "answer": "217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3960", "question": "719310 + 398319 ", "answer": "1117629", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3961", "question": "-43 + -17 * -79 + -94 - 4 ", "answer": "1202", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3962", "question": "1636 + -7617 ", "answer": "-5981", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3963", "question": "239584 * -471237 + -66848 - -103279 - -902314 ", "answer": "-112899906663", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3964", "question": "871 + 667 + 692 + -45 * -45 ", "answer": "4255", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3965", "question": "487153 * -509421 * -535300 - 812756 ", "answer": "132843242890666144", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3966", "question": "74011 + -19361 - 93654 - 71035 * 57165 ", "answer": "-4060754779", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3967", "question": "34 + -45 ", "answer": "-11", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3968", "question": "3244 * 3243 - 515 ", "answer": "10519777", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3969", "question": "122 + 282 - -599 ", "answer": "1003", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3970", "question": "-9732 * 5430 * 9877 * -8598 ", "answer": "4487706277482960", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3971", "question": "1836 - -2007 ", "answer": "3843", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3972", "question": "46 * 81 * 28 + 84 ", "answer": "104412", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3973", "question": "-98 * -9 - -35 + 0 ", "answer": "917", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3974", "question": "-26230 - 34872 + -29291 * 38906 + -43808 ", "answer": "-1139700556", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3975", "question": "-879438 - -670461 ", "answer": "-208977", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3976", "question": "12 - 93 + -10 - -34 ", "answer": "-57", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3977", "question": "8141 - 83398 * -45758 + 34821 ", "answer": "3816168646", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3978", "question": "-6480 - 9751 - 3275 - 5982 - -5993 ", "answer": "-19495", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3979", "question": "52 - -16 ", "answer": "68", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3980", "question": "99201 * -70243 - 73030 + -44242 + 3971 ", "answer": "-6968289144", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3981", "question": "20300 - -59961 - -95623 ", "answer": "175884", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3982", "question": "6862 - 8670 + -139 ", "answer": "-1947", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3983", "question": "46272 + -743915 + 584694 ", "answer": "-112949", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3984", "question": "352 - -508 + -941 ", "answer": "-81", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3985", "question": "-95 - 43 * 2 * -21 ", "answer": "1711", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3986", "question": "-46999 * -61702 * -39450 * -84722 ", "answer": "9692394130763104200", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3987", "question": "-632 * -674 - 369 ", "answer": "425599", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3988", "question": "-40804 - -94852 * -80336 ", "answer": "-7620071076", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3989", "question": "-31 * -3 * 33 ", "answer": "3069", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3990", "question": "-80719 + 14629 ", "answer": "-66090", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "3991", "question": "406237 + -482094 + -791394 ", "answer": "-867251", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3992", "question": "-66 + 6309 ", "answer": "6243", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3993", "question": "-34 - -36 - 53 + -17 ", "answer": "-68", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3994", "question": "-425 - -131 * -496 ", "answer": "-65401", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3995", "question": "-12 - 78 + -17 ", "answer": "-107", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "3996", "question": "881170 * 960939 + -844437 * -932543 * 628277 ", "answer": "494752531743648237", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "3997", "question": "3525 - 1716 ", "answer": "1809", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "3998", "question": "-888 + 187 * 101 * -615 * -261 ", "answer": "3031645917", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "3999", "question": "-232 - 784 * 178 ", "answer": "-139784", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4000", "question": "65258 + -6756 ", "answer": "58502", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4001", "question": "-341 - 52 ", "answer": "-393", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4002", "question": "-21 * -67 - 25 ", "answer": "1382", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4003", "question": "519 * 35 ", "answer": "18165", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4004", "question": "-702606 - -684280 + -602225 ", "answer": "-620551", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4005", "question": "-22 + 49 - 1 ", "answer": "26", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4006", "question": "94449 + -32988 * -43939 * 85948 - 57687 ", "answer": "124578165082698", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4007", "question": "-6077 * -4164 * -2260 ", "answer": "-57188459280", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4008", "question": "-28985 * 139229 * 440725 * -496379 - 308190 ", "answer": "882844254102669139685", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4009", "question": "375864 + 641324 + -741889 + 8462 + -277107 ", "answer": "6654", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4010", "question": "28053 * 25295 ", "answer": "709600635", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4011", "question": "27292 - -71523 ", "answer": "98815", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4012", "question": "-637 * 991 - -20 + 878 + 654 ", "answer": "-629715", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4013", "question": "-462866 + -613252 - -191332 + -294822 + -412887 ", "answer": "-1592495", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4014", "question": "76 - 93 + -48 + 77 - -37 ", "answer": "49", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4015", "question": "-92110 * 9252 + -64545 ", "answer": "-852266265", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4016", "question": "-460309 * -552607 + 657059 + 528546 ", "answer": "254371161168", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4017", "question": "45 + 40 - -86 + -95 ", "answer": "76", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4018", "question": "20 - -62 * 16 - -30 + 48 ", "answer": "1090", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4019", "question": "-966360 - 33577 * -549156 ", "answer": "18438044652", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4020", "question": "7550 * 1321 - -1321 ", "answer": "9974871", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4021", "question": "8548 + -569 ", "answer": "7979", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4022", "question": "-3943 + -6136 * -2853 ", "answer": "17502065", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4023", "question": "66518 + 65633 * -583923 ", "answer": "-38324551741", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4024", "question": "7984 + 55969 + -1090 ", "answer": "62863", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4025", "question": "-299 - -471 - -447 - -521 ", "answer": "1140", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4026", "question": "-95933 - -52747 ", "answer": "-43186", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4027", "question": "-4958 + -6421 ", "answer": "-11379", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4028", "question": "-28 + 836 ", "answer": "808", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4029", "question": "160 + 3588 + -7182 + -8028 ", "answer": "-11462", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4030", "question": "-54956 - -73334 * 21714 ", "answer": "1592319520", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4031", "question": "85868 + 66317 * 99361 * -53367 ", "answer": "-351652423776511", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4032", "question": "593533 + 798681 + -490585 ", "answer": "901629", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4033", "question": "-813 * 747 ", "answer": "-607311", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4034", "question": "-57991 + 90104 * 39094 ", "answer": "3522467785", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4035", "question": "-575 - -914 ", "answer": "339", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4036", "question": "-619204 + -786287 + 194433 ", "answer": "-1211058", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4037", "question": "650 * 119 * -202 - 632 ", "answer": "-15625332", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4038", "question": "478 * 611 + -744 ", "answer": "291314", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4039", "question": "67 - 82 * -79 + 79 + -68 ", "answer": "6556", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4040", "question": "-8127 + -5356 ", "answer": "-13483", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4041", "question": "-4 - -66 + -3 + 22 - 38 ", "answer": "43", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4042", "question": "-85 - 70 + 29 + 95 ", "answer": "-31", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4043", "question": "199557 + 858745 - -25278 - 663813 ", "answer": "419767", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4044", "question": "92 * -6323 - 816 + -6320 ", "answer": "-588852", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4045", "question": "70 * 66 ", "answer": "4620", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4046", "question": "-568 + 41 + -101 * 152 - -256 ", "answer": "-15623", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4047", "question": "-90985 - -71011 + -45978 ", "answer": "-65952", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4048", "question": "-86787 * 65115 ", "answer": "-5651135505", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4049", "question": "4861 + -1221 - 9398 - -7630 - 6417 ", "answer": "-4545", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4050", "question": "50 - -14 * -69 - -97 ", "answer": "-819", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4051", "question": "446 - -985 + 423 * -710 - 878 ", "answer": "-299777", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4052", "question": "-97 + -6771 + 8762 * -4339 + -1378 ", "answer": "-38026564", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4053", "question": "62651 + -180 - 43958 + -16330 - -94180 ", "answer": "96363", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4054", "question": "552432 - 448866 * 449301 - -118249 + 999311 ", "answer": "-201674272674", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4055", "question": "180 - 96 - 823 * -648 - 451 ", "answer": "532937", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4056", "question": "29 * -61 + -73 + 68 + 54 ", "answer": "-1720", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4057", "question": "-27 + -98 * 69 * -68 ", "answer": "459789", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4058", "question": "96 * 8 * 7 - 86 ", "answer": "5290", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4059", "question": "21666 * -55509 + 7334 ", "answer": "-1202650660", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4060", "question": "-854 + 385 ", "answer": "-469", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4061", "question": "1115 + -9256 + -3229 ", "answer": "-11370", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4062", "question": "-3 * -1 + 70 ", "answer": "73", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4063", "question": "-75 * -162 + -658 ", "answer": "11492", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4064", "question": "636016 + 605146 + 992671 - 226281 ", "answer": "2007552", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4065", "question": "21435 + 72289 + 48246 + -77215 + -29971 ", "answer": "34784", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4066", "question": "-9999 - 585 ", "answer": "-10584", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4067", "question": "7 + 23 - 71 - -17 ", "answer": "-24", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4068", "question": "-637 - -876 - -760 * 857 - -767 ", "answer": "652326", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4069", "question": "529235 + 77982 * -687189 * -51527 + 225596 ", "answer": "2761248075611977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4070", "question": "-849 * -886 ", "answer": "752214", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4071", "question": "-962 - 878 - -653 - -317 - 496 ", "answer": "-1366", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4072", "question": "7915 - 9217 - -1519 * -9627 - -7921 ", "answer": "-14616794", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4073", "question": "687 + 4008 ", "answer": "4695", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4074", "question": "494 * -812 ", "answer": "-401128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4075", "question": "-43353 * -72418 - 77049 - -96898 * -10587 ", "answer": "2113601379", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4076", "question": "-25973 * 411345 - -559045 * 275036 * -172115 ", "answer": "-26463982903074985", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4077", "question": "-664880 + 340662 + 160481 - 374602 + 125716 ", "answer": "-412623", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4078", "question": "-386078 * 151329 ", "answer": "-58424797662", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4079", "question": "-7378 * 7558 ", "answer": "-55762924", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4080", "question": "-1298 + -7585 - -4244 ", "answer": "-4639", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4081", "question": "68 - 93 ", "answer": "-25", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4082", "question": "798749 + 823309 - -979129 * -403137 ", "answer": "-394721505615", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4083", "question": "83194 - 40673 * -96624 * -21649 - 61318 ", "answer": "-85080309150972", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4084", "question": "-721 * -692 - 383 - -120 ", "answer": "498669", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4085", "question": "-477 * 937 * -643 - -602 ", "answer": "287388809", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4086", "question": "-484 + -964 ", "answer": "-1448", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4087", "question": "-452486 - 757084 * 637569 + -703690 ", "answer": "-482694444972", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4088", "question": "831 - -770 + 339 + 263 - -819 ", "answer": "3022", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4089", "question": "93 * 78 + -52 ", "answer": "7202", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4090", "question": "150 + -915 + 315 * 896 ", "answer": "281475", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4091", "question": "-15 - -31 - -68 + 62 - 76 ", "answer": "70", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4092", "question": "-596276 - 582859 + -346135 ", "answer": "-1525270", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4093", "question": "-565 - -783 * -187 ", "answer": "-146986", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4094", "question": "4670 * 9848 * 5688 ", "answer": "261592030080", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4095", "question": "57261 - 44981 * 81122 ", "answer": "-3648891421", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4096", "question": "-151102 + 657951 + 975486 * 638950 ", "answer": "623287286549", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4097", "question": "999467 * -734433 + -271515 ", "answer": "-734041818726", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4098", "question": "275488 * -740980 - -287167 ", "answer": "-204130811073", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4099", "question": "884 + -258 * 847 * -177 * 726 ", "answer": "28081028936", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4100", "question": "866921 * -750638 + 599069 - 808388 - 460896 ", "answer": "-650744515813", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4101", "question": "69762 * 37102 - 77210 * -59542 - 43703 ", "answer": "7185503841", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4102", "question": "258283 - -8298 + 607055 + 771341 - 343899 ", "answer": "1301078", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4103", "question": "98 - 52 + 58 ", "answer": "104", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4104", "question": "69 - 41 + -98 ", "answer": "-70", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4105", "question": "66077 - -96771 - 83907 ", "answer": "78941", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4106", "question": "3 - -23 * -88 * -4 - 39 ", "answer": "8060", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4107", "question": "-984186 - 2901 * 22767 - -957915 ", "answer": "-66073338", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4108", "question": "-977770 + -154074 ", "answer": "-1131844", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4109", "question": "-517 + 935 - 736 + 767 ", "answer": "449", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4110", "question": "-725 * 6 - -558 + 512 ", "answer": "-3280", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4111", "question": "-5489 + -3266 * -4957 - -2878 - -8455 ", "answer": "16195406", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4112", "question": "9533 * 17343 + -42537 + -72848 * -39769 ", "answer": "3062380394", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4113", "question": "172935 * 555690 + -39207 ", "answer": "96098210943", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4114", "question": "-71 * -91 + 30 + -52 + -3 ", "answer": "6436", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4115", "question": "-452741 - 777917 - -645390 - -914114 ", "answer": "328846", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4116", "question": "-199 - -455 - -738 + -365 ", "answer": "629", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4117", "question": "887 - 386 + -900 + 598 ", "answer": "199", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4118", "question": "-88 + 896 - -367 - -512 - 583 ", "answer": "1104", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4119", "question": "-7 - -25 ", "answer": "18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4120", "question": "921317 + -413427 * 519024 + -175139 + 135900 ", "answer": "-214577653170", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4121", "question": "14 + 9 * -13 ", "answer": "-103", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4122", "question": "959513 + 477975 + -310227 * -329670 * -369553 ", "answer": "-37795122158677282", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4123", "question": "47008 + -65857 + 72417 - -1161 ", "answer": "54729", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4124", "question": "-608331 * -373895 ", "answer": "227451919245", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4125", "question": "7816 + -4224 - 3904 ", "answer": "-312", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4126", "question": "417262 - 105550 * 816024 - 836605 ", "answer": "-86131752543", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4127", "question": "-12 * 93 - -69 + -53 ", "answer": "-1100", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4128", "question": "160 - 363 * 184 ", "answer": "-66632", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4129", "question": "45322 * -3110 * -98608 + -8308 ", "answer": "13898937615052", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4130", "question": "-67223 - 16709 * 6698 * -7382 ", "answer": "826170355701", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4131", "question": "173 + 858 - -120 ", "answer": "1151", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4132", "question": "-1137 + -4453 * -6918 - -7772 ", "answer": "30812489", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4133", "question": "-79085 - -13411 * -61454 * -93781 ", "answer": "77290510805829", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4134", "question": "92 * 93 + -90 + 19 + 24 ", "answer": "8509", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4135", "question": "4674 + -8961 - 1371 - 999 ", "answer": "-6657", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4136", "question": "888272 + 191271 ", "answer": "1079543", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4137", "question": "520 - 424 + -709 ", "answer": "-613", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4138", "question": "13 - 614 + -338 ", "answer": "-939", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4139", "question": "-704 + -231 ", "answer": "-935", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4140", "question": "729 * -48 + -213 * -522 ", "answer": "76194", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4141", "question": "6152 + -456 - -77143 - 55403 ", "answer": "27436", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4142", "question": "7612 - 5482 + -5887 + 752 - -1614 ", "answer": "-1391", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4143", "question": "557 * -951 + -145 - -698 * 497 ", "answer": "-182946", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4144", "question": "-58 + 75 ", "answer": "17", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4145", "question": "78 * 38 + -49 ", "answer": "2915", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4146", "question": "-82643 + -61413 - -47908 ", "answer": "-96148", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4147", "question": "84 - 95 - 98 * -47 + 24 ", "answer": "4619", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4148", "question": "-719063 * 887855 ", "answer": "-638423679865", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4149", "question": "-5998 * 2832 - 6594 ", "answer": "-16992930", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4150", "question": "-143 + 671 * -471 - 652 + 152 ", "answer": "-316684", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4151", "question": "-248854 * -602216 - 887087 * -189163 * 848842 ", "answer": "142439265241496866", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4152", "question": "570 - 256 * 741 - 657 ", "answer": "-189783", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4153", "question": "572 * 548 ", "answer": "313456", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4154", "question": "-8481 - -5697 - 7243 - 741 + 61 ", "answer": "-10707", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4155", "question": "917 + -888 - -718 + 787 ", "answer": "1534", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4156", "question": "-302 - -856 * 591 ", "answer": "505594", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4157", "question": "-3651 * -7741 ", "answer": "28262391", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4158", "question": "-1358 - 2034 - -2924 - -5376 - 1693 ", "answer": "3215", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4159", "question": "6434 + 6619 ", "answer": "13053", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4160", "question": "-757 * -465 ", "answer": "352005", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4161", "question": "-463 + -101 * -906 ", "answer": "91043", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4162", "question": "-14329 - 76103 ", "answer": "-90432", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4163", "question": "-948 + -530 ", "answer": "-1478", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4164", "question": "23529 - 69100 * -40061 + 15960 * 95015 ", "answer": "4284678029", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4165", "question": "-8484 * -1018 + 5000 ", "answer": "8641712", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4166", "question": "46213 * -80645 - -32155 + -63757 ", "answer": "-3726878987", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4167", "question": "379 - 143 - -504 + -191 ", "answer": "549", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4168", "question": "-409 + -453 ", "answer": "-862", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4169", "question": "-5324 + -4923 ", "answer": "-10247", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4170", "question": "4110 - 8960 ", "answer": "-4850", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4171", "question": "16439 - -61651 * 92192 - 28997 ", "answer": "5683716434", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4172", "question": "2616 + -4149 + -6132 - 9079 * 3863 ", "answer": "-35079842", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4173", "question": "-71 - -49 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4174", "question": "694 * -2125 * 1701 ", "answer": "-2508549750", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4175", "question": "50989 - 29033 * 51207 ", "answer": "-1486641842", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4176", "question": "-21 + -72 - -42 + 4 ", "answer": "-47", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4177", "question": "15440 + -69499 - 38465 ", "answer": "-92524", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4178", "question": "-10 + -68 + 69 ", "answer": "-9", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4179", "question": "-52463 + 174091 * 916032 ", "answer": "159472874449", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4180", "question": "119 - -523 ", "answer": "642", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4181", "question": "52 * -4 ", "answer": "-208", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4182", "question": "3734 + 7321 + -536 * -337 ", "answer": "191687", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4183", "question": "65063 - -31122 + -11551 - -79791 * 34501 ", "answer": "2752953925", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4184", "question": "76 + 98 + 9 * -20 ", "answer": "-6", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4185", "question": "16928 + -23443 ", "answer": "-6515", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4186", "question": "516261 * -487216 ", "answer": "-251530619376", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4187", "question": "4004 - 2119 ", "answer": "1885", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4188", "question": "-25343 + 63626 ", "answer": "38283", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4189", "question": "5 - -50 ", "answer": "55", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4190", "question": "68518 + 41624 ", "answer": "110142", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4191", "question": "-96263 * 55640 + -49669 + 17707 - -10434 ", "answer": "-5356094848", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4192", "question": "81696 - -51529 - -44500 * -4869 ", "answer": "-216537275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4193", "question": "857145 + -72570 + 158908 * -827404 ", "answer": "-131480330257", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4194", "question": "-69 * -64 - -56 ", "answer": "4472", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4195", "question": "28340 - 96587 - 51734 * 9719 ", "answer": "-502870993", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4196", "question": "837345 * -377799 * 384165 * -469733 + 209216 ", "answer": "57086590068005599098191", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4197", "question": "-579 + 5390 ", "answer": "4811", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4198", "question": "-38 - 76 - 48 + 97 * 30 ", "answer": "2748", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4199", "question": "131 - 615 + -978 * -65 - -359 ", "answer": "63445", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4200", "question": "4623 * -6658 * -8550 - -8140 ", "answer": "263168443840", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4201", "question": "-823683 + -696038 * -18887 + 932696 + -264225 ", "answer": "13145914494", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4202", "question": "8176 + -3623 + 5326 - 5655 ", "answer": "4224", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4203", "question": "157090 * 691829 - -659211 + -616537 - -629657 ", "answer": "108680089941", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4204", "question": "-78 + 100 + -70 - 15 - 44 ", "answer": "-107", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4205", "question": "-60847 - -10666 - -65127 * 53228 * 71272 ", "answer": "247070086573851", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4206", "question": "-563 * -533 * -414 ", "answer": "-124232706", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4207", "question": "-819985 * 416371 - 578652 - 989427 * -208166 ", "answer": "-135453492205", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4208", "question": "-34 * -92 ", "answer": "3128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4209", "question": "4551 * 5616 ", "answer": "25558416", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4210", "question": "-94 - -15 - 58 - -96 ", "answer": "-41", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4211", "question": "556843 + 779220 * 785949 - 362182 - -707284 ", "answer": "612428081725", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4212", "question": "-852443 - 514670 * 583269 ", "answer": "-300191908673", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4213", "question": "15 + -59 * 42 ", "answer": "-2463", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4214", "question": "-213 - 23 ", "answer": "-236", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4215", "question": "2508 - -949 * 782 ", "answer": "744626", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4216", "question": "1997 * 8765 ", "answer": "17503705", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4217", "question": "-4041 - 31908 - 47798 + 87299 ", "answer": "3552", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4218", "question": "-74 - -67 ", "answer": "-7", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4219", "question": "-4558 - -5333 - -7323 + 4704 ", "answer": "12802", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4220", "question": "353 + -2432 * -5804 + -224 + 565 ", "answer": "14116022", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4221", "question": "8314 * -9430 * 6541 * 3946 ", "answer": "-2023591949401720", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4222", "question": "96 * -42 + -72 ", "answer": "-4104", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4223", "question": "35380 * 45343 + 96934 ", "answer": "1604332274", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4224", "question": "-53736 * 31895 - 93473 + -17605 * 10529 ", "answer": "-1899366238", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4225", "question": "-34600 - 1420 - 79773 * 15106 + -86830 ", "answer": "-1205173788", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4226", "question": "69681 - -41885 * 58759 + 77870 ", "answer": "2461268266", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4227", "question": "6583 - 8145 - 2315 - -6805 * 4100 ", "answer": "27896623", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4228", "question": "-8970 * 1090 - -6569 + 1983 + -4699 ", "answer": "-9773447", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4229", "question": "-9043 + 1299 ", "answer": "-7744", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4230", "question": "-3158 - -8846 ", "answer": "5688", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4231", "question": "9622 * -5486 ", "answer": "-52786292", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4232", "question": "-4843 * -4084 ", "answer": "19778812", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4233", "question": "-65752 * -68448 ", "answer": "4500592896", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4234", "question": "-66717 * -58494 + -31561 * 21850 * 50424 ", "answer": "-34768883684202", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4235", "question": "-8651 - -7349 - -1111 + -1769 + 7488 ", "answer": "5528", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4236", "question": "-67195 - -3995 * 51072 - 48989 ", "answer": "203916456", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4237", "question": "-15 + -32 * -7 ", "answer": "209", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4238", "question": "4112 + -2304 ", "answer": "1808", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4239", "question": "129891 - 711613 ", "answer": "-581722", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4240", "question": "-1127 + -8346 * 8657 * 2621 * -1681 ", "answer": "318332171849995", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4241", "question": "-198905 * 932801 + -168583 - 782686 + 39944 ", "answer": "-185539694230", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4242", "question": "1522 - -5968 * -9797 - -4570 * 261 ", "answer": "-57274204", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4243", "question": "-3358 * -3111 + 7096 ", "answer": "10453834", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4244", "question": "184 + -581 ", "answer": "-397", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4245", "question": "10770 + -86182 + 7465 - -5102 ", "answer": "-62845", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4246", "question": "-945 + 149 ", "answer": "-796", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4247", "question": "7754 - -6711 * 5546 + 35 ", "answer": "37226995", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4248", "question": "-161899 + -778808 - 687283 ", "answer": "-1627990", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4249", "question": "-45166 * 3015 + -61669 * -94347 + -85701 ", "answer": "5682023952", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4250", "question": "-11 - -27 ", "answer": "16", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4251", "question": "636 - -968 + 404 ", "answer": "2008", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4252", "question": "41533 * 39239 * -44236 * 99608 * 45150 ", "answer": "-324219444349649868398400", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4253", "question": "-590 + 882 + 489 - 992 ", "answer": "-211", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4254", "question": "-88 * 94 ", "answer": "-8272", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4255", "question": "84 - -98 + -31 - 57 ", "answer": "94", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4256", "question": "843 - 148 + 203 * 723 * 894 ", "answer": "131212181", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4257", "question": "-9895 - 8477 - 6095 ", "answer": "-24467", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4258", "question": "48 - -81 + -52 * 45 ", "answer": "-2211", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4259", "question": "-60 - -1 + 13 - 52 * -63 ", "answer": "3230", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4260", "question": "-6712 + -3843 * -1992 ", "answer": "7648544", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4261", "question": "192 + -302 * -436 * -152 + 466 ", "answer": "-20013486", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4262", "question": "493550 - 134466 * 849488 ", "answer": "-114226759858", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4263", "question": "-245722 + -115018 + -376079 * -98698 ", "answer": "37117884402", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4264", "question": "-9 * -7 * -5 ", "answer": "-315", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 1}
{"id": "4265", "question": "28 + -87 ", "answer": "-59", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4266", "question": "35 + 96 + -24 ", "answer": "107", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4267", "question": "-82135 - -13118 * -28331 ", "answer": "-371728193", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4268", "question": "37 + -88 - -29 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4269", "question": "87 + -1 - -41 ", "answer": "127", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4270", "question": "2218 * 949 - -333 - 794 ", "answer": "2104421", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4271", "question": "24608 - 62351 * 27763 - -38689 ", "answer": "-1730987516", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4272", "question": "-50 - 3 * 85 * 52 ", "answer": "-13310", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4273", "question": "13 - -73 * 71 - 82 - 86 ", "answer": "5028", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4274", "question": "642168 - -315556 - 508799 ", "answer": "448925", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4275", "question": "493238 * 121497 - -356197 + 582036 ", "answer": "59927875519", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4276", "question": "-38778 - -87807 ", "answer": "49029", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4277", "question": "-1961 + -4276 - -3212 ", "answer": "-3025", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4278", "question": "-5358 - 4795 ", "answer": "-10153", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4279", "question": "-880312 - 912052 - -727834 * -590317 ", "answer": "-429654575742", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4280", "question": "4739 - -15713 + -97056 * 47264 - -28267 ", "answer": "-4587206065", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4281", "question": "796501 * 653623 ", "answer": "520611373123", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4282", "question": "827 - 709 - 19 * 222 ", "answer": "-4100", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4283", "question": "-90371 * 88045 + 77040 ", "answer": "-7956637655", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4284", "question": "-25 + -92 ", "answer": "-117", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4285", "question": "509604 - 644684 ", "answer": "-135080", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4286", "question": "-17 * 76 + -32 ", "answer": "-1324", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4287", "question": "-928594 - 205555 ", "answer": "-1134149", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4288", "question": "47 * -83 ", "answer": "-3901", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4289", "question": "-781021 * -217540 - 197731 + 253974 ", "answer": "169903364583", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4290", "question": "-2764 + -6478 * -9372 ", "answer": "60709052", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4291", "question": "-985805 + 207122 + 180375 + -63480 ", "answer": "-661788", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4292", "question": "75 - -40 ", "answer": "115", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4293", "question": "29 - -96 ", "answer": "125", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4294", "question": "-337 + 892 - 215 * 248 * -999 ", "answer": "53267235", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4295", "question": "-713864 + -466301 - 673001 + 413336 ", "answer": "-1439830", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4296", "question": "-59 + 3 * 60 - -52 ", "answer": "173", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4297", "question": "-82284 * -84533 + -85643 ", "answer": "6955627729", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4298", "question": "59433 + -4523 * -87712 - -46801 + -97520 ", "answer": "396730090", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4299", "question": "-5838 * 6308 + 3895 * -9524 + 9890 ", "answer": "-73912194", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4300", "question": "-806 + 989 - -474 + 548 + -23 ", "answer": "1182", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4301", "question": "429721 * -300639 * 736880 ", "answer": "-95198184289896720", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4302", "question": "-954 - 558 + -645 + 496 - 113 ", "answer": "-1774", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4303", "question": "-817397 * -914503 * -448986 * -552701 * 345692 ", "answer": "64125468757850471833524997992", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4304", "question": "26553 * 32092 * -1372 ", "answer": "-1169134537872", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4305", "question": "939 + -861 + 340 - -642 + -220 ", "answer": "840", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4306", "question": "-43388 + 49426 ", "answer": "6038", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4307", "question": "72 - -63 ", "answer": "135", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4308", "question": "-4848 * 27129 * -57810 ", "answer": "7603251671520", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4309", "question": "993 - 217 + -217 + -891 ", "answer": "-332", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4310", "question": "51 + 3 + -20 + -52 ", "answer": "-18", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4311", "question": "1438 * -4156 * 6621 ", "answer": "-39569267688", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4312", "question": "430 + -455 * -209 ", "answer": "95525", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4313", "question": "-54 + -93 * -11 ", "answer": "969", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4314", "question": "551290 + 603476 - -205304 + -675169 ", "answer": "684901", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4315", "question": "-279 - 1075 * 7269 + -4222 + 9555 ", "answer": "-7809121", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4316", "question": "-612 + -704 - -295 * 437 * -976 ", "answer": "-125822356", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4317", "question": "94977 + -81162 ", "answer": "13815", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4318", "question": "-880851 + -351207 - -703586 + -898168 ", "answer": "-1426640", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4319", "question": "-599775 * 81530 * 977095 * -48955 - 693910 ", "answer": "2339050765206188474840", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4320", "question": "3721 * 4325 - 6524 + -6849 ", "answer": "16079952", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4321", "question": "6513 + -2426 * -6136 - 1272 ", "answer": "14891177", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4322", "question": "762 + 888 + 727 * 3 + -993 ", "answer": "2838", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4323", "question": "80 + -933 ", "answer": "-853", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4324", "question": "49407 * 9285 + -31285 + -95988 ", "answer": "458616722", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4325", "question": "74513 - 88761 - 90300 ", "answer": "-104548", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4326", "question": "845562 - 227546 + -579287 ", "answer": "38729", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4327", "question": "301423 * -339246 + -389410 + -61146 * 840675 ", "answer": "-153660850018", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4328", "question": "-799039 * -506629 + -585195 ", "answer": "404815744336", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4329", "question": "13016 - 20149 - -65736 ", "answer": "58603", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4330", "question": "292542 + -666024 - -849689 * -750082 ", "answer": "-637336797980", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4331", "question": "-84536 - 376678 + 394189 * -813186 ", "answer": "-320549437368", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4332", "question": "46072 * -68687 ", "answer": "-3164547464", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4333", "question": "-51973 * -5780 - 57559 - -90775 ", "answer": "300437156", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4334", "question": "-317567 + 370188 * 628572 ", "answer": "232689493969", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4335", "question": "9311 * -1917 - 5170 + -1797 + 3310 ", "answer": "-17852844", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4336", "question": "8170 - -8388 - -3116 - -4692 ", "answer": "24366", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4337", "question": "-390 * -111 + -269 - -749 ", "answer": "43770", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4338", "question": "-84 + -6324 + 176 + -5423 - -3576 ", "answer": "-8079", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4339", "question": "-42532 - 58602 ", "answer": "-101134", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4340", "question": "5701 - 1100 - 2383 ", "answer": "2218", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4341", "question": "-745768 - 135586 + -199049 ", "answer": "-1080403", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4342", "question": "38462 * 86158 ", "answer": "3313808996", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4343", "question": "-614 - 890 ", "answer": "-1504", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4344", "question": "2 * 56 + -15 - -58 + -96 ", "answer": "59", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4345", "question": "-942332 * 858025 * 967888 * -339601 ", "answer": "265765098669128324638400", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4346", "question": "-987 * 917 ", "answer": "-905079", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4347", "question": "-4443 - -55984 - -247569 ", "answer": "299110", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4348", "question": "-7420 - 9668 ", "answer": "-17088", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4349", "question": "-685369 - -653750 + 118680 - -735525 - 97938 ", "answer": "724648", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4350", "question": "11698 * -88586 ", "answer": "-1036279028", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4351", "question": "486 + 552 * 388 ", "answer": "214662", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4352", "question": "96493 + -25196 - 61296 ", "answer": "10001", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4353", "question": "-85 + -58 + 84 - 61 - 96 ", "answer": "-216", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4354", "question": "-3063 - -3561 + 1456 ", "answer": "1954", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4355", "question": "45572 * 75595 - -18284 ", "answer": "3445033624", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4356", "question": "29792 - 567113 + 791443 + -868447 * 979607 ", "answer": "-850736506207", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4357", "question": "7695 + 1242 - -1539 ", "answer": "10476", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4358", "question": "82 * 19 ", "answer": "1558", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4359", "question": "-429 - -589 - 582 * -92 + 777 ", "answer": "54481", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4360", "question": "-4118 - -6495 + -1299 ", "answer": "1078", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4361", "question": "-729 - -943 + 473 ", "answer": "687", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4362", "question": "-46329 - 76323 * -76332 ", "answer": "5825840907", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4363", "question": "-1653 * 7380 + -7746 - 820 + -6724 ", "answer": "-12214430", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4364", "question": "663080 + -132446 ", "answer": "530634", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4365", "question": "-939368 + 604163 ", "answer": "-335205", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4366", "question": "147778 * -151409 + -119300 - -293964 ", "answer": "-22374744538", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4367", "question": "-32 - 61 - 48 ", "answer": "-141", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4368", "question": "86898 + -59939 - -72938 ", "answer": "99897", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4369", "question": "-15 * -75 + 3 * 6 * -78 ", "answer": "-279", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4370", "question": "-36 - 34 - 42 + 40 - 26 ", "answer": "-98", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4371", "question": "16 - -100 * -82 * 62 - -86 ", "answer": "-508298", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4372", "question": "577267 + 837884 ", "answer": "1415151", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4373", "question": "-52 + -52 ", "answer": "-104", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4374", "question": "-97641 - 46330 - -80958 * 89184 - 28538 ", "answer": "7219985763", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4375", "question": "-946 + 425 * 679 ", "answer": "287629", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4376", "question": "5985 + -9635 * -2146 ", "answer": "20682695", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4377", "question": "-75 - -87 + -27 + -8 - -34 ", "answer": "11", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4378", "question": "1425 * -1589 + -6956 - 2566 + 6845 ", "answer": "-2267002", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4379", "question": "-43 - 23 + -46 ", "answer": "-112", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4380", "question": "-328948 + -410361 - -61498 ", "answer": "-677811", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4381", "question": "7127 + 2661 - 5433 * -5553 ", "answer": "30179237", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4382", "question": "-38 + -54 ", "answer": "-92", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4383", "question": "-99 + -64 ", "answer": "-163", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4384", "question": "630340 * -47706 * 949553 - -453345 - -359462 ", "answer": "-28554008300169313", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4385", "question": "346 * -965 - -201 * 287 - 13 ", "answer": "-276216", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4386", "question": "-315928 + -254564 - 868707 + -267274 ", "answer": "-1706473", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4387", "question": "65154 * 51915 ", "answer": "3382469910", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4388", "question": "35 * 70 - 77 ", "answer": "2373", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4389", "question": "62 - -46 - 63 + 46 ", "answer": "91", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4390", "question": "-3199 * 2884 + -6507 + 7478 - -6217 ", "answer": "-9218728", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4391", "question": "11 - 42 - -81 + 48 ", "answer": "98", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4392", "question": "22824 + -74213 + 76327 + 91380 ", "answer": "116318", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4393", "question": "-473249 - 489583 * 21358 * -498775 * 659663 ", "answer": "3440437828431695508801", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4394", "question": "-7980 * -35423 * 63908 ", "answer": "18065228410320", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4395", "question": "59 * 15 - 28 ", "answer": "857", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4396", "question": "485930 - 483462 - 891693 + -30444 * 601936 ", "answer": "-18326228809", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4397", "question": "969 * 828 + -622 - -2 * 176 ", "answer": "802062", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4398", "question": "-58749 - -55340 * -77653 ", "answer": "-4297375769", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4399", "question": "671 + -612 ", "answer": "59", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4400", "question": "27536 * -24801 - 3159 + -69986 * -42645 ", "answer": "2301629475", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4401", "question": "55 * 100 + -67 ", "answer": "5433", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4402", "question": "13438 * 91981 ", "answer": "1236040678", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4403", "question": "-424803 - 348143 + -28528 * -73403 + 662773 ", "answer": "2093930611", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4404", "question": "544336 * 858543 - 62787 ", "answer": "467335799661", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4405", "question": "-41148 - -31297 * 13957 ", "answer": "436771081", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4406", "question": "1095 + -5201 - 5738 * -8800 * -7664 ", "answer": "-386989085706", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4407", "question": "-649 * 286 * 783 + -125 ", "answer": "-145335887", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4408", "question": "60 * 90 * 95 ", "answer": "513000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4409", "question": "-567637 * 362773 + -2132 + -914231 * 404598 ", "answer": "-575819413671", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4410", "question": "88795 + 15986 + 93837 * 37857 * 91526 ", "answer": "325135800948315", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4411", "question": "-884 - 225 - 928 * 572 ", "answer": "-531925", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4412", "question": "-491588 - -206183 * 82588 - -290007 + -724267 ", "answer": "17027315756", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4413", "question": "498 + -430 * 597 ", "answer": "-256212", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4414", "question": "882401 - -287773 + -923697 * -365605 ", "answer": "337709411859", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4415", "question": "-7961 * 31953 ", "answer": "-254377833", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4416", "question": "89291 + 26356 * 24809 + -5486 + 41248 ", "answer": "653991057", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4417", "question": "-6309 + 9731 - 8038 ", "answer": "-4616", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4418", "question": "92921 - -16063 * -47639 - 30018 ", "answer": "-765162354", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4419", "question": "-7764 - -4180 * 7811 + 2666 ", "answer": "32644882", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4420", "question": "-2971 + 8374 - 5047 ", "answer": "356", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4421", "question": "-35261 + -25583 + 15477 ", "answer": "-45367", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4422", "question": "169 - -359 ", "answer": "528", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4423", "question": "62 - -88 ", "answer": "150", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4424", "question": "6124 + -5989 - 4666 + -8297 ", "answer": "-12828", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4425", "question": "-26 + -922 * -315 + 650 - 302 ", "answer": "290752", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4426", "question": "-6025 - -7920 - -4911 + 4298 - -1604 ", "answer": "12708", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4427", "question": "74 * -43 - 49 * 20 ", "answer": "-4162", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4428", "question": "403 * 494 * -56 + -671 + 284 ", "answer": "-11148979", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4429", "question": "-5955 * 7433 + -3019 ", "answer": "-44266534", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4430", "question": "-66 * 968 + 740 ", "answer": "-63148", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4431", "question": "-64 - -92 * -57 * 49 * 53 ", "answer": "-13618732", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4432", "question": "83 + -38 ", "answer": "45", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4433", "question": "906 - -765 * -315 ", "answer": "-240069", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4434", "question": "-217086 * -503124 ", "answer": "109221176664", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4435", "question": "19 * 53 + -8 ", "answer": "999", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4436", "question": "-587 + 735 ", "answer": "148", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4437", "question": "469397 * 735225 ", "answer": "345112409325", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4438", "question": "-746163 - 638161 * 401061 + 459790 * 797245 ", "answer": "110623043566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4439", "question": "-138 - -703 ", "answer": "565", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4440", "question": "-44753 - -70581 + -1164 - -16814 ", "answer": "41478", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4441", "question": "-5773 - 2015 ", "answer": "-7788", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4442", "question": "-609168 + -956564 + 627783 - 520186 + -266906 ", "answer": "-1725041", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4443", "question": "-22 + 83 ", "answer": "61", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4444", "question": "663 * -387 + 464 + -981 * -495 ", "answer": "229478", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4445", "question": "-25294 - 25907 - 76328 + 53210 - 39219 ", "answer": "-113538", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4446", "question": "-7661 * -7803 ", "answer": "59778783", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4447", "question": "-411 - -372 * -91 - 600 ", "answer": "-34863", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4448", "question": "76226 - 57071 - -20304 * 57654 - -37404 ", "answer": "1170663375", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4449", "question": "947 * -224 + -176 + 231 - -533 ", "answer": "-211540", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4450", "question": "-74 * -80 + -50 + 41 ", "answer": "5911", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4451", "question": "-131 * 942 ", "answer": "-123402", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4452", "question": "-285449 - -596258 * -337657 + -621265 ", "answer": "-201331594220", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4453", "question": "40 * -62 ", "answer": "-2480", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4454", "question": "28971 * 59975 * 66847 ", "answer": "116149050609075", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4455", "question": "-76 + 55 + -70 + 59 - -70 ", "answer": "38", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4456", "question": "-27 - -78 - 92 ", "answer": "-41", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4457", "question": "344 + 744 ", "answer": "1088", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4458", "question": "-7367 - -52985 * 73850 * -80253 * -86993 ", "answer": "27318007654384017883", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4459", "question": "2617 * 3957 * 802 * -8987 - 2873 ", "answer": "-74637809125079", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4460", "question": "193 * 506 * 606 - 794 ", "answer": "59179954", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4461", "question": "-4121 * -9411 ", "answer": "38782731", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4462", "question": "6109 + -9111 - 8400 - -5601 - 1461 ", "answer": "-7262", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4463", "question": "83336 * -61830 ", "answer": "-5152664880", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4464", "question": "22924 - 56479 + 9793 - 93733 ", "answer": "-117495", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4465", "question": "340 * 656 + -909 ", "answer": "222131", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4466", "question": "-220750 - 745781 * 873100 + -411270 + 476620 ", "answer": "-651141546500", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4467", "question": "-416086 * -713506 ", "answer": "296879857516", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4468", "question": "1439 * 38181 * 74677 ", "answer": "4102938010743", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4469", "question": "654379 - 801340 - 972319 * -364921 ", "answer": "354819474838", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4470", "question": "30846 - 98241 ", "answer": "-67395", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4471", "question": "31 - -3 + 81 ", "answer": "115", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4472", "question": "4452 + -9900 + -1088 + 1824 ", "answer": "-4712", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4473", "question": "-12156 * -15289 ", "answer": "185853084", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4474", "question": "-865009 - 186109 + 981266 - -420873 + -170582 ", "answer": "180439", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4475", "question": "-32 + -17 + 66 ", "answer": "17", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4476", "question": "89675 * -10779 + -92247 * -43302 + 6876 ", "answer": "3027879645", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4477", "question": "82 + 13 + -5 ", "answer": "90", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4478", "question": "484 + -927 ", "answer": "-443", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4479", "question": "6793 - 8092 - -9723 ", "answer": "8424", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4480", "question": "23 + 91 * -95 - 46 + -45 ", "answer": "-8713", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4481", "question": "-47 + -63 ", "answer": "-110", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4482", "question": "84 * 54 ", "answer": "4536", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4483", "question": "416618 + 525920 * 939051 * 620679 - -154813 ", "answer": "306532070002575111", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4484", "question": "-747608 * 480205 - 667526 - -795670 - -691261 ", "answer": "-359004280235", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4485", "question": "-2060 - -4411 ", "answer": "2351", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4486", "question": "44697 + -15216 + 38055 * 14432 * 30473 ", "answer": "16736069045961", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4487", "question": "-3250 + 9399 - -2372 ", "answer": "8521", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4488", "question": "20 - -71 - 51 * 83 ", "answer": "-4142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4489", "question": "-3660 + -2193 + -8375 ", "answer": "-14228", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4490", "question": "-88293 + 7840 + 83624 - -26919 ", "answer": "30090", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4491", "question": "-48444 + -87406 ", "answer": "-135850", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4492", "question": "2 * -50 - -91 - -85 ", "answer": "76", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4493", "question": "39 + -57 ", "answer": "-18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4494", "question": "-736427 * 106851 + -493252 ", "answer": "-78688454629", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4495", "question": "42687 - 75 + 34741 ", "answer": "77353", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4496", "question": "-8761 * 1663 ", "answer": "-14569543", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4497", "question": "584937 + 926322 ", "answer": "1511259", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4498", "question": "72 - 81 * 30 - -80 ", "answer": "-2278", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4499", "question": "6687 * -1793 ", "answer": "-11989791", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4500", "question": "-641 + -611 + 841 - 40 ", "answer": "-451", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4501", "question": "46424 + -78491 * 66475 ", "answer": "-5217642801", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4502", "question": "-710163 * 374771 - -69292 + 518854 + -677937 ", "answer": "-266148587464", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4503", "question": "-833 * -13 * 781 - -372 ", "answer": "8457821", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4504", "question": "-92 - 52 ", "answer": "-144", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4505", "question": "294 + -142 - -997 + 758 ", "answer": "1907", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4506", "question": "59564 + -36973 ", "answer": "22591", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4507", "question": "47 + 4 ", "answer": "51", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4508", "question": "6298 + -1154 - -8152 ", "answer": "13296", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4509", "question": "-438 + -275 * 842 ", "answer": "-231988", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4510", "question": "64 - -3 ", "answer": "67", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4511", "question": "-67781 + -67978 ", "answer": "-135759", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4512", "question": "-369 * -305 ", "answer": "112545", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4513", "question": "70 + -50 * 66 ", "answer": "-3230", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4514", "question": "-98 * 64 - -9 ", "answer": "-6263", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4515", "question": "-2277 - 947 + 7453 ", "answer": "4229", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4516", "question": "-11650 + 2695 - -31696 * 91040 ", "answer": "2885594885", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4517", "question": "439 + 563 + 301 * -637 - 555 ", "answer": "-191290", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4518", "question": "563 - -777 + 654 - -380 ", "answer": "2374", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4519", "question": "65894 * 67897 + -9846 * 38788 + -75032 ", "answer": "4092023238", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4520", "question": "2677 - -9761 ", "answer": "12438", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4521", "question": "464 * -622 + -983 * -90 * 57 ", "answer": "4754182", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4522", "question": "-7 - -4 * -88 * 21 ", "answer": "-7399", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4523", "question": "516654 - 512046 - -654668 ", "answer": "659276", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4524", "question": "21534 - 53372 * -39100 ", "answer": "2086866734", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4525", "question": "4085 * -6307 + -7974 + 3416 ", "answer": "-25768653", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4526", "question": "-9367 * -9156 - 6832 + 6187 - -8486 ", "answer": "85772093", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4527", "question": "68 + 99 ", "answer": "167", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4528", "question": "7003 + -154794 - 977686 + 143925 - 894786 ", "answer": "-1876338", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4529", "question": "-7354 + -6920 ", "answer": "-14274", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4530", "question": "84 * -53 - 79 ", "answer": "-4531", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4531", "question": "18219 * -79086 + -25014 + -84479 - -67038 ", "answer": "-1440910289", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4532", "question": "244769 * 209798 ", "answer": "51352046662", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4533", "question": "52493 + 48304 + -44924 * 7611 ", "answer": "-341815767", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4534", "question": "-39 * -50 - -25 * 34 * 96 ", "answer": "83550", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4535", "question": "-56 + 49 * 92 * -41 ", "answer": "-184884", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4536", "question": "-26 * -98 ", "answer": "2548", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4537", "question": "74264 + -91686 - 26428 - -80235 ", "answer": "36385", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4538", "question": "-9868 * 2820 ", "answer": "-27827760", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4539", "question": "-92689 + -874076 * -78328 * 364265 - -713204 ", "answer": "24939266600018435", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4540", "question": "-31 + -89 ", "answer": "-120", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4541", "question": "-81 + -6 ", "answer": "-87", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4542", "question": "11 - -93 ", "answer": "104", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4543", "question": "55780 + 37026 + -95838 + 52156 ", "answer": "49124", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4544", "question": "-9 + 32 * -7 ", "answer": "-233", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4545", "question": "-334 - -2135 + 9024 ", "answer": "10825", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4546", "question": "-5677 - -97919 * 8286 + -61454 ", "answer": "811289703", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4547", "question": "-24 + 4 * -16 + 74 ", "answer": "-14", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4548", "question": "-351 - -492 - 5 ", "answer": "136", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4549", "question": "-820 - 356 * 97 ", "answer": "-35352", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4550", "question": "-406 - -694 - 934 ", "answer": "-646", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4551", "question": "-6168 + 372 + 5818 * -562 ", "answer": "-3275512", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4552", "question": "-608121 - 408330 - -450091 ", "answer": "-566360", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4553", "question": "-4067 + -7272 - 8473 - 3569 - 1518 ", "answer": "-24899", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4554", "question": "-5932 * -19111 - 35440 * -77233 - -10681 ", "answer": "2850514653", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4555", "question": "92 - 66 * 12 - -92 ", "answer": "-608", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4556", "question": "-39276 + 721145 + 484269 * -879377 * 416324 ", "answer": "-177293665517739943", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4557", "question": "-695 - -556 * 205 * 931 + -683 ", "answer": "106114002", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4558", "question": "-35 - -3 - -94 ", "answer": "62", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4559", "question": "7451 - -2145 * -5648 ", "answer": "-12107509", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4560", "question": "-9363 + -3423 - -1852 ", "answer": "-10934", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4561", "question": "900592 * 333730 ", "answer": "300554568160", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4562", "question": "459643 + 668948 + 471659 - 156988 ", "answer": "1443262", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4563", "question": "970 + 924 * -902 ", "answer": "-832478", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4564", "question": "1807 * 54533 + 85344 * -76499 ", "answer": "-6430189525", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4565", "question": "910 + 120 + -387 + 913 ", "answer": "1556", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4566", "question": "101 - 151 + 667 ", "answer": "617", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4567", "question": "-122964 - -838158 + 873983 ", "answer": "1589177", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4568", "question": "-401981 + -426894 ", "answer": "-828875", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4569", "question": "-120863 + -832892 ", "answer": "-953755", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4570", "question": "61180 - -91666 - 29113 * -26814 - -67472 ", "answer": "780856300", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4571", "question": "9938 * 7250 ", "answer": "72050500", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4572", "question": "17305 + -342845 ", "answer": "-325540", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4573", "question": "47 - 40 * -48 - 62 * 34 ", "answer": "-141", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4574", "question": "269 * 716 + 815 * 528 - 589 ", "answer": "622335", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4575", "question": "-13 + 98 * 74 ", "answer": "7239", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4576", "question": "394243 - -972458 ", "answer": "1366701", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4577", "question": "482 + 981 * 2 ", "answer": "2444", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4578", "question": "7101 + -4937 * 4745 ", "answer": "-23418964", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4579", "question": "51960 * 95240 * 78075 * -41349 ", "answer": "-15975907337756520000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4580", "question": "-331 + 886 + -513 * -215 - -433 ", "answer": "111283", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4581", "question": "42336 * 91717 * 38568 * 29455 * 48994 ", "answer": "216116888740553383672320", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4582", "question": "585 + 389 + 127 + 53 ", "answer": "1154", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4583", "question": "69 + 75 + -42 - -86 * -4 ", "answer": "-242", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4584", "question": "-602656 - 682452 + 173943 * 653043 ", "answer": "113590973441", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4585", "question": "-94453 * 74093 + -43171 + -16784 * -20602 ", "answer": "-6652565332", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4586", "question": "-660767 * 68194 - -511288 + 301867 + -37515 ", "answer": "-45059569158", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4587", "question": "125357 * 886117 + -390057 * -380461 ", "answer": "259482445046", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4588", "question": "-46511 * -95509 + -14457 ", "answer": "4442204642", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4589", "question": "25 * 60 - -99 * -88 ", "answer": "-7212", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4590", "question": "5738 - 9864 * 8321 ", "answer": "-82072606", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4591", "question": "933 + -7091 + -2421 - 5459 ", "answer": "-14038", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4592", "question": "125043 + -787719 ", "answer": "-662676", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4593", "question": "-155796 * -661998 ", "answer": "103136640408", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4594", "question": "-349 - -686 ", "answer": "337", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4595", "question": "-85 - 43 * 38 - 73 + -71 ", "answer": "-1863", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4596", "question": "75973 + -42994 + -47012 - 21156 ", "answer": "-35189", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4597", "question": "688 - -348 ", "answer": "1036", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4598", "question": "-4700 + 7488 - -2121 ", "answer": "4909", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4599", "question": "758618 + -860788 + -535772 ", "answer": "-637942", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4600", "question": "288 - 298 * -69 + 783 ", "answer": "21633", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4601", "question": "78 + -47 - -28 - 4 ", "answer": "55", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4602", "question": "737 + -648 * 701 ", "answer": "-453511", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4603", "question": "-882 * 942 ", "answer": "-830844", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4604", "question": "-5122 + 36831 * 38220 - -76755 - 85678 ", "answer": "1407666775", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4605", "question": "217 * 672 - 188 - -957 ", "answer": "146593", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4606", "question": "-53 * -5 * 84 ", "answer": "22260", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4607", "question": "-43 * 495 * -483 + -660 * -938 ", "answer": "10899735", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4608", "question": "-221968 * -119640 * -887347 - -588959 ", "answer": "-23564610116928481", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4609", "question": "103339 * 366178 ", "answer": "37840468342", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4610", "question": "33 + 32 ", "answer": "65", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4611", "question": "27 - 80 + 35 * 47 ", "answer": "1592", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4612", "question": "-58 + 4 - 46 ", "answer": "-100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4613", "question": "-56664 + 32515 - -11259 + 19122 ", "answer": "6232", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4614", "question": "5997 * 7717 - -3354 ", "answer": "46282203", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4615", "question": "21572 + -95996 - -80738 ", "answer": "6314", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4616", "question": "-3 + 40 * -77 - -15 - -14 ", "answer": "-3054", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4617", "question": "-186257 + -768646 + -41358 + 139398 ", "answer": "-856863", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4618", "question": "99 * 59 * 46 * 18 ", "answer": "4836348", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4619", "question": "-274635 - 185038 ", "answer": "-459673", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4620", "question": "-84 - 17 ", "answer": "-101", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4621", "question": "421 + -991 + -964 - 566 ", "answer": "-2100", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4622", "question": "617 + 265 ", "answer": "882", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4623", "question": "264 + 2539 - -1760 * 3608 ", "answer": "6352883", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4624", "question": "-3809 + -7592 ", "answer": "-11401", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4625", "question": "276 * -554 + -219 + -768 + 449 ", "answer": "-153442", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4626", "question": "-2 * 41 + 84 ", "answer": "2", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4627", "question": "121 * -751 + 963 ", "answer": "-89908", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4628", "question": "-722 - -2857 ", "answer": "2135", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4629", "question": "4948 - 4399 + -7568 ", "answer": "-7019", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4630", "question": "-543 * -733 * -253 - 743 ", "answer": "-100699550", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4631", "question": "3303 - -5299 ", "answer": "8602", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4632", "question": "5 - 59 * 20 + -45 ", "answer": "-1220", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4633", "question": "-42 * 73 + -66 ", "answer": "-3132", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4634", "question": "-14664 * -69953 ", "answer": "1025790792", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4635", "question": "26 - -50 + -59 ", "answer": "17", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4636", "question": "-83 * 24 + 74 ", "answer": "-1918", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4637", "question": "9 + -43 * -62 * 90 - 40 ", "answer": "239909", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4638", "question": "-809 + 809 - 384 ", "answer": "-384", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4639", "question": "435943 - -456308 + 929128 - -476788 * 908750 ", "answer": "433282916379", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4640", "question": "5148 * 6641 - -885 ", "answer": "34188753", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4641", "question": "-89 - -86 - 24 + -91 ", "answer": "-118", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4642", "question": "7953 + 9717 * 259 * 423 ", "answer": "1064573322", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4643", "question": "-10654 - 86028 * 86257 + 9606 - 15048 ", "answer": "-7420533292", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4644", "question": "-60541 - -96417 - -63591 * -51372 ", "answer": "-3266760976", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4645", "question": "1562 + -3128 - -4773 ", "answer": "3207", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4646", "question": "-221876 * -859885 * 299335 ", "answer": "57109479361567100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4647", "question": "-16196 * 386930 + -77357 * 715889 ", "answer": "-61645743653", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4648", "question": "-403993 + -281802 * 882664 - -4256 + 362690 ", "answer": "-248736517575", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4649", "question": "660759 + -229059 ", "answer": "431700", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4650", "question": "987 + -2733 ", "answer": "-1746", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4651", "question": "61 - 35 ", "answer": "26", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4652", "question": "69827 * 18044 ", "answer": "1259958388", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4653", "question": "1386 - -8603 * -1401 ", "answer": "-12051417", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4654", "question": "16 + 88 + -49 + -42 ", "answer": "13", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4655", "question": "-214 + -867 ", "answer": "-1081", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4656", "question": "-5633 * -7083 * 6561 + 4662 - 6910 ", "answer": "261774312131", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4657", "question": "52581 * -89765 * -23752 * -55879 ", "answer": "-6264475089979137720", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4658", "question": "-47 * -99 ", "answer": "4653", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4659", "question": "-502841 - -981193 ", "answer": "478352", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4660", "question": "443 - -689 ", "answer": "1132", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4661", "question": "746 * -767 * 656 ", "answer": "-375351392", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4662", "question": "3922 + -87655 * -64221 - -68148 * 14052 ", "answer": "6586911373", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4663", "question": "8878 - 9930 ", "answer": "-1052", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4664", "question": "87 - 51 ", "answer": "36", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4665", "question": "82257 * -3447 + 52888 * 19150 + 2964 ", "answer": "729268285", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4666", "question": "5123 - 53695 ", "answer": "-48572", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4667", "question": "-36 - 24 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4668", "question": "83650 * -67002 ", "answer": "-5604717300", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4669", "question": "-67935 + 803695 + 601823 * -477179 ", "answer": "-287176561557", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4670", "question": "27685 * 17564 ", "answer": "486259340", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4671", "question": "2894 * 4653 - 7521 + -6342 + -3069 ", "answer": "13448850", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4672", "question": "806906 - -964121 - 397787 - -22982 ", "answer": "1396222", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4673", "question": "100 * 2 + -25 ", "answer": "175", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4674", "question": "12 - -41 * -32 + 49 ", "answer": "-1251", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4675", "question": "-75 + 99 * -30 ", "answer": "-3045", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4676", "question": "1887 - 3215 + 6779 ", "answer": "5451", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4677", "question": "24535 - -3353 * 8310 * 36356 ", "answer": "1013002885615", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4678", "question": "-7798 + -9580 - 4888 ", "answer": "-22266", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4679", "question": "-60 - 95 + 18 ", "answer": "-137", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4680", "question": "5667 + -6953 - -5546 + -4017 ", "answer": "243", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4681", "question": "-67 * 43 + -20 ", "answer": "-2901", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4682", "question": "-93313 * -48653 - -92985 + -8510 ", "answer": "4540041864", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4683", "question": "771 * -403 - -100 ", "answer": "-310613", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4684", "question": "-54 * 8 + 32 + -30 ", "answer": "-430", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4685", "question": "452866 + -368269 ", "answer": "84597", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4686", "question": "-460508 - 585626 ", "answer": "-1046134", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4687", "question": "-3510 + 5833 * 1717 * 668 ", "answer": "6690190838", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4688", "question": "3 - -48 * 9 + -56 ", "answer": "379", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4689", "question": "-2244 * -7908 ", "answer": "17745552", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4690", "question": "9372 * 2988 ", "answer": "28003536", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4691", "question": "775455 + -897028 + 500372 + -98482 ", "answer": "280317", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4692", "question": "-7331 * -5134 + 830 ", "answer": "37638184", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4693", "question": "57 + 71 + -13 - 66 ", "answer": "49", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4694", "question": "1659 - 7948 ", "answer": "-6289", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4695", "question": "2223 - -5323 - 6887 + 5757 - -6843 ", "answer": "13259", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4696", "question": "73 - 65 + 52 ", "answer": "60", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4697", "question": "113942 + 10137 * -968698 + 512289 + -162767 ", "answer": "-9819228162", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4698", "question": "895 + -707 * 435 - -534 + 951 ", "answer": "-305165", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4699", "question": "-19270 * 47441 * 14297 - 69035 ", "answer": "-13070146905825", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4700", "question": "-525 - -530 * 863 * -525 - 934 ", "answer": "-240131209", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4701", "question": "80 + 42 * 24 + -5 ", "answer": "1083", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4702", "question": "-48 + -29 + 92 * -9 - -54 ", "answer": "-851", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4703", "question": "176 * -607 * 442 - 475 + -98 ", "answer": "-47220317", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4704", "question": "-1881 + -1164 ", "answer": "-3045", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4705", "question": "953 + 798 ", "answer": "1751", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4706", "question": "-273232 * 897827 + -58786 + -408668 ", "answer": "-245315534318", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4707", "question": "-15935 - 52774 + -32049 ", "answer": "-100758", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4708", "question": "-2369 - 83850 - 22445 ", "answer": "-108664", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4709", "question": "8265 + -9910 * -3577 - -3598 - -3708 ", "answer": "35463641", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4710", "question": "57806 - -47154 * 35533 + -23590 + -92734 ", "answer": "1675464564", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4711", "question": "-3 + 47 * -64 + 98 - -89 ", "answer": "-2824", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4712", "question": "9 + -36 - 84 + -43 + -38 ", "answer": "-192", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4713", "question": "536 * -963 * 244 - -400 ", "answer": "-125944592", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4714", "question": "-817768 * -209483 * -806870 * -725751 ", "answer": "100315977255797533055280", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4715", "question": "-5204 * -9200 ", "answer": "47876800", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4716", "question": "-548232 - -783388 + 897462 ", "answer": "1132618", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4717", "question": "-52 + -78 ", "answer": "-130", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4718", "question": "2009 + -6354 + 4520 - -3529 ", "answer": "3704", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4719", "question": "3174 * -78710 - 60944 ", "answer": "-249886484", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4720", "question": "76 - 38 ", "answer": "38", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4721", "question": "-414297 - 815631 - 775878 - -880403 ", "answer": "-1125403", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4722", "question": "87 - 83 * -11 - 98 ", "answer": "902", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4723", "question": "2980 * -6058 + 5002 * -588 * -819 ", "answer": "2390770304", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4724", "question": "432585 * 158616 + -306499 ", "answer": "68614595861", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4725", "question": "511076 - -939177 ", "answer": "1450253", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4726", "question": "-625 + -974 + -52 + -108 - -461 ", "answer": "-1298", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4727", "question": "-195969 * -746784 ", "answer": "146346513696", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4728", "question": "1363 - 8173 - -3866 + 5100 - -6236 ", "answer": "8392", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4729", "question": "-1921 * -954 - -9475 - -432 - -3116 ", "answer": "1845657", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4730", "question": "-586449 - -116676 * -577799 + -142423 * 650486 ", "answer": "-160060030151", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4731", "question": "-646 - -832 ", "answer": "186", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4732", "question": "-23051 + 50701 * -79493 * 67073 ", "answer": "-270329315099340", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4733", "question": "6 + 4 - 99 - -12 + -8 ", "answer": "-85", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4734", "question": "-40 + 40 + 58 ", "answer": "58", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4735", "question": "-57769 + 539405 - -192952 + 911484 ", "answer": "1586072", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4736", "question": "22920 * 1656 ", "answer": "37955520", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4737", "question": "-14312 - 60034 * 20909 * -14875 - 46358 ", "answer": "18671857166080", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4738", "question": "98 - -65 * -27 ", "answer": "-1657", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4739", "question": "-77 - -65 - 68 ", "answer": "-80", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4740", "question": "1931 * -9793 * -3488 ", "answer": "65959067104", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4741", "question": "5146 * 5727 + 5780 + -8520 + 1091 ", "answer": "29469493", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4742", "question": "24 * -51 * -65 - -14 ", "answer": "79574", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4743", "question": "26484 - 30333 * -87708 + -86595 + 14642 ", "answer": "2660401295", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4744", "question": "-40 * -94 + 20 ", "answer": "3780", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4745", "question": "32186 - -52080 ", "answer": "84266", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4746", "question": "115239 * 427425 * -96457 + -142309 ", "answer": "-4751088844858084", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4747", "question": "-4139 + 875 - -5499 + 2936 ", "answer": "5171", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4748", "question": "-71 - -96 ", "answer": "25", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4749", "question": "-34740 + -31109 - 87453 ", "answer": "-153302", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4750", "question": "-808 + -43 * 972 ", "answer": "-42604", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4751", "question": "-941169 - 696621 + -476220 * 820640 * 15606 ", "answer": "-6098905653202590", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4752", "question": "-585 * -8363 + -2896 + 3045 - 3412 ", "answer": "4889092", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4753", "question": "-9551 * -369 - 7491 + -5793 ", "answer": "3511035", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4754", "question": "913802 - 336150 + -630484 - -584737 ", "answer": "531905", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4755", "question": "-93 * 0 * 82 - -18 + 31 ", "answer": "49", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4756", "question": "-47 + -85 + 50 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4757", "question": "72872 * -598225 ", "answer": "-43593852200", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4758", "question": "82032 + -42669 ", "answer": "39363", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4759", "question": "2 - -45 * -53 * 80 ", "answer": "-190798", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4760", "question": "-61 * -80 - -45 ", "answer": "4925", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4761", "question": "79278 + 84714 ", "answer": "163992", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4762", "question": "2829 * 9551 ", "answer": "27019779", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4763", "question": "-56 * 49 + -13 - -40 * 60 ", "answer": "-357", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4764", "question": "600704 * 479391 * 920237 ", "answer": "265002573348509568", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4765", "question": "94 * 67 * -52 + -33 ", "answer": "-327529", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4766", "question": "507 + -569 ", "answer": "-62", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4767", "question": "6602 - 4488 * 6903 ", "answer": "-30974062", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4768", "question": "-50467 * -20119 + -66300 + -99582 ", "answer": "1015179691", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4769", "question": "-515601 * 595386 + 879450 + 764478 * 135637 ", "answer": "-203289235050", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4770", "question": "2866 * -1530 ", "answer": "-4384980", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4771", "question": "-433 * 54 * 432 * -449 * -398 ", "answer": "-1805073190848", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4772", "question": "-81876 * -943921 * -567496 ", "answer": "-43858630876326816", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4773", "question": "-8457 + 16073 + -48181 - -25666 ", "answer": "-14899", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4774", "question": "33 * 48 + -82 + -78 * -85 ", "answer": "8132", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4775", "question": "884 * -199 * -468 * 323 + 239 ", "answer": "26592166463", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4776", "question": "-11 - 48 * -80 ", "answer": "3829", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4777", "question": "99285 + -32297 ", "answer": "66988", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4778", "question": "-5217 * 8431 ", "answer": "-43984527", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4779", "question": "22 - -9 * -73 * 2 ", "answer": "-1292", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4780", "question": "-41 + -39 ", "answer": "-80", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4781", "question": "-11958 + -35885 - 80237 ", "answer": "-128080", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4782", "question": "-16946 - 21113 ", "answer": "-38059", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4783", "question": "181 * 167 ", "answer": "30227", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4784", "question": "60615 + -30278 * -81914 + 35530 ", "answer": "2480288237", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4785", "question": "89798 * -59632 - 47802 ", "answer": "-5354882138", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4786", "question": "78 - 15 - -46 * 76 ", "answer": "3559", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4787", "question": "919913 - 125329 ", "answer": "794584", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4788", "question": "3187 + -9011 - 288 ", "answer": "-6112", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4789", "question": "-154283 + -13407 + -153770 * 616816 - -59278 ", "answer": "-94847904732", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4790", "question": "41 - 825 * 890 * -34 + 412 ", "answer": "24964953", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4791", "question": "535 + 979 + -369 - -765 - 503 ", "answer": "1407", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4792", "question": "444 - 950 ", "answer": "-506", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4793", "question": "-215 * -926 - 842 ", "answer": "198248", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4794", "question": "983 - 327 - 479 + 101 * 276 ", "answer": "28053", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4795", "question": "-8887 - 3553 ", "answer": "-12440", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4796", "question": "326 + -1149 * -6947 * 9897 ", "answer": "78998873717", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4797", "question": "49286 + 86985 * -73106 * -66525 ", "answer": "423040817949536", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4798", "question": "-70876 + -88999 + -16197 * -30721 - 38850 ", "answer": "497389312", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4799", "question": "-219378 - 865998 - 96639 + -78233 ", "answer": "-1260248", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4800", "question": "-678276 * 451987 + 41699 ", "answer": "-306571892713", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4801", "question": "4258 * -7366 * -289 ", "answer": "9064319692", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4802", "question": "3179 - -4282 ", "answer": "7461", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4803", "question": "-8667 - -4679 * -3546 * 1725 ", "answer": "-28620749817", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4804", "question": "-10659 * -928695 * -176615 * 467497 ", "answer": "-817327259035373713275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4805", "question": "6628 * 1509 - 1114 - 7675 ", "answer": "9992863", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4806", "question": "-68429 + 78000 + -75511 - 99414 + 69187 ", "answer": "-96167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4807", "question": "97 - 63 + -56 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4808", "question": "299 - -141 - 263 - 325 + 189 ", "answer": "41", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4809", "question": "885 + -723 - -721 - 54 * -195 ", "answer": "11413", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4810", "question": "-352 - 657 - 140 + -509 + 291 ", "answer": "-1367", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4811", "question": "332 - -822 * 291 ", "answer": "239534", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4812", "question": "19 + 35 ", "answer": "54", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4813", "question": "17 * 32 ", "answer": "544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4814", "question": "64894 * -60533 * -44368 ", "answer": "174287642176736", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4815", "question": "2390 - 2481 - 9034 ", "answer": "-9125", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4816", "question": "-84483 * -19693 ", "answer": "1663723719", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4817", "question": "375 + -518 ", "answer": "-143", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4818", "question": "23 - -8 + 45 + 82 ", "answer": "158", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4819", "question": "-13381 + 69342 ", "answer": "55961", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4820", "question": "273192 + 709396 ", "answer": "982588", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4821", "question": "-89 + 233 * 733 * 309 + -6 ", "answer": "52773706", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4822", "question": "722097 - -354424 + 344169 - 213887 - 428920 ", "answer": "777883", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4823", "question": "-6765 * 5652 * -857 - -7586 ", "answer": "32768071046", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4824", "question": "-58 - 95 - -18 + -16 ", "answer": "-151", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4825", "question": "-536511 - -528919 * 875707 ", "answer": "463177534222", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4826", "question": "5726 * 5948 - 88083 ", "answer": "33970165", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4827", "question": "-843245 - -736546 ", "answer": "-106699", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4828", "question": "6644 * -9854 ", "answer": "-65469976", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4829", "question": "-83 * 0 ", "answer": "0", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4830", "question": "9134 + -313 + 3527 - 56 + -2037 ", "answer": "10255", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4831", "question": "126 + -594 + -446 - -843 ", "answer": "-71", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4832", "question": "-3583 - -2394 + -7936 + 4260 ", "answer": "-4865", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4833", "question": "187 - -616 ", "answer": "803", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4834", "question": "203 + -838 + -900 * -473 ", "answer": "425065", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4835", "question": "-823259 * -610655 * 425162 * 9731 ", "answer": "2079908925040639695190", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4836", "question": "-77945 * 43022 ", "answer": "-3353349790", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4837", "question": "724515 * 928812 * -920155 ", "answer": "-619207473510657900", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4838", "question": "-100 - -88 ", "answer": "-12", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4839", "question": "-82799 + 77095 + -11295 - -31322 * 30665 ", "answer": "960472131", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4840", "question": "51143 * 89326 + 31932 - -12361 ", "answer": "4568443911", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4841", "question": "-52 - -43 - -85 + -75 ", "answer": "1", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4842", "question": "25739 * -7367 - -13808 ", "answer": "-189605405", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4843", "question": "85 - 88 ", "answer": "-3", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4844", "question": "4613 + 7566 + 8095 ", "answer": "20274", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4845", "question": "-24 - -100 - -7 ", "answer": "83", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4846", "question": "-29776 - 20870 ", "answer": "-50646", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4847", "question": "600 * 720 * -434 ", "answer": "-187488000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4848", "question": "-58 - 498 * -727 ", "answer": "361988", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4849", "question": "-9655 - 1430 * 8392 ", "answer": "-12010215", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4850", "question": "21 * -59 ", "answer": "-1239", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4851", "question": "-68954 + -95442 - -23748 * -51091 - 83418 ", "answer": "-1213556882", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4852", "question": "-979140 + 332994 ", "answer": "-646146", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4853", "question": "-24566 + 79369 * 38883 * -47274 * 51193 ", "answer": "-7468675755452700980", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4854", "question": "-450 + 643 * 770 - 692 + -484 ", "answer": "493484", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4855", "question": "74 - -58 + 56 * -65 ", "answer": "-3508", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4856", "question": "24695 - 44860 - -70167 + 99924 - -88618 ", "answer": "238544", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4857", "question": "3690 * 316 ", "answer": "1166040", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4858", "question": "-5896 * -2002 + -7855 * 5194 ", "answer": "-28995078", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4859", "question": "-24 + -71 ", "answer": "-95", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4860", "question": "32 + -54 + -30 ", "answer": "-52", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4861", "question": "-914 * 899 ", "answer": "-821686", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4862", "question": "-125 + -122 + -802 - -288 ", "answer": "-761", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4863", "question": "-13 + 847 ", "answer": "834", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4864", "question": "-909 + 9532 ", "answer": "8623", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4865", "question": "9108 - -704 + 5902 + -5112 ", "answer": "10602", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4866", "question": "-755 - -49 ", "answer": "-706", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4867", "question": "-9045 - -8618 ", "answer": "-427", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4868", "question": "-7734 * -905 - -2401 ", "answer": "7001671", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4869", "question": "-9833 * 6757 - 9053 ", "answer": "-66450634", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4870", "question": "838 - -177 - 737 * -962 * 792 ", "answer": "561524263", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4871", "question": "-7672 - 911 - 6694 + 8666 - -5159 ", "answer": "-1452", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4872", "question": "724673 + 48414 - 704605 ", "answer": "68482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4873", "question": "893 + 45 * 729 + 209 ", "answer": "33907", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4874", "question": "52 * -7 * 64 ", "answer": "-23296", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4875", "question": "-333045 * -780532 ", "answer": "259952279940", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4876", "question": "-2451 * -53351 - 77367 - 55272 ", "answer": "130630662", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4877", "question": "-81 - -5 ", "answer": "-76", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4878", "question": "-79 * 91 * 31 ", "answer": "-222859", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4879", "question": "36252 + -18892 * -4028 * 54595 * 27892 ", "answer": "115877715776486492", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4880", "question": "-8237 * 2569 - 8233 + -4252 ", "answer": "-21173338", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4881", "question": "95 + -53 - -9 + -77 ", "answer": "-26", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4882", "question": "-187 + 498 + -821 + 788 ", "answer": "278", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4883", "question": "49621 + -906474 + 57677 - -950370 ", "answer": "151194", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4884", "question": "-79599 + -29736 - 60243 - 58449 ", "answer": "-228027", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4885", "question": "41713 - 26825 + -39484 ", "answer": "-24596", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4886", "question": "-4909 - 3793 + -5040 ", "answer": "-13742", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4887", "question": "-65 * 44 * -52 - -15 - 63 ", "answer": "148672", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4888", "question": "-366 * -617 - -993 * 713 ", "answer": "933831", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4889", "question": "-61272 + -54731 + -69514 ", "answer": "-185517", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4890", "question": "93382 * -36770 * 78744 ", "answer": "-270379819088160", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4891", "question": "-5737 - 3598 ", "answer": "-9335", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4892", "question": "-4889 + 6596 ", "answer": "1707", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4893", "question": "460 + 326 * -129 ", "answer": "-41594", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4894", "question": "462 + -732 - 571 * 327 ", "answer": "-186987", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4895", "question": "595473 - 699514 + 601362 ", "answer": "497321", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4896", "question": "601880 * -469043 - -263787 * -986909 ", "answer": "-542641365223", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4897", "question": "4991 * -7746 + -909 + 8296 - -6526 ", "answer": "-38646373", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4898", "question": "89227 * -9661 ", "answer": "-862022047", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4899", "question": "32674 + 73018 + -90363 * 56539 ", "answer": "-5108927965", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4900", "question": "4771 + 5097 - -9238 * -6368 ", "answer": "-58817716", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4901", "question": "54 - 76 * 75 * -61 ", "answer": "347754", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4902", "question": "-410 + -474 + -523 ", "answer": "-1407", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4903", "question": "-57 + 54 ", "answer": "-3", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4904", "question": "-27307 - 13358 ", "answer": "-40665", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4905", "question": "73 - 95 + -73 - 27 - 99 ", "answer": "-221", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4906", "question": "2758 * 2259 ", "answer": "6230322", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4907", "question": "0 * 6 - -47 * -15 + -30 ", "answer": "-735", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4908", "question": "534 - -1063 + -1916 ", "answer": "-319", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4909", "question": "29 - 40 * -39 - -9 * 8 ", "answer": "1661", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4910", "question": "-380322 + -232318 - 917449 * -235829 - 387484 ", "answer": "216360080097", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4911", "question": "-6039 + -6517 + 9827 - 4320 - -382 ", "answer": "-6667", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4912", "question": "-31832 + 78219 ", "answer": "46387", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4913", "question": "50642 + -55684 ", "answer": "-5042", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4914", "question": "-24 * 14 ", "answer": "-336", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4915", "question": "52619 * 47889 + 8712 ", "answer": "2519880003", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4916", "question": "4928 + -1762 ", "answer": "3166", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4917", "question": "-41506 * -58784 * -90250 ", "answer": "-220199955536000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4918", "question": "-780 + 174 * -97 + -852 + -570 ", "answer": "-19080", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4919", "question": "3999 * -7847 - 4039 * -2808 * 3211 ", "answer": "36386214879", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4920", "question": "-16261 - 14022 ", "answer": "-30283", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4921", "question": "-196 + -645 * 461 ", "answer": "-297541", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4922", "question": "-844125 + 427449 * 827552 - 324940 ", "answer": "353735105783", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4923", "question": "688 + -714 ", "answer": "-26", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4924", "question": "-87 + 33 * -27 + -28 ", "answer": "-1006", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4925", "question": "-7627 * -81671 * -60542 + 77481 ", "answer": "-37711897299133", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4926", "question": "55739 + 48061 - 53439 - 45455 * -30737 ", "answer": "1397200696", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4927", "question": "-12 + -13 ", "answer": "-25", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4928", "question": "-15 * -87 - 81 - 30 ", "answer": "1194", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4929", "question": "-9383 * -5591 - -35890 - 96754 + 26490 ", "answer": "52425979", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4930", "question": "79 * -57 * 1 ", "answer": "-4503", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4931", "question": "-827 * 8624 - 7698 ", "answer": "-7139746", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4932", "question": "77 - 6 + -76 ", "answer": "-5", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4933", "question": "653 - -840 - -374 - -898 - -364 ", "answer": "3129", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4934", "question": "533462 * 549367 * -997578 - 165023 * -820622 ", "answer": "-292356476266757906", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4935", "question": "-983 * -918 ", "answer": "902394", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4936", "question": "-402 - 803 ", "answer": "-1205", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4937", "question": "8 * -26 - 86 + 42 - 77 ", "answer": "-329", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4938", "question": "-4133 + -7715 ", "answer": "-11848", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4939", "question": "767184 * 890166 - 436931 + -296270 ", "answer": "682920379343", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4940", "question": "236 * 878 * -693 * -380 - -343 ", "answer": "54566155063", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4941", "question": "5169 - 265 * -9895 - -84 ", "answer": "2627428", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4942", "question": "-647 * -957 - -782 * -683 ", "answer": "85073", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4943", "question": "9600 + 6530 - 136 ", "answer": "15994", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4944", "question": "-57 * 94 - -58 + -98 * -2 ", "answer": "-5104", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4945", "question": "-426501 + -482065 + -432409 - -77336 + 173273 ", "answer": "-1090366", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4946", "question": "-756 + -958 ", "answer": "-1714", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4947", "question": "-32 + 52 + 73 - 48 - 85 ", "answer": "-40", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4948", "question": "-440889 * 603967 + -353103 - -467270 + 185888 ", "answer": "-266282106608", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4949", "question": "29310 * -93504 - -58478 - 45662 * 39745 ", "answer": "-4555379952", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4950", "question": "2424 - 5891 * -4387 + 2351 ", "answer": "25848592", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4951", "question": "-177 - -424 * 943 ", "answer": "399655", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4952", "question": "-9248 - 748 + -3593 - -7783 + 1020 ", "answer": "-4786", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4953", "question": "-20335 * -25006 ", "answer": "508497010", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4954", "question": "-7997 + 7181 ", "answer": "-816", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4955", "question": "3476 + 4491 * 8244 + -6353 + -9986 ", "answer": "37010941", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4956", "question": "55203 + -94092 - -75249 + -72750 ", "answer": "-36390", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4957", "question": "-43063 + 9228 * 30538 ", "answer": "281761601", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4958", "question": "7434 + -2131 ", "answer": "5303", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4959", "question": "2576 - 9114 + -151 * -8479 * -5977 ", "answer": "-7652532971", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4960", "question": "286 * 482 - -375 ", "answer": "138227", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4961", "question": "-3544 * -6354 ", "answer": "22518576", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4962", "question": "50653 + -49730 - 48414 * -20443 ", "answer": "989728325", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4963", "question": "-19238 + 65596 ", "answer": "46358", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4964", "question": "-234 + 929 * -508 ", "answer": "-472166", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4965", "question": "149 * -416 * -930 + -985 * 286 ", "answer": "57363410", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4966", "question": "-2738 + 1654 + 6408 ", "answer": "5324", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4967", "question": "-61 * -68 - 20 + 40 ", "answer": "4168", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4968", "question": "15504 - -63369 - 21023 * 48581 ", "answer": "-1021239490", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4969", "question": "4016 - -270 + 4102 - 4525 ", "answer": "3863", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4970", "question": "87045 + -54919 - -30160 ", "answer": "62286", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4971", "question": "-574862 + 620442 - 233058 * 228347 - -237173 ", "answer": "-53217812373", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4972", "question": "841027 * -446904 * 479158 - 865306 ", "answer": "-180095525882501770", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4973", "question": "-3240 + -1843 * -762 ", "answer": "1401126", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4974", "question": "-32637 * -64252 - 33879 ", "answer": "2096958645", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4975", "question": "-2170 + 17047 * 77662 * -58446 + 6890 ", "answer": "-77376899842124", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4976", "question": "50687 + -85885 ", "answer": "-35198", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4977", "question": "-328663 * -291766 - 665589 ", "answer": "95892023269", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4978", "question": "50 + 33 + -86 * -66 + 51 ", "answer": "5810", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4979", "question": "-975 - 137 * -703 ", "answer": "95336", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4980", "question": "578143 + -833941 + -726617 ", "answer": "-982415", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4981", "question": "-779944 - 761842 - -892532 + -339685 ", "answer": "-988939", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4982", "question": "808 - -718 ", "answer": "1526", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4983", "question": "588 * -487 ", "answer": "-286356", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4984", "question": "768469 - 658025 - -66503 ", "answer": "176947", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4985", "question": "90145 + 32694 + -36406 * -25757 ", "answer": "937832181", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4986", "question": "-12 + 25 * 72 * 5 + -5 ", "answer": "8983", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4987", "question": "-91 * 96 * -9 + -25 ", "answer": "78599", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4988", "question": "-524 * 593 - 682 ", "answer": "-311414", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4989", "question": "636741 * -699384 ", "answer": "-445326467544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4990", "question": "3612 + -5779 - -7537 ", "answer": "5370", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4991", "question": "-253 - -440 * -783 + -742 ", "answer": "-345515", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4992", "question": "17628 * -77196 ", "answer": "-1360811088", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4993", "question": "-2652 - 9236 * -3168 * 4943 * 9347 ", "answer": "1351860723275556", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4994", "question": "174 - 958 ", "answer": "-784", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "4995", "question": "-92 - 64 + -25 * 39 * 72 ", "answer": "-70356", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "4996", "question": "-848638 * -568829 * -301346 - -54338 * -150935 ", "answer": "-145468734124104122", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "4997", "question": "91639 + -63622 ", "answer": "28017", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "4998", "question": "8759 * -2798 + 4967 - -6015 - -8487 ", "answer": "-24488213", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "4999", "question": "3501 + -9255 ", "answer": "-5754", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5000", "question": "-822405 * 577566 + 680425 + 299290 * 440766 ", "answer": "-343075629665", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5001", "question": "8573 + -1705 ", "answer": "6868", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5002", "question": "-831 - -818 + -396 - 947 ", "answer": "-1356", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5003", "question": "39 * 91 + -99 ", "answer": "3450", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5004", "question": "21 - 51 + -94 * 85 ", "answer": "-8020", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5005", "question": "189 + -567 ", "answer": "-378", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5006", "question": "671569 + 38368 * 944638 + -830334 ", "answer": "36243712019", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5007", "question": "89 - -57 + -23 * -27 - 3 ", "answer": "764", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5008", "question": "3009 * -648 ", "answer": "-1949832", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5009", "question": "-559 * 392 ", "answer": "-219128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5010", "question": "-783135 + 991269 ", "answer": "208134", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5011", "question": "-8 + 0 - -99 ", "answer": "91", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5012", "question": "-489 * -642 + -620 ", "answer": "313318", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5013", "question": "-61960 * 23160 - 924 ", "answer": "-1434994524", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5014", "question": "343 + 581 * -193 - 849 + 422 ", "answer": "-112217", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5015", "question": "6620 - 5541 + -4520 + 739 + 9093 ", "answer": "6391", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5016", "question": "1726 * 248 * -5349 + 9440 ", "answer": "-2289619312", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5017", "question": "-6083 + 8812 * -2361 ", "answer": "-20811215", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5018", "question": "-39 + -3 ", "answer": "-42", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5019", "question": "11 - -55 * -51 - 40 * 84 ", "answer": "-6154", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5020", "question": "-91443 + 498729 * -496167 - 719602 - -888530 ", "answer": "-247452794258", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5021", "question": "18424 * -54013 * 52473 * 52629 * -52350 ", "answer": "143866581165954048704400", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5022", "question": "99324 - 74752 + 31394 ", "answer": "55966", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5023", "question": "872 + 742 * -373 + -18 ", "answer": "-275912", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5024", "question": "48701 + -11932 - -889 ", "answer": "37658", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5025", "question": "741180 * 224344 - 810801 - -70430 * 838938 ", "answer": "225364878459", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5026", "question": "-18 + 67 ", "answer": "49", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5027", "question": "-282 - 340 * -962 ", "answer": "326798", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5028", "question": "-6089 * 23621 ", "answer": "-143828269", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5029", "question": "-709 * 656 - -446 + 598 * -180 ", "answer": "-572298", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5030", "question": "653 - -530 - -997 ", "answer": "2180", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5031", "question": "4189 - 5552 * 3146 * -5479 - -7202 ", "answer": "95699468959", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5032", "question": "85861 + 28548 * 47110 + -49395 + -15787 ", "answer": "1344916959", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5033", "question": "5987 * 5508 - 6624 + -7584 ", "answer": "32962188", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5034", "question": "25 - -436 * -483 * 384 * 689 ", "answer": "-55716530663", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5035", "question": "-1650 + -5594 - 9068 * -7728 ", "answer": "70070260", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5036", "question": "338 - 912 * 780 - 253 ", "answer": "-711275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5037", "question": "-56301 * 76146 ", "answer": "-4287095946", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5038", "question": "-63784 * 61635 - 41348 - -32724 ", "answer": "-3931335464", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5039", "question": "51468 - 46935 * 64733 - -75295 ", "answer": "-3038116592", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5040", "question": "102 * 643 - 105 ", "answer": "65481", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5041", "question": "-894847 - -193508 * 139273 - 325729 * -297604 ", "answer": "123887798153", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5042", "question": "335446 - -788132 * 852024 * 763777 ", "answer": "512881891539132982", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5043", "question": "-4636 - -3077 - -3580 - -1042 + 2555 ", "answer": "5618", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5044", "question": "379784 + -214285 + -683936 + 251706 - 951960 ", "answer": "-1218691", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5045", "question": "24 * -79 + -51 ", "answer": "-1947", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5046", "question": "-882107 - -843226 + -98615 + -984884 ", "answer": "-1122380", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5047", "question": "-442 * 873 * -317 + 336 + 138 ", "answer": "122319996", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5048", "question": "23196 * 82122 + 71410 + -46720 + -28566 ", "answer": "1904898036", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5049", "question": "-94420 - 70528 - 89313 + -71156 - 82353 ", "answer": "-407770", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5050", "question": "-732364 + 762517 + 849892 ", "answer": "880045", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5051", "question": "57 * -40 - 12 ", "answer": "-2292", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5052", "question": "-9722 * -4171 * 4277 ", "answer": "173434325974", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5053", "question": "487345 + 318339 * 507957 * 585547 ", "answer": "94684427483254726", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5054", "question": "695186 * -125316 ", "answer": "-87117928776", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5055", "question": "-1520 + -6586 + -3088 + -2637 ", "answer": "-13831", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5056", "question": "-71155 + 797205 ", "answer": "726050", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5057", "question": "-34874 + 14064 + -80823 ", "answer": "-101633", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5058", "question": "-8426 * 93274 ", "answer": "-785926724", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5059", "question": "-667 - -322 - 934 ", "answer": "-1279", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5060", "question": "-44513 - 99611 * 12370 - 71474 * 80446 ", "answer": "-6982029987", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5061", "question": "85 * 77 * 97 + -92 * 72 ", "answer": "628241", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5062", "question": "943 - -500 ", "answer": "1443", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5063", "question": "120645 + -742760 ", "answer": "-622115", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5064", "question": "-30710 * -25886 + -46217 * -26972 + -50691 ", "answer": "2041473293", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5065", "question": "-4024 * -2024 - 9552 ", "answer": "8135024", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5066", "question": "65482 * 89393 * -45603 + -99549 * -16290 ", "answer": "-266941577869668", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5067", "question": "-373259 - -3967 + 470240 * 588390 * -90728 ", "answer": "-25103032550270092", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5068", "question": "-474490 * 338622 - 359495 - -36595 ", "answer": "-160673075680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5069", "question": "0 - 43 ", "answer": "-43", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5070", "question": "-641889 - 789542 - 418505 - 257119 + 25378 ", "answer": "-2081677", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5071", "question": "6414 - 6918 * -2174 ", "answer": "15046146", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5072", "question": "-3371 - -563 ", "answer": "-2808", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5073", "question": "-378245 * -473876 + 940338 ", "answer": "179242167958", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5074", "question": "616 + -731 + -156 + 596 + 146 ", "answer": "471", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5075", "question": "-214918 - -634340 + -767135 + -98177 ", "answer": "-445890", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5076", "question": "108 + 3691 + 7965 - -9364 ", "answer": "21128", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5077", "question": "-73638 * 81240 ", "answer": "-5982351120", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5078", "question": "401 - -394 - 380 ", "answer": "415", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5079", "question": "-34 * 72 - -60 * -19 ", "answer": "-3588", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5080", "question": "-373792 + -398551 * 366857 - -402341 ", "answer": "-146211195658", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5081", "question": "98935 * 79587 + -21506 - 94440 - 92179 ", "answer": "7873731720", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5082", "question": "-4287 * 6064 ", "answer": "-25996368", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5083", "question": "-16 * -456 - 24 * -112 * 824 ", "answer": "2222208", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5084", "question": "-14206 + 34637 + 5969 * 34093 ", "answer": "203521548", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5085", "question": "-59 - -496 - -695 - -885 ", "answer": "2017", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5086", "question": "-728775 - 740929 * 893762 ", "answer": "-662214913673", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5087", "question": "-51454 + 94636 * 9544 ", "answer": "903154530", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5088", "question": "24 - 9 + -70 + -90 ", "answer": "-145", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5089", "question": "954329 * 271958 - -231214 * 515486 + 133501 ", "answer": "378725119687", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5090", "question": "-7905 + -4228 - 3904 * 9427 ", "answer": "-36815141", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5091", "question": "60 + 29 ", "answer": "89", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5092", "question": "-20464 + -157137 - -225965 - -848725 ", "answer": "897089", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5093", "question": "61309 + 37711 ", "answer": "99020", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5094", "question": "68 + -73 - -31 ", "answer": "26", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5095", "question": "-77295 - -76025 - 52654 + 86586 - -14696 ", "answer": "47358", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5096", "question": "77 + -163 - -948 * 737 ", "answer": "698590", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5097", "question": "-83221 + -14343 - -77675 ", "answer": "-19889", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5098", "question": "88 * -92 * -86 + -37 - -75 ", "answer": "696294", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5099", "question": "-608 - 975 * -909 + 898 ", "answer": "886565", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5100", "question": "-6404 + -6666 * 3221 * 4902 + 3319 ", "answer": "-105251756857", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5101", "question": "26770 - 9573 + -83995 ", "answer": "-66798", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5102", "question": "98248 + 791153 * -921647 * 43277 * -752728 ", "answer": "23753100798218564395344", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5103", "question": "171640 - 417725 * 435394 + -427191 + -152457 ", "answer": "-181875366658", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5104", "question": "-8072 - -5874 ", "answer": "-2198", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5105", "question": "-231524 - 399145 + -101650 * -95499 ", "answer": "9706842681", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5106", "question": "8240 * -352 + -1372 ", "answer": "-2901852", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5107", "question": "98071 * -87806 ", "answer": "-8611222226", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5108", "question": "-2345 - 7087 * 9380 + -9184 ", "answer": "-66487589", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5109", "question": "-708 * 816 * 0 - 916 ", "answer": "-916", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5110", "question": "-41 * -10 - 28 + 61 ", "answer": "443", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5111", "question": "-2585 - -532 * 8765 ", "answer": "4660395", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5112", "question": "3 + 52 ", "answer": "55", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5113", "question": "-558 + -5094 * 8329 + 4344 ", "answer": "-42424140", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5114", "question": "200295 * 982128 ", "answer": "196715327760", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5115", "question": "805931 * -594510 + 365477 + 748977 ", "answer": "-479132924356", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5116", "question": "-660967 + 937255 + 838818 - 30959 ", "answer": "1084147", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5117", "question": "-82 - 88 * -25 ", "answer": "2118", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5118", "question": "735938 + -851918 ", "answer": "-115980", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5119", "question": "-145 * 613 + 92 ", "answer": "-88793", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5120", "question": "99496 * 73054 * 51679 + 44565 ", "answer": "375632986380901", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5121", "question": "3 - -53 - -64 + -62 * 33 ", "answer": "-1926", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5122", "question": "3503 * 5194 - 1136 * -5969 - -9449 ", "answer": "24984815", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5123", "question": "-807388 - 797687 + 404381 - 700714 + 293935 ", "answer": "-1607473", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5124", "question": "-17929 * -49107 ", "answer": "880439403", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5125", "question": "739379 * -475339 * 415262 ", "answer": "-145946186296329022", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5126", "question": "49736 + -815618 - 419935 * -814885 ", "answer": "342197966593", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5127", "question": "89781 * -41407 * 97220 - 82157 * -68650 ", "answer": "-361415724631690", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5128", "question": "-92392 + 68266 * -58348 - -90058 + -45997 ", "answer": "-3983232899", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5129", "question": "-254 + -617 - 335 ", "answer": "-1206", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5130", "question": "-65837 * 61496 * -1664 * 15790 ", "answer": "106378130360453120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5131", "question": "85402 * 54899 + 26548 - 29154 - -66009 ", "answer": "4688547801", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5132", "question": "82 * 6 - 6 ", "answer": "486", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5133", "question": "932 + -7991 - -2802 * -1235 ", "answer": "-3467529", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5134", "question": "63 * 87 * 33 ", "answer": "180873", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5135", "question": "-18457 * 63428 - 71508 * -57101 + -11458 ", "answer": "2912476254", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5136", "question": "-8914 - -9244 - 3882 - 4037 ", "answer": "-7589", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5137", "question": "669 * -242 - 899 + 629 ", "answer": "-162168", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5138", "question": "-77 - 31 + 9 * -93 * -89 ", "answer": "74385", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5139", "question": "39451 - 74032 ", "answer": "-34581", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5140", "question": "63539 * 1923 - -2371 * -6448 + -50844 ", "answer": "106846445", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5141", "question": "-51827 - -34912 ", "answer": "-16915", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5142", "question": "-829 * -2 ", "answer": "1658", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5143", "question": "-17413 + -97544 - 54183 * 50425 ", "answer": "-2732292732", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5144", "question": "-581 + -79 * -526 ", "answer": "40973", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5145", "question": "7390 * 4498 ", "answer": "33240220", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5146", "question": "-63851 * 36351 * -77288 + -18225 ", "answer": "179389134696663", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5147", "question": "9445 * 9977 + 4474 ", "answer": "94237239", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5148", "question": "468 + -310 * -980 * 894 ", "answer": "271597668", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5149", "question": "54205 + -1029 - 314 ", "answer": "52862", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5150", "question": "56820 * -58752 - -30265 ", "answer": "-3338258375", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5151", "question": "4 + -2 * -3 ", "answer": "10", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 1}
{"id": "5152", "question": "-734 * 431 * -325 ", "answer": "102815050", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5153", "question": "-521 * 767 * -133 ", "answer": "53147731", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5154", "question": "6129 - -2540 * 5239 - 9903 ", "answer": "13303286", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5155", "question": "12 + 87 * 98 ", "answer": "8538", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5156", "question": "99 - -21 - 0 * -71 ", "answer": "120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5157", "question": "256 - 756 ", "answer": "-500", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5158", "question": "-45206 * 63580 * -35926 + 3302 - 57156 ", "answer": "103258418612626", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5159", "question": "323 + -245 + 438 ", "answer": "516", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5160", "question": "571 + 733 - 616 - 924 ", "answer": "-236", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5161", "question": "-341 * -345 ", "answer": "117645", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5162", "question": "-2437 * 959165 - -786761 * -378718 ", "answer": "-300298037503", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5163", "question": "-4804 + 7562 - -8265 - 3398 + 122 ", "answer": "7747", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5164", "question": "606 - -121 + 11 + -825 ", "answer": "-87", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5165", "question": "-61 - 21 + 56 * 56 + 38 ", "answer": "3092", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5166", "question": "87 + -10 - -100 + -71 + -36 ", "answer": "70", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5167", "question": "9711 - 310 ", "answer": "9401", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5168", "question": "-70 + -38 * -79 + -60 - 57 ", "answer": "2815", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5169", "question": "-479193 - -217316 - -817985 + -909576 ", "answer": "-353468", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5170", "question": "541 * 786 * -385 - 924 * -442 ", "answer": "-163303602", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5171", "question": "48293 * -14042 ", "answer": "-678130306", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5172", "question": "-100 * 74 + 65 + -4 + -72 ", "answer": "-7411", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5173", "question": "231 * 591 ", "answer": "136521", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5174", "question": "-66 + 58 + 92 ", "answer": "84", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5175", "question": "-2 + 473 ", "answer": "471", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5176", "question": "-809 - -303 + 642 * 185 - -849 ", "answer": "119113", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5177", "question": "316 + -965 * -363 - 96 * -748 ", "answer": "422419", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5178", "question": "-6 + 683 ", "answer": "677", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5179", "question": "-38829 * -9164 ", "answer": "355828956", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5180", "question": "-520164 - 776288 + 689079 ", "answer": "-607373", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5181", "question": "-376093 + -779620 * -658681 ", "answer": "513520505127", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5182", "question": "8139 * -6999 + -477 - -481 * 4260 ", "answer": "-54916278", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5183", "question": "-2460 * 430 - -680 + -4137 ", "answer": "-1061257", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5184", "question": "65855 + 59680 - 3593 ", "answer": "121942", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5185", "question": "712 + -187 + 439 - 874 - 48 ", "answer": "42", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5186", "question": "63 * -17 + -94 - -1 * 83 ", "answer": "-1082", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5187", "question": "48 + -38 ", "answer": "10", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5188", "question": "-7514 - 1042 - -6293 + -2399 ", "answer": "-4662", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5189", "question": "132067 + 715406 - 80968 * -81294 * 960201 ", "answer": "6320247113898465", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5190", "question": "-872 + 304 - -669 - -379 ", "answer": "480", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5191", "question": "-957056 * -203976 * 672952 + -537051 + -28289 ", "answer": "131371303593099172", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5192", "question": "-3619 - -4281 ", "answer": "662", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5193", "question": "701 + 940 ", "answer": "1641", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5194", "question": "-3057 - 5297 + 1267 - -1562 ", "answer": "-5525", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5195", "question": "827166 - -718989 ", "answer": "1546155", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5196", "question": "-626 - 40599 * -97400 * 95849 ", "answer": "379019783866774", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5197", "question": "-882 + -8091 ", "answer": "-8973", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5198", "question": "77 * 95 + 44 ", "answer": "7359", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5199", "question": "-4259 * 5360 - 9109 ", "answer": "-22837349", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5200", "question": "-3 + -50 - 93 ", "answer": "-146", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5201", "question": "577 * 318 ", "answer": "183486", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5202", "question": "-551 - -127 - 175 ", "answer": "-599", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5203", "question": "42045 + -34068 + -73303 ", "answer": "-65326", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5204", "question": "600405 - -631409 * 904276 + 23637 ", "answer": "570968628926", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5205", "question": "-251 + -960 ", "answer": "-1211", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5206", "question": "55165 + 66322 * -91864 ", "answer": "-6092549043", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5207", "question": "-635401 * 839773 ", "answer": "-533592603973", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5208", "question": "-7543 - 2223 - -35611 ", "answer": "25845", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5209", "question": "-870468 + -674734 + 626130 - -795372 - 338029 ", "answer": "-461729", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5210", "question": "332 - 55 - 446 * 869 - 182 ", "answer": "-387479", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5211", "question": "72253 * -99930 - -14260 ", "answer": "-7220228030", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5212", "question": "-3454 * 9826 ", "answer": "-33939004", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5213", "question": "2197 + 9819 + -3624 + -2440 + 5987 ", "answer": "11939", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5214", "question": "90 + -53 + -44 ", "answer": "-7", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5215", "question": "102 * 914 + 552 + -646 * -219 ", "answer": "235254", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5216", "question": "-907 - 37453 ", "answer": "-38360", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5217", "question": "-57 * -33 ", "answer": "1881", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5218", "question": "-3299 + 4049 * 8864 - -5854 ", "answer": "35892891", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5219", "question": "-617 - 950 ", "answer": "-1567", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5220", "question": "99 - -64 ", "answer": "163", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5221", "question": "-99 + 58 - 42 ", "answer": "-83", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5222", "question": "-83674 - -25593 - 60868 * -70741 ", "answer": "4305805107", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5223", "question": "-24 - -33 * -6 * -39 ", "answer": "7698", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5224", "question": "-563 - -1 - 639 * 254 + 334 ", "answer": "-162534", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5225", "question": "-467 - -4344 ", "answer": "3877", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5226", "question": "-7755 + -2542 + 4468 ", "answer": "-5829", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5227", "question": "-97 - -93 - 99 + 1 + -53 ", "answer": "-155", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5228", "question": "233241 - 921593 + 902364 - 924549 ", "answer": "-710537", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5229", "question": "-98 + -29 ", "answer": "-127", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5230", "question": "-64 * 75 - 96 + 88 + 74 ", "answer": "-4734", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5231", "question": "-8257 + -8524 ", "answer": "-16781", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5232", "question": "-648460 - -133606 * -804404 ", "answer": "-107473849284", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5233", "question": "-5463 + -35215 + -24353 * 51944 ", "answer": "-1265032910", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5234", "question": "-21 + 826 + -499 * 51 * 895 ", "answer": "-22776050", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5235", "question": "82 + -70 ", "answer": "12", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5236", "question": "-975 + 5944 - -4197 + 2619 * -194 ", "answer": "-498920", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5237", "question": "-100 * 12680 * -25735 + 50401 + -37469 ", "answer": "32631992932", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5238", "question": "-528 - -564 * 931 - -185 ", "answer": "524741", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5239", "question": "95128 + 61628 + -48059 * 76358 + -87256 ", "answer": "-3669619622", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5240", "question": "-46 - 39 * -24 - 31 * -9 ", "answer": "1169", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5241", "question": "73 + 0 * -69 ", "answer": "73", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5242", "question": "41 - 4 ", "answer": "37", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5243", "question": "-7854 * 5844 * 826 ", "answer": "-37912388976", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5244", "question": "-72 + -332 - -632 + 395 - -44 ", "answer": "667", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5245", "question": "631840 + 934304 + 462861 - -753859 - -479954 ", "answer": "3262818", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5246", "question": "9423 * -2513 * 4508 * 8641 ", "answer": "-922421872086372", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5247", "question": "-88147 + 30879 - 25949 + 86103 ", "answer": "2886", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5248", "question": "-78 - 652 + 218 * -925 ", "answer": "-202380", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5249", "question": "16277 * -71677 - 15231 + 80963 - 70895 ", "answer": "-1166691692", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5250", "question": "-2048 - 8716 - 6194 ", "answer": "-16958", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5251", "question": "-54 * -64 - -66 + 22 ", "answer": "3544", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5252", "question": "-563859 + 997884 + 237304 * 762921 ", "answer": "181044639009", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5253", "question": "-705 + 352 ", "answer": "-353", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5254", "question": "5303 * -4731 - 6897 + -3168 + -5379 ", "answer": "-25103937", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5255", "question": "-313301 + -960568 + 475282 ", "answer": "-798587", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5256", "question": "746952 + -999423 ", "answer": "-252471", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5257", "question": "-24814 + -11511 * -8040 - 89678 * 78308 ", "answer": "-6929981198", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5258", "question": "4507 * 7392 * 2374 + -9387 - -6095 ", "answer": "79091572964", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5259", "question": "221910 + 179116 + -145317 * -668470 ", "answer": "97140456016", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5260", "question": "-312 + -711 ", "answer": "-1023", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5261", "question": "810149 - 596666 * -123012 ", "answer": "73397888141", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5262", "question": "-48 + 68 - 98 ", "answer": "-78", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5263", "question": "-753 + 905 * -588 - -672 + -340 ", "answer": "-532561", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5264", "question": "-93442 + -89210 * 24854 + -45499 ", "answer": "-2217364281", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5265", "question": "-96 + 63 * 3 - -38 ", "answer": "131", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5266", "question": "29 - 470 * -954 * -349 * -593 ", "answer": "92795379689", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5267", "question": "65 - 5 + 66 ", "answer": "126", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5268", "question": "-411 + 646 - -180 * 219 * 910 ", "answer": "35872435", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5269", "question": "-25574 + -83483 * -73290 - -14533 ", "answer": "6118458029", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5270", "question": "371 - -7192 * -2722 * 1377 ", "answer": "-26957010877", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5271", "question": "44 - 23 + 41 ", "answer": "62", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5272", "question": "-141 + -54 ", "answer": "-195", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5273", "question": "-43354 - 788911 + 547089 + 712551 - -401178 ", "answer": "828553", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5274", "question": "-98431 * -27524 - 2790 * 30339 - -7695 ", "answer": "2624576729", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5275", "question": "75 - 7 + -80 + -23 ", "answer": "-35", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5276", "question": "-1067 - -286 + -5002 - -5120 ", "answer": "-663", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5277", "question": "-555581 - 583860 * -377163 ", "answer": "220209833599", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5278", "question": "746395 * 369408 * -813716 + 86137 + 578957 ", "answer": "-224361261608873466", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5279", "question": "-890 - -844 - 960 - 112 - -378 ", "answer": "-740", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5280", "question": "-9432 * -11082 * 17428 ", "answer": "1821669089472", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5281", "question": "-681060 * 989482 + -995818 ", "answer": "-673897606738", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5282", "question": "-88 - -2 + -6 + 47 ", "answer": "-45", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5283", "question": "530 + -404 + -239 + 442 ", "answer": "329", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5284", "question": "-633 * -592 * 548 ", "answer": "205355328", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5285", "question": "-27 * 79 * 89 + 25 ", "answer": "-189812", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5286", "question": "40 * 98 + 47 * 12 ", "answer": "4484", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5287", "question": "-201625 - -767267 + 702299 - -624555 ", "answer": "1892496", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5288", "question": "-30 + -51 * 80 + -38 * -68 ", "answer": "-1526", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5289", "question": "-7397 - -8458 - 7843 - 4959 ", "answer": "-11741", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5290", "question": "682855 + -841182 - 788196 ", "answer": "-946523", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5291", "question": "3649 + -2127 ", "answer": "1522", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5292", "question": "-8443 + 3687 ", "answer": "-4756", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5293", "question": "-100 + 81 ", "answer": "-19", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5294", "question": "-982 * 579 - 915 * -940 ", "answer": "291522", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5295", "question": "9079 + 2707 - -9688 - -2423 - -5191 ", "answer": "29088", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5296", "question": "2274 + -734 ", "answer": "1540", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5297", "question": "16 * 54 + -82 + -30 * 27 ", "answer": "-28", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5298", "question": "-272725 + -640725 * -353695 ", "answer": "226620956150", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5299", "question": "-55 - -23 ", "answer": "-32", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5300", "question": "15 - -65 ", "answer": "80", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5301", "question": "-25 - -37 * -79 ", "answer": "-2948", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5302", "question": "-495288 - -20326 - -192147 * 995653 ", "answer": "191311262029", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5303", "question": "-562 - 66 * -315 * 434 * 30 ", "answer": "270685238", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5304", "question": "6314 + 6576 + -8018 ", "answer": "4872", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5305", "question": "625 - -960 * -512 - -13 ", "answer": "-490882", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5306", "question": "60 * 92 ", "answer": "5520", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5307", "question": "-75988 * -61556 - -84098 + -47413 ", "answer": "4677554013", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5308", "question": "-72 + 30 + -40 + 16 + -22 ", "answer": "-88", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5309", "question": "296257 * -910991 + -464282 + 400166 ", "answer": "-269887524803", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5310", "question": "-45 - 53 - 75 * 48 ", "answer": "-3698", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5311", "question": "974 + -258 - -276 ", "answer": "992", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5312", "question": "-850 * -350 + 679 * -807 * 649 ", "answer": "-355323997", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5313", "question": "-748 + -192 * 933 - -784 - -340 ", "answer": "-178760", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5314", "question": "-85404 - -69098 - 30934 - 34767 ", "answer": "-82007", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5315", "question": "-93 + 52 + -47 + 16 * 15 ", "answer": "152", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5316", "question": "55 * 210 ", "answer": "11550", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5317", "question": "-510 * 982 * -47 ", "answer": "23538540", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5318", "question": "7136 * -5012 ", "answer": "-35765632", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5319", "question": "568 + 832 * 203 - 199 ", "answer": "169265", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5320", "question": "75 + 46 + -75 ", "answer": "46", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5321", "question": "52 + 51 ", "answer": "103", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5322", "question": "-530 * 564 - -704 + 433 ", "answer": "-297783", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5323", "question": "-824 - -154 ", "answer": "-670", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5324", "question": "-1363 - 946 ", "answer": "-2309", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5325", "question": "75190 + -14543 ", "answer": "60647", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5326", "question": "-6930 - -3202 ", "answer": "-3728", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5327", "question": "-28 * 16 - -22 + -5 ", "answer": "-431", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5328", "question": "-4280 + 3886 - 8498 - 8146 ", "answer": "-17038", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5329", "question": "6849 * -4337 + 1390 ", "answer": "-29702723", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5330", "question": "-507 * -329 - -780 * 227 * -944 ", "answer": "-166977837", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5331", "question": "-933874 - 258617 + -69446 + -65939 ", "answer": "-1327876", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5332", "question": "-46471 - 64712 * 66441 ", "answer": "-4299576463", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5333", "question": "-84 * -10 * 33 + 38 ", "answer": "27758", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5334", "question": "-113980 * 370679 - 752936 ", "answer": "-42250745356", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5335", "question": "-79 + 97 ", "answer": "18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5336", "question": "-85 * 4 + -49 ", "answer": "-389", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5337", "question": "145335 + -25549 - 657249 * -401518 - 877858 ", "answer": "263896545910", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5338", "question": "6252 - 3866 * 3379 ", "answer": "-13056962", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5339", "question": "-2415 * -5465 ", "answer": "13197975", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5340", "question": "-40202 - 82341 + -40488 ", "answer": "-163031", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5341", "question": "-8130 - 6334 + 278 * 5026 - -5053 ", "answer": "1387817", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5342", "question": "5 * -434 + -876 + -17 ", "answer": "-3063", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5343", "question": "-5517 - -502 * -6253 * -7297 ", "answer": "22905321265", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5344", "question": "-544 * -862 * -871 ", "answer": "-408436288", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5345", "question": "-9482 + 3601 - 5405 + 4903 ", "answer": "-6383", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5346", "question": "212 * -7279 + -478 * 3409 ", "answer": "-3172650", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5347", "question": "-29325 - 6680 ", "answer": "-36005", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5348", "question": "978 * 740 * -70 * 978 ", "answer": "-49545871200", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5349", "question": "427 + -551 - -100 - 266 * 378 ", "answer": "-100572", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5350", "question": "530267 * -751983 ", "answer": "-398751769461", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5351", "question": "8417 + -9345 ", "answer": "-928", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5352", "question": "320028 + 297238 ", "answer": "617266", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5353", "question": "151 - -181 - -600 + -272 * -960 ", "answer": "262052", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5354", "question": "441 - -4047 - 6885 ", "answer": "-2397", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5355", "question": "-17779 + -45471 ", "answer": "-63250", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5356", "question": "-135 - 820 + 610 - -78 * -819 ", "answer": "-64227", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5357", "question": "-548 - 241 - -313 * -35 + 55 ", "answer": "-11689", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5358", "question": "262 * 978 - -429 - 592 ", "answer": "256073", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5359", "question": "-827 * -877 - -774 - -29 + 206 ", "answer": "726288", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5360", "question": "76 * 18 - -100 - 62 ", "answer": "1406", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5361", "question": "-1114 + 9952 ", "answer": "8838", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5362", "question": "263 + -981 * 971 - 696 ", "answer": "-952984", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5363", "question": "-34860 * -45430 - 39790 + 32734 * 38634 ", "answer": "2848295366", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5364", "question": "59394 - -78831 - 14948 + 42736 - -53489 ", "answer": "219502", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5365", "question": "5436 - -2480 * 1020 + 6738 + -7325 ", "answer": "2534449", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5366", "question": "262452 * -626119 + -139806 + 18647 ", "answer": "-164326304947", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5367", "question": "556486 - 156455 + -530189 ", "answer": "-130158", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5368", "question": "596 + -275 + -128 - -129 ", "answer": "322", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5369", "question": "49618 + -65452 - 84051 ", "answer": "-99885", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5370", "question": "7360 + -4137 - -4976 ", "answer": "8199", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5371", "question": "-721 * -987 + 132 - -361 + 477 ", "answer": "712597", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5372", "question": "-994695 * 233440 * 280605 - -107831 + -59788 ", "answer": "-65156930192435957", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5373", "question": "56687 * -97840 ", "answer": "-5546256080", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5374", "question": "90 + 43 * -3 * 57 * 84 ", "answer": "-617562", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5375", "question": "884 + -214 + -197 + -976 ", "answer": "-503", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5376", "question": "-266268 + -104231 + -873012 ", "answer": "-1243511", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5377", "question": "-218 * -408 + -958 + -846 - 890 ", "answer": "86250", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5378", "question": "9058 * -9690 - 9700 - 3609 ", "answer": "-87785329", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5379", "question": "-904084 - -954899 + 590228 * -944900 ", "answer": "-557706386385", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5380", "question": "5284 + 4246 + -2366 * -7811 ", "answer": "18490356", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5381", "question": "-13 + -74 * -86 + 38 ", "answer": "6389", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5382", "question": "-2333 + 3939 + 7027 * -3919 ", "answer": "-27537207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5383", "question": "97 * 52 - -53 * -6 + 21 ", "answer": "4747", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5384", "question": "-3930 * 194 - -6605 - -4416 ", "answer": "-751399", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5385", "question": "551 * -32 + -573 ", "answer": "-18205", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5386", "question": "157 - -7276 + 1517 - -3737 ", "answer": "12687", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5387", "question": "483 + 319 ", "answer": "802", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5388", "question": "473 * 181 + 727 ", "answer": "86340", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5389", "question": "66452 + 32907 * 76964 + 70660 + -7897 ", "answer": "2532783563", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5390", "question": "-933 + -493 * -675 - -413 * 363 ", "answer": "481761", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5391", "question": "-76512 - -62136 + 88822 ", "answer": "74446", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5392", "question": "-1431 * 6432 + -2444 ", "answer": "-9206636", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5393", "question": "-54 - 48 * -79 * 37 - -62 ", "answer": "140312", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5394", "question": "-530737 - -792527 * -139151 * -554337 ", "answer": "61132796886709712", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5395", "question": "54890 * -93183 ", "answer": "-5114814870", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5396", "question": "527 + -8139 ", "answer": "-7612", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5397", "question": "-296 * -187 - 325 ", "answer": "55027", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5398", "question": "-82293 - -71216 ", "answer": "-11077", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5399", "question": "-9011 * 14183 - -30039 + 9610 ", "answer": "-127763364", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5400", "question": "-96 - 27 + 55 ", "answer": "-68", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5401", "question": "9516 - -7640 + -9446 + -281 - -571 ", "answer": "8000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5402", "question": "88378 + -75093 * -55847 - -5485 + 2366 ", "answer": "4193815000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5403", "question": "456 * -805 - -799 - 802 - 564 ", "answer": "-367647", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5404", "question": "73805 - -23197 + 66904 ", "answer": "163906", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5405", "question": "-34836 - 42594 * 85083 - -10347 ", "answer": "-3624049791", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5406", "question": "-12100 + -65225 * 1040 ", "answer": "-67846100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5407", "question": "77 - -67 + -37 * -4 - -79 ", "answer": "371", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5408", "question": "652 + -937 - -447 * 82 - -767 ", "answer": "37136", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5409", "question": "-701035 + -497976 - 632398 + -686512 + 399503 ", "answer": "-2118418", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5410", "question": "79 + -36 ", "answer": "43", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5411", "question": "-601 * -589 ", "answer": "353989", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5412", "question": "-74388 * -41988 * -44918 * -77272 ", "answer": "10841032210788359424", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5413", "question": "661394 * 837094 * 283347 - 703317 * -723556 ", "answer": "156875277651738744", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5414", "question": "-577991 + 992619 + -139286 - -396709 - -171072 ", "answer": "843123", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5415", "question": "-130 * 845 * -151 ", "answer": "16587350", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5416", "question": "-876540 + -622975 ", "answer": "-1499515", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5417", "question": "842179 + -269879 ", "answer": "572300", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5418", "question": "-948 * 245 + -980 + 98 * 247 ", "answer": "-209034", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5419", "question": "-864073 * -453740 - 997743 ", "answer": "392063485277", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5420", "question": "7195 + -4335 * 846 ", "answer": "-3660215", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5421", "question": "35 - 47 + -45 ", "answer": "-57", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5422", "question": "-14638 - -97280 - -34555 ", "answer": "117197", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5423", "question": "682 + 137 * 359 ", "answer": "49865", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5424", "question": "-93829 + -75636 ", "answer": "-169465", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5425", "question": "-26 + -60 + -64 ", "answer": "-150", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5426", "question": "8936 + -88350 ", "answer": "-79414", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5427", "question": "60603 - 88723 - -99111 ", "answer": "70991", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5428", "question": "8119 * 9259 * 6341 ", "answer": "476677198961", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5429", "question": "884 + -509 ", "answer": "375", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5430", "question": "20 + -42 + 97 * 7 ", "answer": "657", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5431", "question": "92 * 61 ", "answer": "5612", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5432", "question": "-15494 + -70550 * 62300 + -7510 * 14900 ", "answer": "-4507179494", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5433", "question": "57 - 1 + 8 - 62 - 80 ", "answer": "-78", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5434", "question": "993 * -2591 - -7691 ", "answer": "-2565172", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5435", "question": "-46 * -38 - 80 ", "answer": "1668", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5436", "question": "-4445 * -5566 * 8032 + 2097 + -5224 ", "answer": "198718664713", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5437", "question": "164390 + 1161 * -108538 ", "answer": "-125848228", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5438", "question": "-227 * 405 ", "answer": "-91935", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5439", "question": "-46116 + -538350 ", "answer": "-584466", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5440", "question": "-727 * -632 ", "answer": "459464", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5441", "question": "-859 + 5852 + 7660 ", "answer": "12653", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5442", "question": "6126 + 6828 ", "answer": "12954", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5443", "question": "-2130 * -41703 - -72358 ", "answer": "88899748", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5444", "question": "-80067 * -16437 + 91607 + 89719 + -56363 ", "answer": "1316186242", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5445", "question": "787 + -349 + -613 - -197 - -112 ", "answer": "134", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5446", "question": "-36 * -4 * -58 + -93 ", "answer": "-8445", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5447", "question": "-12516 - -10122 - 68499 ", "answer": "-70893", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5448", "question": "100 - -63 ", "answer": "163", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5449", "question": "-69 + -65 - 85 - -26 ", "answer": "-193", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5450", "question": "104938 - -111220 * -268828 + 138485 - -647053 ", "answer": "-29898159684", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5451", "question": "-67 * -39 * -59 ", "answer": "-154167", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5452", "question": "-6651 + -2648 + -7877 ", "answer": "-17176", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5453", "question": "-188832 - 519389 * 808002 + -282583 ", "answer": "-419667822193", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5454", "question": "-404055 + -30464 ", "answer": "-434519", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5455", "question": "-45 + 76 ", "answer": "31", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5456", "question": "-5429 - -2024 + 4781 + 3178 ", "answer": "4554", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5457", "question": "722407 - 475903 * 176293 ", "answer": "-83897645172", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5458", "question": "9927 + -62 * -2773 - -2181 ", "answer": "184034", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5459", "question": "978 - 8956 * 6574 - 6212 ", "answer": "-58881978", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5460", "question": "-1540 * -62455 - -21933 + 25735 * 29599 ", "answer": "857932898", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5461", "question": "-70554 - 63401 ", "answer": "-133955", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5462", "question": "368 * 2904 * 8414 + 1214 * 4952 ", "answer": "8997817936", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5463", "question": "-5179 + -9790 ", "answer": "-14969", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5464", "question": "36680 - 66754 ", "answer": "-30074", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5465", "question": "-986369 + 232188 ", "answer": "-754181", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5466", "question": "-307 + -420 - 388 - -715 + -211 ", "answer": "-611", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5467", "question": "88 + -48 - -93 ", "answer": "133", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5468", "question": "-904 * -901 + 557 ", "answer": "815061", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5469", "question": "-316 - 174 ", "answer": "-490", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5470", "question": "41 - -49 - -67 - 8 * -62 ", "answer": "653", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5471", "question": "438858 * 274696 + -570804 * 469189 ", "answer": "-147262420788", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5472", "question": "-4468 * -9557 + -1337 + -8736 + 3466 ", "answer": "42694069", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5473", "question": "44657 + -5186 - 52695 + -46795 ", "answer": "-60019", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5474", "question": "433031 - -827018 * 844325 + 990674 + 423256 ", "answer": "698273819811", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5475", "question": "-25 + -21 ", "answer": "-46", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5476", "question": "-3117 + -5470 + -9546 + 2461 ", "answer": "-15672", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5477", "question": "593385 - 493987 ", "answer": "99398", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5478", "question": "-64 * 19 ", "answer": "-1216", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5479", "question": "-507 - -594 + 450 * 893 * -882 ", "answer": "-354431613", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5480", "question": "95 * -65 ", "answer": "-6175", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5481", "question": "391 - 487 * -122 - 600 + -774 ", "answer": "58431", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5482", "question": "-48 - -52 * 76 * -77 ", "answer": "-304352", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5483", "question": "100 - -96 ", "answer": "196", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5484", "question": "-171961 * -746715 ", "answer": "128405858115", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5485", "question": "-95 - 23 * 66 * 24 + 41 ", "answer": "-36486", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5486", "question": "580360 - -391663 ", "answer": "972023", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5487", "question": "11815 - 10308 + 62956 ", "answer": "64463", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5488", "question": "0 - 23 ", "answer": "-23", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5489", "question": "49 + -46 + 19 - 29 ", "answer": "-7", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5490", "question": "-12 - -41 ", "answer": "29", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5491", "question": "57 - -54 * 55 ", "answer": "3027", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5492", "question": "3901 - -9055 + -5833 - -3655 ", "answer": "10778", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5493", "question": "-918947 + 2859 - 898178 + 420266 + 873336 ", "answer": "-520664", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5494", "question": "993 * -382 * -820 + 908 + 133 ", "answer": "311048361", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5495", "question": "-831158 * 393464 * -77060 + -530077 * 898001 ", "answer": "25200513686426643", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5496", "question": "52149 * -72652 ", "answer": "-3788729148", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5497", "question": "28748 + -29321 + -20704 + 50283 ", "answer": "29006", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5498", "question": "65 * -68 - -99 * 44 ", "answer": "-64", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5499", "question": "-81 * -949 - -741 ", "answer": "77610", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5500", "question": "-979006 - -543128 + 985257 - -751932 - 614282 ", "answer": "687029", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5501", "question": "-745 + 118 - -70 ", "answer": "-557", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5502", "question": "-624255 - -997202 + -217913 + -146872 + -470394 ", "answer": "-462232", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5503", "question": "71 * -90 + -16 * 75 ", "answer": "-7590", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5504", "question": "791052 + -23927 - 739479 + -957033 + -149803 ", "answer": "-1079190", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5505", "question": "178 * -91 * -950 + -913 - 288 ", "answer": "15386899", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5506", "question": "-837 - 166 + 66 ", "answer": "-937", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5507", "question": "57 + 99 - -30 - -58 + 94 ", "answer": "338", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5508", "question": "51 - 25 - -68 ", "answer": "94", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5509", "question": "-5782 * -8819 ", "answer": "50991458", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5510", "question": "824309 + 653387 + 541904 - 745950 - -924987 ", "answer": "2198637", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5511", "question": "909 - -683 * -132 + 996 - 5 ", "answer": "-88256", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5512", "question": "-52136 * -74999 + 93266 ", "answer": "3910241130", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5513", "question": "32 * 704 - 175 - 763 ", "answer": "21590", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5514", "question": "67552 + -88915 ", "answer": "-21363", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5515", "question": "586 + 7684 - 5578 - 8522 - 7618 ", "answer": "-13448", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5516", "question": "-70396 * -89933 ", "answer": "6330923468", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5517", "question": "517 + 20 ", "answer": "537", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5518", "question": "19259 * 16067 + -45320 ", "answer": "309389033", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5519", "question": "6539 * -81 ", "answer": "-529659", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5520", "question": "268 + 233 ", "answer": "501", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5521", "question": "-820 * -987 + -80 * -309 - -262 ", "answer": "834322", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5522", "question": "455 - -684 - -422 - 94 ", "answer": "1467", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5523", "question": "-184365 - 829980 - -408909 * -205130 - -382833 ", "answer": "-83880134682", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5524", "question": "-3137 * -8909 * 5603 + 3304 ", "answer": "156590030703", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5525", "question": "49 * 61 * 6 - -86 * 85 ", "answer": "25244", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5526", "question": "6965 - 4645 + 8967 * -7287 ", "answer": "-65340209", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5527", "question": "5510 - -8690 - 9874 + 8548 ", "answer": "12874", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5528", "question": "-426832 - 942575 * -238396 + -215390 ", "answer": "224705467478", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5529", "question": "543064 + 876447 - -270732 - 250116 + 632478 ", "answer": "2072605", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5530", "question": "-996433 + 634932 ", "answer": "-361501", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5531", "question": "982 * -964 ", "answer": "-946648", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5532", "question": "9559 * 6337 ", "answer": "60575383", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5533", "question": "472746 - 623842 + 49706 ", "answer": "-101390", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5534", "question": "67073 * 93206 * 83662 ", "answer": "523021864351156", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5535", "question": "-14 - 67 + -51 * -9 ", "answer": "378", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5536", "question": "-560285 - -26252 - 588314 * 789913 ", "answer": "-464717410715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5537", "question": "567112 - -951541 * -805733 - 193515 * 804771 ", "answer": "-922422677506", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5538", "question": "-3985 * 1730 ", "answer": "-6894050", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5539", "question": "606 - 752 ", "answer": "-146", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5540", "question": "-24397 + 87055 ", "answer": "62658", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5541", "question": "419136 + 303094 ", "answer": "722230", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5542", "question": "76 + 48 ", "answer": "124", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5543", "question": "15 * 62 - -34 - 72 ", "answer": "892", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5544", "question": "878106 * 293552 * 966935 * 418415 + -412563 ", "answer": "104288522408484635196237", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5545", "question": "789746 * -909021 ", "answer": "-717895698666", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5546", "question": "53312 + -89559 + 18214 * -93571 - 60157 ", "answer": "-1704398598", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5547", "question": "7905 + -3868 ", "answer": "4037", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5548", "question": "478 - 333 * -864 + -152 + 754 ", "answer": "288792", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5549", "question": "3424 + -8960 * -3001 ", "answer": "26892384", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5550", "question": "7017 - -63514 * 51834 - 4799 - 73580 ", "answer": "3292113314", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5551", "question": "-42 + -924 * -443 * -38 ", "answer": "-15554658", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5552", "question": "4126 - -8020 + 4406 ", "answer": "16552", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5553", "question": "94077 - 77460 * 39687 * 16731 ", "answer": "-51433687545543", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5554", "question": "-677 * 392 * -558 * -60 ", "answer": "-8885056320", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5555", "question": "639926 - -299573 - -982671 - 202462 ", "answer": "1719708", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5556", "question": "-3370 * 3021 + -146 * -2411 * -1305 ", "answer": "-469548600", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5557", "question": "-1868 - -3551 + -1381 ", "answer": "302", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5558", "question": "439 * -961 * -627 ", "answer": "264518133", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5559", "question": "719 * -994 - 434 ", "answer": "-715120", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5560", "question": "73 * 15 ", "answer": "1095", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5561", "question": "34357 - -31087 - 39775 ", "answer": "25669", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5562", "question": "510 - -462 * -835 ", "answer": "-385260", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5563", "question": "-5692 * 6205 ", "answer": "-35318860", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5564", "question": "-604583 * -996855 ", "answer": "602681586465", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5565", "question": "-9570 - 85 + -4709 + -8159 ", "answer": "-22523", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5566", "question": "-28577 + -22107 ", "answer": "-50684", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5567", "question": "-686865 - -774621 * -490767 + -762945 * 579 ", "answer": "-380600856327", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5568", "question": "-760 + 782 * 53 + 386 ", "answer": "41072", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5569", "question": "89062 + 48445 * -54925 - 3207 ", "answer": "-2660755770", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5570", "question": "-384 * 668 + -964 ", "answer": "-257476", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5571", "question": "556 * 8 - 672 * 92 ", "answer": "-57376", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5572", "question": "35 + -71 + 77 * 97 + 54 ", "answer": "7487", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5573", "question": "95618 + 69759 ", "answer": "165377", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5574", "question": "-5008 + 5757 * -2892 - -4745 ", "answer": "-16649507", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5575", "question": "297 + 126 * -101 ", "answer": "-12429", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5576", "question": "36 - -94 + -48 ", "answer": "82", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5577", "question": "776214 + -501149 ", "answer": "275065", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5578", "question": "96922 + -88545 ", "answer": "8377", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5579", "question": "-9301 * 3547 ", "answer": "-32990647", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5580", "question": "-99 - -48 + 51 ", "answer": "0", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5581", "question": "-880 - -521 + 601 + -328 + -52 ", "answer": "-138", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5582", "question": "52561 - 38264 * 82589 - -43687 ", "answer": "-3160089248", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5583", "question": "-469 + -251 * -680 * 676 - 799 ", "answer": "115378412", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5584", "question": "99329 - -12041 - 97761 ", "answer": "13609", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5585", "question": "18579 * -42485 + 78070 + 37039 - 71101 ", "answer": "-789284807", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5586", "question": "-566 + 350 ", "answer": "-216", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5587", "question": "-982364 - -252483 ", "answer": "-729881", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5588", "question": "-60626 + -33669 ", "answer": "-94295", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5589", "question": "-950 * 393 - -311 ", "answer": "-373039", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5590", "question": "46750 - 30342 ", "answer": "16408", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5591", "question": "-5317 + 1031 + 9980 ", "answer": "5694", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5592", "question": "18 * 61 - -72 - 4 - 68 ", "answer": "1098", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5593", "question": "-701 * 376 ", "answer": "-263576", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5594", "question": "-79164 * 36144 + 50391 ", "answer": "-2861253225", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5595", "question": "-48 * 57 - 48 ", "answer": "-2784", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5596", "question": "-20447 - -73385 * -51485 + 42054 + -41162 ", "answer": "-3778246280", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5597", "question": "25 + -41 + -11 ", "answer": "-27", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5598", "question": "-66249 * -69744 - 4610 * 51762 - -28087 ", "answer": "4381875523", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5599", "question": "-2572 * -3248 - 2350 - 1869 ", "answer": "8349637", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5600", "question": "23320 - 79074 - 77129 + -81511 + -74142 ", "answer": "-288536", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5601", "question": "-895 + -44 * 440 ", "answer": "-20255", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5602", "question": "8641 + 2725 * -331 ", "answer": "-893334", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5603", "question": "838265 + -113182 - 822339 * 309558 + -282640 ", "answer": "-254561173719", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5604", "question": "185 * -512 - 777 + -530 ", "answer": "-96027", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5605", "question": "4615 - 1296 ", "answer": "3319", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5606", "question": "6856 + -55687 + 87086 - -63886 * 71364 ", "answer": "4559198759", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5607", "question": "-251770 - 899230 - -720032 ", "answer": "-430968", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5608", "question": "-38 - -33 ", "answer": "-5", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5609", "question": "247154 * 530858 ", "answer": "131203678132", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5610", "question": "-45 - -67 - -85 + -90 * 11 ", "answer": "-883", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5611", "question": "23602 + -80722 * 8783 * -52893 + -20556 ", "answer": "37500149279164", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5612", "question": "-49356 - -62411 + -71300 * 24072 ", "answer": "-1716320545", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5613", "question": "3594 * 1051 + -348 - 576 + 3481 ", "answer": "3779851", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5614", "question": "-14 - 53 * -50 ", "answer": "2636", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5615", "question": "6162 + -239 ", "answer": "5923", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5616", "question": "760 * -473 + 830 ", "answer": "-358650", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5617", "question": "682350 + -611687 * 717429 + -338722 - -538864 ", "answer": "-438841110231", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5618", "question": "-58 * -503 - -404 ", "answer": "29578", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5619", "question": "88771 - -43789 + -79409 + -41602 ", "answer": "11549", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5620", "question": "-567246 * -424565 - 203268 + 839101 ", "answer": "240833433823", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5621", "question": "-128566 + -625787 ", "answer": "-754353", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5622", "question": "-236 - 859 ", "answer": "-1095", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5623", "question": "30708 + -48081 - -39881 ", "answer": "22508", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5624", "question": "-1284 - 8804 + 2881 - 5219 - 4974 ", "answer": "-17400", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5625", "question": "-705 * 431 - -462 + 570 + -866 ", "answer": "-303689", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5626", "question": "-80 * -14 ", "answer": "1120", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5627", "question": "297103 + 230169 + 256913 ", "answer": "784185", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5628", "question": "-308078 + 671687 - -791996 - 101749 + -564385 ", "answer": "489471", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5629", "question": "-5942 - 7078 * -1143 + -8900 ", "answer": "8075312", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5630", "question": "327 + 765 ", "answer": "1092", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5631", "question": "-5060 + 6378 - -24272 * 52191 ", "answer": "1266781270", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5632", "question": "48 * -43 * -71 + 100 ", "answer": "146644", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5633", "question": "-5803 * 7996 * 3377 ", "answer": "-156695461076", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5634", "question": "-7 * -8 + 17 ", "answer": "73", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5635", "question": "-14801 + 277114 * -514517 ", "answer": "-142579878739", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5636", "question": "-27 + -81 - -62 ", "answer": "-46", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5637", "question": "-442657 + 922054 - 877934 - -632615 * -73717 ", "answer": "-46634878492", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5638", "question": "4814 + 5440 + 4313 - 9523 + -6563 ", "answer": "-1519", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5639", "question": "78 - 68 - -28 + 70 + -56 ", "answer": "52", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5640", "question": "944 - -292 * -448 ", "answer": "-129872", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5641", "question": "92997 * 25471 - -67179 * 74750 - -12412 ", "answer": "7390369249", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5642", "question": "-733022 * -197966 * 977128 * -862984 ", "answer": "-122366297459766894363904", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5643", "question": "81 - -87 - 56 * 19 * -37 ", "answer": "39536", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5644", "question": "529 - 813 * -27 * 235 ", "answer": "5159014", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5645", "question": "-2598 * 226 + 6295 ", "answer": "-580853", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5646", "question": "-4768 + 3319 * 8755 * -9132 * 1809 ", "answer": "-480029439141628", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5647", "question": "-5911 + 4974 * 9311 - 4233 + -2090 ", "answer": "46300680", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5648", "question": "95 - 94 * 17 * 71 ", "answer": "-113363", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5649", "question": "-36 * -19 - -8 + 31 ", "answer": "723", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5650", "question": "-961 + -198 - 544 ", "answer": "-1703", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5651", "question": "-256 * -396 - 688 * 671 ", "answer": "-360272", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5652", "question": "395 + 25 * 101 * -491 + -432 ", "answer": "-1239812", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5653", "question": "29792 - 83936 ", "answer": "-54144", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5654", "question": "87 * -46 * -47 + 86 + 49 ", "answer": "188229", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5655", "question": "117 * 652 - -126 + 555 ", "answer": "76965", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5656", "question": "-4395 - -4900 + -8620 - -7911 ", "answer": "-204", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5657", "question": "8611 + 4085 - -8239 ", "answer": "20935", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5658", "question": "-82 + -301 * 149 * -169 + -506 ", "answer": "7578893", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5659", "question": "-390066 + 865130 * -879367 - 760400 - -680313 ", "answer": "-760767242863", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5660", "question": "-6 + -37 + 32 - -94 ", "answer": "83", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5661", "question": "332613 + -399709 + 959707 * -665011 ", "answer": "-638215778873", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5662", "question": "80 + 82 - 30 - 44 ", "answer": "88", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5663", "question": "-8360 + 2790 * -6309 * 2001 ", "answer": "-35221830470", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5664", "question": "-2183 + 7370 ", "answer": "5187", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5665", "question": "11438 + 31710 * -74045 + -93219 * -37408 ", "answer": "1139180840", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5666", "question": "97081 + -77578 * 16411 + -81653 + 59504 ", "answer": "-1273057626", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5667", "question": "21 - 17 + 17 + 35 * -15 ", "answer": "-504", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5668", "question": "-257 + -761 ", "answer": "-1018", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5669", "question": "-612 - -920 * -850 - -556 - 482 ", "answer": "-782538", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5670", "question": "-64 - -22 * -82 + 24 ", "answer": "-1844", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5671", "question": "-50058 * 53564 ", "answer": "-2681306712", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5672", "question": "-97530 * 909253 - 527392 ", "answer": "-88679972482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5673", "question": "-209482 - -81351 * -678596 + -849261 - -43340 ", "answer": "-55205478599", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5674", "question": "-859580 - -740225 + -86204 - -182748 ", "answer": "-22811", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5675", "question": "4111 * -40099 * -14351 - 64834 * -3666 ", "answer": "2365956820583", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5676", "question": "310652 - -174214 + 315092 ", "answer": "799958", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5677", "question": "36 * -6 - -84 * 52 ", "answer": "4152", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5678", "question": "-6914 - 87003 * -54493 ", "answer": "4741047565", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5679", "question": "-2239 * 1910 + -2938 + -1109 * 5311 ", "answer": "-10169327", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5680", "question": "-18706 * 68973 * -2795 * -26021 ", "answer": "-93835212338075910", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5681", "question": "4996 * -9362 * 8307 - -4355 ", "answer": "-388539585109", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5682", "question": "3308 - -7277 ", "answer": "10585", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5683", "question": "1870 + -6107 - 4873 ", "answer": "-9110", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5684", "question": "-723291 - 244405 * 416324 ", "answer": "-101752390511", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5685", "question": "7 - 60 ", "answer": "-53", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5686", "question": "472164 + -673520 - -47339 ", "answer": "-154017", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5687", "question": "-406330 - -808127 ", "answer": "401797", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5688", "question": "-643001 + 721220 - 883836 * 539280 ", "answer": "-476634999861", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5689", "question": "207776 + -316088 * -783380 ", "answer": "247617225216", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5690", "question": "-74 * 91 ", "answer": "-6734", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5691", "question": "67195 + -123402 + 661356 - 742544 + -622427 ", "answer": "-759822", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5692", "question": "88 - 74 - 9 ", "answer": "5", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5693", "question": "-29149 * -200889 ", "answer": "5855713461", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5694", "question": "55257 * 93412 + 26410 - -95306 ", "answer": "5161788600", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5695", "question": "556676 * 973159 * -299557 ", "answer": "-162280289568248588", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5696", "question": "669729 - 468687 + -580260 * -841532 ", "answer": "488307559362", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5697", "question": "-898814 * -955190 * -480477 - 992632 ", "answer": "-412507832132795452", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5698", "question": "41 - 213 + 265 - 878 - 939 ", "answer": "-1724", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5699", "question": "6927 * 2819 * -1976 ", "answer": "-38585772888", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5700", "question": "513 + -522 + -982 * 789 + -144 ", "answer": "-774951", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5701", "question": "93984 - 511037 - -536192 ", "answer": "119139", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5702", "question": "25 + 29 - -6 - -66 * 17 ", "answer": "1182", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5703", "question": "-37 + 83 - 32 + 35 - 11 ", "answer": "38", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5704", "question": "693572 + -954282 ", "answer": "-260710", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5705", "question": "534 * 631 * -336 * -856 - 463 ", "answer": "96913361201", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5706", "question": "-6 * -70 ", "answer": "420", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5707", "question": "-21 + -89 ", "answer": "-110", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5708", "question": "48 * 63 + 35 - 85 ", "answer": "2974", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5709", "question": "596 * 68 ", "answer": "40528", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5710", "question": "-276408 - 266821 ", "answer": "-543229", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5711", "question": "-85740 + 64693 ", "answer": "-21047", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5712", "question": "-69666 - -98359 ", "answer": "28693", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5713", "question": "797882 + 404305 + 898453 * 644496 * 617531 ", "answer": "357580933226347515", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5714", "question": "-577095 * 955521 + -609403 ", "answer": "-551427000898", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5715", "question": "-78 * 67 * -61 - -46 * -28 ", "answer": "317498", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5716", "question": "5671 * 7017 + -1147 ", "answer": "39792260", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5717", "question": "2 + -95 - 63 + -86 - 73 ", "answer": "-315", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5718", "question": "-202 * 558 ", "answer": "-112716", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5719", "question": "4431 - 119 - -5924 ", "answer": "10236", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5720", "question": "-84558 * -78903 - 82783 ", "answer": "6671797091", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5721", "question": "91116 - 11395 * 26861 - -67070 ", "answer": "-305922909", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5722", "question": "-7172 - 8995 - -6023 ", "answer": "-10144", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5723", "question": "552 - -642 - -605 * 510 * -107 ", "answer": "-33013656", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5724", "question": "582237 + 522449 ", "answer": "1104686", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5725", "question": "-1384 * -7565 + 881 * -8015 - 6663 ", "answer": "3402082", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5726", "question": "214346 * -13735 * -451354 * -189006 ", "answer": "-251152169388519586440", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5727", "question": "812452 - 202130 * 437282 ", "answer": "-88386998208", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5728", "question": "20 * -68 ", "answer": "-1360", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5729", "question": "-405537 * 652366 ", "answer": "-264558550542", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5730", "question": "7463 - -2806 + 8368 * -1774 ", "answer": "-14834563", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5731", "question": "-475 - 710 - 569 ", "answer": "-1754", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5732", "question": "56753 * -205182 - 787109 * 504721 * -118960 ", "answer": "47259280086733394", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5733", "question": "536 * -896 - -499 * 163 ", "answer": "-398919", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5734", "question": "-395048 + 115185 * -976202 ", "answer": "-112444222418", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5735", "question": "-226 + -6139 + 2942 * -55 ", "answer": "-168175", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5736", "question": "4808 + 7029 - -391 - 4042 * -6313 ", "answer": "25529374", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5737", "question": "-45 * 82 + -25 - -95 + -41 ", "answer": "-3661", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5738", "question": "2534 + 3575 - -7634 * -3955 * -4658 ", "answer": "140636531369", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5739", "question": "-123 * -80 + -192 ", "answer": "9648", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5740", "question": "-6 - -12 * -14 ", "answer": "-174", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5741", "question": "-85481 * -53065 + -41312 ", "answer": "4536007953", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5742", "question": "11949 + 45082 * 32498 ", "answer": "1465086785", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5743", "question": "206 - -763 + 513 ", "answer": "1482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5744", "question": "-912203 * 439382 ", "answer": "-400805578546", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5745", "question": "674297 + -135166 * 317309 + 424584 * 857714 ", "answer": "321282926979", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5746", "question": "-44 + -67 ", "answer": "-111", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5747", "question": "62289 * 63983 - 60808 ", "answer": "3985376279", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5748", "question": "-631 * -397 ", "answer": "250507", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5749", "question": "-64879 + -28244 * 83759 + 11230 ", "answer": "-2365742845", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5750", "question": "9464 * 52321 + 82507 - -61623 - -98796 ", "answer": "495408870", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5751", "question": "-2632 - -7525 ", "answer": "4893", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5752", "question": "3129 - 4276 - -7390 ", "answer": "6243", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5753", "question": "-64758 * 26071 ", "answer": "-1688305818", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5754", "question": "247 * 697 + -422 + 371 - -512 ", "answer": "172620", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5755", "question": "-36205 + 22862 - 34915 ", "answer": "-48258", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5756", "question": "-66467 + -85976 ", "answer": "-152443", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5757", "question": "-7065 + 8836 + -5636 * 7916 - -8838 ", "answer": "-44603967", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5758", "question": "2334 - 4032 * 5312 - -4981 * -7649 ", "answer": "-59515319", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5759", "question": "-492122 * -993963 - 825835 + -404063 ", "answer": "489149829588", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5760", "question": "9614 + -2890 * 3848 - -3842 ", "answer": "-11107264", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5761", "question": "-79892 + 76610 - -38762 - 4699 ", "answer": "30781", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5762", "question": "-888325 + 926097 + -718677 + 343304 * -34121 ", "answer": "-11714556689", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5763", "question": "-23 - 67 - -39 ", "answer": "-51", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5764", "question": "2367 * 3260 ", "answer": "7716420", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5765", "question": "834065 * -194673 + -671429 - 52060 - 160645 ", "answer": "-162370819879", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5766", "question": "5187 * -3891 * 3152 + 7749 - -9855 ", "answer": "-63615591180", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5767", "question": "-982 * -604 ", "answer": "593128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5768", "question": "750 * 416 + -126 - -454 - 250 ", "answer": "312078", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5769", "question": "-25901 + 81604 + 10830 - -77139 ", "answer": "143672", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5770", "question": "-6730 + -6043 + -9151 * -2908 - 2392 ", "answer": "26595943", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5771", "question": "-173353 - -4126 + 196877 * -456655 * 1191 ", "answer": "-107076696093312", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5772", "question": "-973312 - -881012 * -845459 ", "answer": "-744860497820", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5773", "question": "106241 - 490400 * 904725 - -412053 * 669616 ", "answer": "-167759752111", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5774", "question": "-35336 + -99640 ", "answer": "-134976", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5775", "question": "123 * 489 ", "answer": "60147", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5776", "question": "-317705 + 521077 * -905278 - 858974 * -226988 ", "answer": "-276743071799", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5777", "question": "-97090 - -89011 + 63734 + -30477 ", "answer": "25178", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5778", "question": "-52664 + -93319 + 7238 + 93550 - 6654 ", "answer": "-51849", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5779", "question": "-288107 - 979739 + 839200 * -928719 * -439281 ", "answer": "342367258382660954", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5780", "question": "86899 - 384855 ", "answer": "-297956", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5781", "question": "-41376 - 95351 * -50706 - -72802 * -66498 ", "answer": "-6360966", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5782", "question": "-97714 - -48088 ", "answer": "-49626", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5783", "question": "100 * 605 ", "answer": "60500", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5784", "question": "-3281 + -9522 + -2590 + -1295 * -5616 ", "answer": "7257327", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5785", "question": "-1056 * 843 - 8604 - 327 * -1127 ", "answer": "-530283", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5786", "question": "-73 * 100 + -7 - 18 + -39 ", "answer": "-7364", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5787", "question": "-9946 + 54572 - 68570 ", "answer": "-23944", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5788", "question": "-82 - -94 * -7 + -55 + -85 ", "answer": "-880", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5789", "question": "654810 - -89183 + 868298 + 904467 ", "answer": "2516758", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5790", "question": "-11602 * 73826 * 23171 * 84852 * -11294 ", "answer": "19019401364028906724896", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5791", "question": "460869 + -482457 ", "answer": "-21588", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5792", "question": "1340 * 157 - 8937 ", "answer": "201443", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5793", "question": "42451 - -63386 - 2142 ", "answer": "103695", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5794", "question": "698 + 6741 ", "answer": "7439", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5795", "question": "-857 - 425 - 991 * 460 * -314 ", "answer": "143138758", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5796", "question": "-811468 + -238431 ", "answer": "-1049899", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5797", "question": "50061 - -10093 - 99503 * 56492 - 8654 ", "answer": "-5621071976", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5798", "question": "51441 + 8156 + -16413 * 42602 ", "answer": "-699167029", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5799", "question": "387 - -74 ", "answer": "461", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5800", "question": "-486 + 562 + -804 ", "answer": "-728", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5801", "question": "155 * -29 - -286 ", "answer": "-4209", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5802", "question": "14 + -65 - -88 ", "answer": "37", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5803", "question": "-19 * 90 - 24 + -34 * -74 ", "answer": "782", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5804", "question": "-4108 - -9951 - 3264 - 9149 * -8693 ", "answer": "79534836", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5805", "question": "86673 - 23587 * -66250 + -33166 ", "answer": "1562692257", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5806", "question": "12961 - 97538 - 99403 + 43934 - -98592 ", "answer": "-41454", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5807", "question": "-118750 * 782772 * 59099 - 38283 + -740218 ", "answer": "-5493498789103501", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5808", "question": "36341 + -84782 + -16653 + -59032 ", "answer": "-124126", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5809", "question": "16842 + 31478 ", "answer": "48320", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5810", "question": "-102 * -123 * -976 - -463 ", "answer": "-12244433", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5811", "question": "8045 + 2086 + 8056 ", "answer": "18187", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5812", "question": "92 + -17 - 15 * -98 * 96 ", "answer": "141195", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5813", "question": "2261 - 9916 - 3498 + 2105 * -4083 ", "answer": "-8605868", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5814", "question": "-56 + -38 - 76 + -93 ", "answer": "-263", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5815", "question": "61984 - -48633 + 9422 + 93312 * 11539 ", "answer": "1076847207", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5816", "question": "-707641 + -159342 + 959924 * 67830 + -656604 ", "answer": "65110121333", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5817", "question": "-70 * 66 - -62 ", "answer": "-4558", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5818", "question": "7937 + -9659 + 852 ", "answer": "-870", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5819", "question": "316326 * -381705 * -540029 + -635457 ", "answer": "65204838100823613", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5820", "question": "536631 * -811907 ", "answer": "-435694465317", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5821", "question": "-25751 + -80648 + 67507 + -35548 ", "answer": "-74440", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5822", "question": "7691 * 6298 + 4405 * -2893 + -4028 ", "answer": "35690225", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5823", "question": "40605 + 56819 - 24435 * 47620 * 69115 ", "answer": "-80421847593076", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5824", "question": "2103 + 729 - 2438 ", "answer": "394", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5825", "question": "96 - -64 + -99 + 47 * 28 ", "answer": "1377", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5826", "question": "34755 + -29703 + 28473 ", "answer": "33525", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5827", "question": "2790 + 803 + -8182 * -7757 + -4679 ", "answer": "63466688", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5828", "question": "4480 - -6853 - -9644 + -9776 - -8464 ", "answer": "19665", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5829", "question": "11 * -67 - -3 ", "answer": "-734", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5830", "question": "-624 - -433 * -674 - -317 + -416 ", "answer": "-292565", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5831", "question": "4 + 59 ", "answer": "63", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5832", "question": "1702 * -1473 * 1814 * 6718 ", "answer": "-30551995740792", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5833", "question": "38149 * 97392 + -76850 ", "answer": "3715330558", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5834", "question": "-791 * -527 + -221 * -189 + 666 ", "answer": "459292", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5835", "question": "548584 + 166405 * -980628 ", "answer": "-163180853756", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5836", "question": "-405 * -164 ", "answer": "66420", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5837", "question": "62 + 12 ", "answer": "74", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5838", "question": "-2873 * 9337 ", "answer": "-26825201", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5839", "question": "108 * 554 + -353 - 739 - -987 ", "answer": "59727", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5840", "question": "-53 + 66 ", "answer": "13", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5841", "question": "391707 - 143528 ", "answer": "248179", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5842", "question": "-586 - -484 + 348 ", "answer": "246", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5843", "question": "-5600 * 9611 * 3838 ", "answer": "-206567300800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5844", "question": "30 * 69 - -33 * -78 ", "answer": "-504", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5845", "question": "-48 + -64 + -60 + -3 + -61 ", "answer": "-236", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5846", "question": "-836408 + -557724 * -434217 ", "answer": "242172405700", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5847", "question": "-30645 - -44390 * -72902 ", "answer": "-3236150425", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5848", "question": "86 + -72 * -18 ", "answer": "1382", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5849", "question": "-43 + 72 * -63 + 13 ", "answer": "-4566", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5850", "question": "-518086 - -724868 - 800462 ", "answer": "-593680", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5851", "question": "-95219 + 3184 ", "answer": "-92035", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5852", "question": "-4623 + 8417 ", "answer": "3794", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5853", "question": "51 - 8 * -43 * -24 - 7 ", "answer": "-8212", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5854", "question": "8418 + 7681 ", "answer": "16099", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5855", "question": "150 - -323 - 922 ", "answer": "-449", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5856", "question": "-40296 - -88226 - -66682 ", "answer": "114612", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5857", "question": "-217 * 198 - -672 - -780 ", "answer": "-41514", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5858", "question": "73 - 62 ", "answer": "11", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5859", "question": "-27 - -95 * 45 ", "answer": "4248", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5860", "question": "211656 * -615674 - 521079 ", "answer": "-130311617223", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5861", "question": "875 - -1120 - 1544 * 5758 * -889 ", "answer": "7903524923", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5862", "question": "89 - 14 ", "answer": "75", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5863", "question": "99080 + 93518 - -22784 + -22966 * 34086 ", "answer": "-782603694", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5864", "question": "-50 - 65 - 91 + 55 ", "answer": "-151", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5865", "question": "118293 * 608102 - -578817 ", "answer": "71934788703", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5866", "question": "-316121 * 369324 - 361916 + -994779 ", "answer": "-116752428899", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5867", "question": "5158 * 127 + -1851 * -3723 - 6933 ", "answer": "7539406", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5868", "question": "3313 - -2404 ", "answer": "5717", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5869", "question": "-69619 * 39254 * 94711 + 62505 ", "answer": "-258828515206181", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5870", "question": "954270 + -149403 ", "answer": "804867", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5871", "question": "243 * -749 ", "answer": "-182007", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5872", "question": "1064 + -3321 + -3234 * 5667 ", "answer": "-18329335", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5873", "question": "53795 + -56410 ", "answer": "-2615", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5874", "question": "-48 + 12 ", "answer": "-36", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5875", "question": "976 - -9135 - -1444 ", "answer": "11555", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5876", "question": "4052 * -4168 * -5096 ", "answer": "86064998656", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5877", "question": "54975 + -91410 - -37004 ", "answer": "569", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5878", "question": "3459 * 5719 * 5036 - 2791 ", "answer": "99622254965", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5879", "question": "36870 - 40121 + 25067 ", "answer": "21816", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5880", "question": "19146 + 97616 - -84042 - -80133 ", "answer": "280937", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5881", "question": "-4878 - -8854 * 9785 + 8662 ", "answer": "86640174", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5882", "question": "-108 + 846 * -690 ", "answer": "-583848", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5883", "question": "-683309 - -440556 ", "answer": "-242753", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5884", "question": "809 - 529 - 794 + 439 ", "answer": "-75", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5885", "question": "-638 - -862 ", "answer": "224", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5886", "question": "-67 - -17 ", "answer": "-50", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5887", "question": "-44 + -11 + -88 ", "answer": "-143", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5888", "question": "-337031 * 575048 ", "answer": "-193809002488", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5889", "question": "602 + 8349 * 5111 ", "answer": "42672341", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5890", "question": "61 * 73 + 52 + -64 * -37 ", "answer": "6873", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5891", "question": "4172 + -1724 + -6374 ", "answer": "-3926", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5892", "question": "-1566 - 8205 - -3555 * -1286 ", "answer": "-4581501", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5893", "question": "154 - 597 - 22 + 59 ", "answer": "-406", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5894", "question": "597 + -242 * 737 + 949 ", "answer": "-176808", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5895", "question": "-76 + 0 * -60 + 8 ", "answer": "-68", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5896", "question": "7 * -32 - -77 + -95 ", "answer": "-242", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5897", "question": "2290 * 7477 - -6946 + 8762 * -3431 ", "answer": "-12933146", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5898", "question": "7848 * 8761 ", "answer": "68756328", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5899", "question": "301387 + 170252 - -952300 ", "answer": "1423939", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5900", "question": "-54779 - 62932 + 99622 ", "answer": "-18089", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5901", "question": "437240 - -489443 ", "answer": "926683", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5902", "question": "-37255 - 21712 ", "answer": "-58967", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5903", "question": "-99 * 583 ", "answer": "-57717", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5904", "question": "-636709 * -830216 ", "answer": "528605999144", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5905", "question": "47 + -60 + 87 ", "answer": "74", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5906", "question": "6494 + 2247 ", "answer": "8741", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5907", "question": "-229 + 769 * 225 * 654 - 313 ", "answer": "113157808", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5908", "question": "88 * -54 ", "answer": "-4752", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5909", "question": "4289 - 9214 ", "answer": "-4925", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5910", "question": "-95060 * -83646 - -52180 - 68766 - -68645 ", "answer": "7951440819", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5911", "question": "72 - -378 + 968 + -403 + -843 ", "answer": "172", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5912", "question": "-3850 + -356 - -436 ", "answer": "-3770", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5913", "question": "71376 - 92029 - -84125 * 13743 ", "answer": "1156109222", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5914", "question": "-256088 + 60595 + 256173 ", "answer": "60680", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5915", "question": "-638445 + -881066 - -526967 + -517347 ", "answer": "-1509891", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5916", "question": "-720688 - -428281 - 186623 * 970353 ", "answer": "-181090480326", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5917", "question": "-16 * 55 - 74 * 27 ", "answer": "-2878", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5918", "question": "784799 + 28043 - -885889 ", "answer": "1698731", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5919", "question": "-249973 * 726605 ", "answer": "-181631631665", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5920", "question": "-50 + -36 + 70 * -71 ", "answer": "-5056", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5921", "question": "506 - -935 + 161 * 182 ", "answer": "30743", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5922", "question": "2770 - -4016 * -2761 * 510 ", "answer": "-5654966990", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5923", "question": "-910317 + 667240 + 922244 - -373036 - -13790 ", "answer": "1065993", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5924", "question": "-679762 - 428296 + 818815 ", "answer": "-289243", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5925", "question": "222 + 426 - -117 * -527 ", "answer": "-61011", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5926", "question": "-4921 - 1720 - -7002 * -9058 - 1127 ", "answer": "-63431884", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5927", "question": "-2598 - -44962 * -48875 - 77372 ", "answer": "-2197597720", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5928", "question": "-983097 - 870321 ", "answer": "-1853418", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5929", "question": "-72647 * 89762 ", "answer": "-6520940014", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5930", "question": "913419 + 149061 - 580240 - -614698 ", "answer": "1096938", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5931", "question": "534261 * 321180 + 610587 * -696647 ", "answer": "-253769653809", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5932", "question": "51 * 6 + 7 + -46 ", "answer": "267", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5933", "question": "85414 + -28859 - -93051 ", "answer": "149606", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5934", "question": "450671 - 767742 * -960988 + 107296 ", "answer": "737791407063", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5935", "question": "-285416 + -603206 * -57589 ", "answer": "34737744918", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5936", "question": "72203 * -30369 - -70481 ", "answer": "-2192662426", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5937", "question": "-879452 - 896957 ", "answer": "-1776409", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5938", "question": "91 - 27 + -18 ", "answer": "46", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5939", "question": "647 * 819 + -869 ", "answer": "529024", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5940", "question": "2750 - 1592 + -5058 + -8250 * 3772 ", "answer": "-31122900", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5941", "question": "810 * 405 - 895 - -397 ", "answer": "327552", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5942", "question": "16407 - -536943 - -664875 ", "answer": "1218225", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5943", "question": "9612 - -6307 * -2433 - -8919 * 1115 ", "answer": "-5390634", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5944", "question": "-4467 - -7336 ", "answer": "2869", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5945", "question": "903350 - -775300 ", "answer": "1678650", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5946", "question": "-100 - -7064 ", "answer": "6964", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5947", "question": "58174 - -87532 ", "answer": "145706", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5948", "question": "-15124 * -42745 ", "answer": "646475380", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5949", "question": "-87 * 382 - -674 ", "answer": "-32560", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5950", "question": "771 * 940 - 174 - 977 ", "answer": "723589", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5951", "question": "-27225 - 40208 - -69867 ", "answer": "2434", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5952", "question": "-7976 + -857 ", "answer": "-8833", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5953", "question": "-53 + -21 ", "answer": "-74", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5954", "question": "173782 - -820945 * 190000 * -597342 ", "answer": "-93173136355926218", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5955", "question": "63155 - -64998 * -43665 + 20062 + -25486 ", "answer": "-2838079939", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5956", "question": "-675 - -182 - 278 + 623 ", "answer": "-148", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5957", "question": "-8812 + 2258 + 3766 * 4689 ", "answer": "17652220", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5958", "question": "655 - -318 * -408 + 144 - -862 ", "answer": "-128083", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5959", "question": "-31 - -416 + -615 ", "answer": "-230", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5960", "question": "-55511 * -38551 + -58628 * 45244 ", "answer": "-512560671", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5961", "question": "9 + 80 + -81 * -18 ", "answer": "1547", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5962", "question": "-33716 - 652444 * -959965 ", "answer": "626323370744", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5963", "question": "4365 + -3952 + -6983 + 3187 - -5054 ", "answer": "1671", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5964", "question": "-65 + 50 - 22 + -24 ", "answer": "-61", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5965", "question": "4116 + 4793 + -1620 + 6577 * -5871 ", "answer": "-38606278", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5966", "question": "1914 - 2561 * -2287 ", "answer": "5858921", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5967", "question": "-396 - 968 + -932 + 816 - -702 ", "answer": "-778", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5968", "question": "945 + 9 - -471 + 640 ", "answer": "2065", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5969", "question": "23634 * -35288 - -21644 ", "answer": "-833974948", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5970", "question": "463 - -895 + -148 + 332 ", "answer": "1542", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5971", "question": "-94 * 6 * -53 * -5 ", "answer": "-149460", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5972", "question": "8 * -89 + -64 ", "answer": "-776", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5973", "question": "33139 - 458636 ", "answer": "-425497", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5974", "question": "-154998 + 270300 - 10048 - -839600 - -408333 ", "answer": "1353187", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5975", "question": "717926 * 26374 - 67777 - -244463 - 772058 ", "answer": "18933984952", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5976", "question": "-631 - 217 * 448 - -89 + -409 ", "answer": "-98167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5977", "question": "5 + 14 - 55 - -14 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5978", "question": "-6792 - 4138 * -884 ", "answer": "3651200", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5979", "question": "-735 - 255 + -370 + 88 ", "answer": "-1272", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5980", "question": "-217 * -585 + 821 - -208 ", "answer": "127974", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5981", "question": "706 - 625 ", "answer": "81", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5982", "question": "78 * 49 ", "answer": "3822", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5983", "question": "-8335 * 6268 * 6966 * 1413 ", "answer": "-514233332301240", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5984", "question": "5409 - -4962 + 2166 ", "answer": "12537", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5985", "question": "63509 + 6155 * -36435 + -96724 - -91493 ", "answer": "-224199147", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5986", "question": "2601 - -7116 * 5567 + 2499 ", "answer": "39619872", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5987", "question": "319294 - -650891 + 391471 * -528626 * -41202 ", "answer": "8526413936923077", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5988", "question": "8454 - -8134 ", "answer": "16588", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5989", "question": "13692 - -7371 * 56761 - -70160 ", "answer": "418469183", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5990", "question": "-34282 * 81191 - 77686 ", "answer": "-2783467548", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5991", "question": "-48 * 91 + -64 ", "answer": "-4432", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5992", "question": "-72041 + -96776 + 99090 * 602 ", "answer": "59483363", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5993", "question": "-627 + 895 + -958 * -38 ", "answer": "36672", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "5994", "question": "99039 * 90571 - 23601 - -17090 ", "answer": "8970054758", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "5995", "question": "-65 + 92 ", "answer": "27", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "5996", "question": "-1751 + 8011 ", "answer": "6260", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "5997", "question": "370103 - 136253 ", "answer": "233850", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5998", "question": "-123234 + 247859 * 746125 ", "answer": "184933673141", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "5999", "question": "-1018 + 9261 ", "answer": "8243", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6000", "question": "-2932 - 8555 - 2971 + -2708 * 1704 ", "answer": "-4628890", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6001", "question": "-476 * 213 ", "answer": "-101388", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6002", "question": "-575 * -892 ", "answer": "512900", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6003", "question": "1174 * -8907 * -2678 - -3167 + -1010 ", "answer": "28003360761", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6004", "question": "284875 + 24407 + 287101 ", "answer": "596383", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6005", "question": "-75 - -31 + 52 * 98 - 65 ", "answer": "4987", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6006", "question": "74 - -6 ", "answer": "80", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6007", "question": "531 * 328 ", "answer": "174168", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6008", "question": "73 + -74 * -80 + 50 ", "answer": "6043", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6009", "question": "93 * 63 * -18 + 75 ", "answer": "-105387", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6010", "question": "560 * -632 - -801 ", "answer": "-353119", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6011", "question": "-126 * -646 + -870 + -531 * 646 ", "answer": "-262500", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6012", "question": "38228 - 51827 + -25867 + -83469 * 58480 ", "answer": "-4881306586", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6013", "question": "4710 * -9766 ", "answer": "-45997860", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6014", "question": "38 * 24 * -37 ", "answer": "-33744", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6015", "question": "-37954 + -50684 ", "answer": "-88638", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6016", "question": "-32844 * -42434 * 48978 + -77718 ", "answer": "68260750975770", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6017", "question": "6298 + 94840 + 58613 - 93127 ", "answer": "66624", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6018", "question": "11999 + 36444 - 92557 ", "answer": "-44114", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6019", "question": "13020 + 9168 * -71400 ", "answer": "-654582180", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6020", "question": "5516 * -8655 + 7789 ", "answer": "-47733191", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6021", "question": "-967 * 486 * -158 ", "answer": "74253996", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6022", "question": "3390 - 7005 - -7165 ", "answer": "3550", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6023", "question": "-114034 - 799415 * -663127 ", "answer": "530113556671", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6024", "question": "-89684 + 911572 * -821736 - -216529 + -58282 ", "answer": "-749071460429", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6025", "question": "80938 * -230145 ", "answer": "-18627476010", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6026", "question": "861 - 649 ", "answer": "212", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6027", "question": "31464 - 367323 - 676769 - 676261 * 442069 ", "answer": "-298955036637", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6028", "question": "-9605 + 7408 ", "answer": "-2197", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6029", "question": "-787 * 252 ", "answer": "-198324", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6030", "question": "374 + 422 - 603 + -426 + 556 ", "answer": "323", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6031", "question": "-25 + 43 ", "answer": "18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6032", "question": "74856 - -72717 - 39867 ", "answer": "107706", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6033", "question": "-7329 - -5887 * 3539 ", "answer": "20826764", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6034", "question": "-4771 * -5544 ", "answer": "26450424", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6035", "question": "76677 * -172284 - -524309 ", "answer": "-13209695959", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6036", "question": "105615 * -107019 ", "answer": "-11302811685", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6037", "question": "-47332 * 831632 + -607136 - 176169 ", "answer": "-39363589129", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6038", "question": "540131 - 323224 + -502956 ", "answer": "-286049", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6039", "question": "-6 + -62 - -61 ", "answer": "-7", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6040", "question": "94573 - -10240 - 75359 + 58002 ", "answer": "87456", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6041", "question": "46 - 13 * -97 ", "answer": "1307", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6042", "question": "2169 * 1616 + -7178 + 7943 + 2776 ", "answer": "3508645", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6043", "question": "950 * 145 * 183 + -827 ", "answer": "25207423", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6044", "question": "-5950 + 2645 - 5407 * 4491 - 872 ", "answer": "-24287014", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6045", "question": "-7373 - 1603 - -4674 * 2899 ", "answer": "13540950", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6046", "question": "-55262 + -47962 + 53212 ", "answer": "-50012", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6047", "question": "-1684 * -242 * 5774 - -2588 ", "answer": "2353069260", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6048", "question": "-5570 + 8162 * -3584 + -6405 - 3462 ", "answer": "-29268045", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6049", "question": "-96 - 63 * -47 - 55 * -84 ", "answer": "7485", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6050", "question": "-4210 + -9318 - 5027 * 2478 * -4267 ", "answer": "53153604374", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6051", "question": "4509 + 6981 - 6836 ", "answer": "4654", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6052", "question": "568288 + 682500 * -509114 * 990090 ", "answer": "-344026874276881712", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6053", "question": "972193 * -46841 + 20427 + 883079 * 442852 ", "answer": "345534829422", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6054", "question": "456228 * -264037 * -111488 * 515015 + 419579 ", "answer": "6916632931989212111099", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6055", "question": "876 * 168 ", "answer": "147168", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6056", "question": "331255 - 915992 - 136659 * -345232 * -92211 ", "answer": "-4350428291917105", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6057", "question": "-6131 + -49007 - -93530 + 83419 * -728 ", "answer": "-60690640", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6058", "question": "-772854 * -616813 - 71179 - 437431 * -315975 ", "answer": "614923583348", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6059", "question": "-6875 - -74972 ", "answer": "68097", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6060", "question": "-74892 - -55650 * -14221 ", "answer": "-791473542", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6061", "question": "29972 + -38392 ", "answer": "-8420", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6062", "question": "-662 - 8470 + 975 - 7639 - -6884 ", "answer": "-8912", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6063", "question": "207 + 804 ", "answer": "1011", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6064", "question": "-98 + 51 ", "answer": "-47", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6065", "question": "-68993 - -79634 - -15923 * 89465 - -98075 ", "answer": "1424659911", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6066", "question": "10 - -5 * -22 - 26 ", "answer": "-126", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6067", "question": "2015 + 2815 * -2734 ", "answer": "-7694195", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6068", "question": "-984 + 864 + -344 + -163 ", "answer": "-627", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6069", "question": "-202220 + -603085 + 637315 ", "answer": "-167990", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6070", "question": "-7034 + 5780 * 2470 + -300 * -7168 ", "answer": "16419966", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6071", "question": "-200 + -725 ", "answer": "-925", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6072", "question": "-7 + -97 - -89 ", "answer": "-15", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6073", "question": "29488 * 97050 ", "answer": "2861810400", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6074", "question": "203 - -1063 * -8249 - -7211 ", "answer": "-8761273", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6075", "question": "-28 - -87 + -66 * 81 - 23 ", "answer": "-5310", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6076", "question": "-647 + -615 ", "answer": "-1262", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6077", "question": "-6064 - -4846 - -3284 * 1651 ", "answer": "5420666", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6078", "question": "-73720 - -39320 + 81020 + 96106 * 81145 ", "answer": "7798567990", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6079", "question": "-715120 + 185180 + 62294 - -780498 - -710824 ", "answer": "1023676", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6080", "question": "4358 * 9142 + 3719 + -6376 + 7068 ", "answer": "39845247", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6081", "question": "-81749 - -39240 ", "answer": "-42509", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6082", "question": "800479 * -926035 ", "answer": "-741271570765", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6083", "question": "4 + -91 + 49 * 95 ", "answer": "4568", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6084", "question": "-295793 + -791319 + 21570 + -446102 + -350100 ", "answer": "-1861744", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6085", "question": "2054 + 3166 ", "answer": "5220", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6086", "question": "109251 + 728639 * 396865 * -642190 ", "answer": "-185702927893940399", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6087", "question": "648 - -21 + 412 - 553 - -919 ", "answer": "1447", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6088", "question": "-43 * 49 * 26 - -11 + -48 ", "answer": "-54819", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6089", "question": "-88 + -72 - 46 + 14 - 29 ", "answer": "-221", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6090", "question": "-287 - -460 ", "answer": "173", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6091", "question": "-87 * -142 * 631 + -798 * 857 ", "answer": "7111488", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6092", "question": "33109 * 20474 ", "answer": "677873666", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6093", "question": "926 - 277 ", "answer": "649", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6094", "question": "-497 + -266 * 734 * 755 - 695 ", "answer": "-147410412", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6095", "question": "954 * 6 * -557 + 301 * -355 ", "answer": "-3295123", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6096", "question": "-189451 - -687808 * 121698 ", "answer": "83704668533", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6097", "question": "-79 - -54 - -90 + 47 ", "answer": "112", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6098", "question": "739 - 664 - 667 ", "answer": "-592", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6099", "question": "-737183 * -259567 + 146177 ", "answer": "191348525938", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6100", "question": "-1742 - 3570 * 401 + -2832 - 7474 ", "answer": "-1443618", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6101", "question": "81 + 5 - -52 - -87 ", "answer": "225", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6102", "question": "751 * 332 ", "answer": "249332", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6103", "question": "-24 * -48 + -92 ", "answer": "1060", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6104", "question": "-84218 - 15311 + 81507 ", "answer": "-18022", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6105", "question": "-498188 * 421395 ", "answer": "-209933932260", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6106", "question": "-562576 + 784665 - 369281 - 1905 ", "answer": "-149097", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6107", "question": "-9978 + -9035 - 2051 ", "answer": "-21064", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6108", "question": "968 + 997 * 929 ", "answer": "927181", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6109", "question": "7 - -1 ", "answer": "8", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 1}
{"id": "6110", "question": "1697 - -8532 ", "answer": "10229", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6111", "question": "590838 - -160653 + 611386 * 396033 ", "answer": "242129783229", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6112", "question": "5049 - -4678 * 7840 ", "answer": "36680569", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6113", "question": "-88128 + -91541 - -25817 + 32164 ", "answer": "-121688", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6114", "question": "-63432 * -96747 * -12928 - 31125 ", "answer": "-79337270572437", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6115", "question": "-492480 * 826586 + 703601 + 281792 + -426859 ", "answer": "-407076514746", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6116", "question": "870601 - 17211 ", "answer": "853390", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6117", "question": "-83585 - -80598 + -36818 - 54011 * -98727 ", "answer": "5332304192", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6118", "question": "949952 - -96481 ", "answer": "1046433", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6119", "question": "-45192 + 26474 - 5714 + -34309 ", "answer": "-58741", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6120", "question": "-325 + -4392 ", "answer": "-4717", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6121", "question": "7 + -20 + -21 * 50 * -97 ", "answer": "101837", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6122", "question": "87 * 82 ", "answer": "7134", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6123", "question": "-749 * 990 * -125 + 608 - -878 ", "answer": "92690236", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6124", "question": "74937 + 48380 + -90997 ", "answer": "32320", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6125", "question": "675516 - -604265 ", "answer": "1279781", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6126", "question": "5361 * 25 + -1981 - 1180 ", "answer": "130864", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6127", "question": "-66819 + 80093 - 26008 - 45958 + 19706 ", "answer": "-38986", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6128", "question": "-200280 - -692933 + -748710 ", "answer": "-256057", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6129", "question": "-619642 * 438480 * -17359 - 855501 ", "answer": "4716451133937939", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6130", "question": "561002 * 180002 ", "answer": "100981482004", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6131", "question": "-196101 - 285968 + -650850 + 923269 - 527677 ", "answer": "-737327", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6132", "question": "-451681 - -538302 + -113711 * -590502 ", "answer": "67146659543", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6133", "question": "-3084 - -5237 * 1725 ", "answer": "9030741", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6134", "question": "-255 * 907 - -458 * -452 * 387 ", "answer": "-80346477", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6135", "question": "804064 - -773165 * -34565 - -728871 * 658256 ", "answer": "453060064815", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6136", "question": "-2827 + -554 + 3075 * -5716 - 24 ", "answer": "-17580105", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6137", "question": "-26579 + 83096 + 5003 - 6938 ", "answer": "54582", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6138", "question": "-19 * -93 * 80 * 92 - -37 ", "answer": "13005157", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6139", "question": "899 - 237 - -989 + -742 ", "answer": "909", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6140", "question": "-538 + 968 ", "answer": "430", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6141", "question": "-76545 - 61067 - 46343 + -86606 ", "answer": "-270561", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6142", "question": "-59 + 3 + 53 - -69 - -48 ", "answer": "114", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6143", "question": "359168 * 705633 + -440489 - 566243 - -957620 ", "answer": "253440744232", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6144", "question": "-3609 * 669 - -9620 ", "answer": "-2404801", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6145", "question": "-39626 + -90432 - 79835 + 11561 + -84976 ", "answer": "-283308", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6146", "question": "-666 + 355 ", "answer": "-311", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6147", "question": "-774 - 917 - 962 + -203 * 517 ", "answer": "-107604", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6148", "question": "5851 * -8641 ", "answer": "-50558491", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6149", "question": "-1855 - 3829 - -4139 ", "answer": "-1545", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6150", "question": "507642 - -31282 - 912109 ", "answer": "-373185", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6151", "question": "-9211 + 280 - 8433 ", "answer": "-17364", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6152", "question": "-90364 + 35648 * 23935 ", "answer": "853144516", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6153", "question": "4 * 26 ", "answer": "104", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6154", "question": "38 + 368 - 307 ", "answer": "99", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6155", "question": "453842 * 724303 + 111575 * 387223 * -893686 ", "answer": "-38610844262473224", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6156", "question": "354 - -83 - 942 * -288 * 255 ", "answer": "69180917", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6157", "question": "70449 + -24955 - -73255 + -13205 - -71182 ", "answer": "176726", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6158", "question": "-9636 - -2116 ", "answer": "-7520", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6159", "question": "-561180 + -844652 ", "answer": "-1405832", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6160", "question": "372 + -381 + -728 + -288 ", "answer": "-1025", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6161", "question": "688665 + 631662 ", "answer": "1320327", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6162", "question": "-217 - 630 - 936 - -761 ", "answer": "-1022", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6163", "question": "61610 * 23745 * -15176 * -49871 ", "answer": "1107206883824017200", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6164", "question": "88 * -100 * -91 + 21 - -95 ", "answer": "800916", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6165", "question": "24231 + 38727 - 45903 ", "answer": "17055", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6166", "question": "475628 + 948160 * 752623 - 862795 * -556935 ", "answer": "1194128232633", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6167", "question": "39017 - -98531 ", "answer": "137548", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6168", "question": "-11 * -22 * -73 ", "answer": "-17666", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6169", "question": "70 - 94 ", "answer": "-24", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6170", "question": "-32487 + 62262 * 10273 * -43806 ", "answer": "-28019085376443", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6171", "question": "144 * -759 + 193 + 601 - -726 ", "answer": "-107776", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6172", "question": "4024 + -8513 ", "answer": "-4489", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6173", "question": "184 + 574 - -695 - 187 - -211 ", "answer": "1477", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6174", "question": "-5 - 99 - 5 + -6 + -19 ", "answer": "-134", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6175", "question": "41729 + 64497 ", "answer": "106226", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6176", "question": "199830 * 261666 + -968724 * 871541 ", "answer": "-791993966904", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6177", "question": "-427033 + 952876 + -684324 ", "answer": "-158481", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6178", "question": "-36045 * 9433 * 33174 * -82477 ", "answer": "930305439428595030", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6179", "question": "1148 - -75279 + 22669 ", "answer": "99096", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6180", "question": "96 + -37 - 74 + 52 ", "answer": "37", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6181", "question": "-629 + -827 ", "answer": "-1456", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6182", "question": "32 - -20 ", "answer": "52", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6183", "question": "-7571 + -7490 - -8371 * 7873 * -1575 ", "answer": "-103800205786", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6184", "question": "-7749 + 5224 ", "answer": "-2525", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6185", "question": "-9760 + -8167 + -4711 - 6916 - -8655 ", "answer": "-20899", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6186", "question": "-85776 - -904306 * -709119 + 596929 + 64925 ", "answer": "-641259990336", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6187", "question": "-678581 + -743087 + -85855 + 365645 + -906760 ", "answer": "-2048638", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6188", "question": "557970 + 75279 * -595875 * -601015 ", "answer": "26959654202794845", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6189", "question": "77073 + -1849 - -175 + 6839 ", "answer": "82238", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6190", "question": "-835390 - 708669 + 51487 - -723799 ", "answer": "-768773", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6191", "question": "-42110 + -860021 ", "answer": "-902131", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6192", "question": "-2356 - -790 ", "answer": "-1566", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6193", "question": "8037 + -6400 ", "answer": "1637", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6194", "question": "677566 * 925219 ", "answer": "626896936954", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6195", "question": "-9047 * -1716 * -9841 ", "answer": "-152778100332", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6196", "question": "-778102 - -817981 ", "answer": "39879", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6197", "question": "-51090 - 52730 + -15127 * 67972 ", "answer": "-1028316264", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6198", "question": "463 - 470 - -324 ", "answer": "317", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6199", "question": "-97712 + -22924 - 97127 ", "answer": "-217763", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6200", "question": "-1856 + -7340 * -4700 - -6665 ", "answer": "34502809", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6201", "question": "14 - 72 * -30 * 8 + 61 ", "answer": "17355", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6202", "question": "-561 - 809 + -660 - 952 * -591 ", "answer": "560602", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6203", "question": "346 * 828 * -435 - 165 ", "answer": "-124622445", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6204", "question": "93 + -46 - 25 ", "answer": "22", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6205", "question": "-8 - -54 * -79 + 30 * 0 ", "answer": "-4274", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6206", "question": "91 + 29 - -15 ", "answer": "135", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6207", "question": "87 + 10 ", "answer": "97", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6208", "question": "994 - 181 - -958 ", "answer": "1771", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6209", "question": "-850 - -420 - 596 - 976 - 272 ", "answer": "-2274", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6210", "question": "703685 + -709701 + -52980 * 164171 ", "answer": "-8697785596", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6211", "question": "6835 - -9939 * 7233 ", "answer": "71895622", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6212", "question": "-98 - 655 - 921 * 278 - -444 ", "answer": "-256347", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6213", "question": "3951 * -3224 * 4043 * 6162 - -7188 ", "answer": "-317341958811996", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6214", "question": "-31037 + -33235 - 55694 - -84544 * -10721 ", "answer": "-906516190", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6215", "question": "-4285 - -807 * 8518 ", "answer": "6869741", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6216", "question": "-40 - -70 * 30 - 74 + -79 ", "answer": "1907", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6217", "question": "9847 - 5552 - 2086 - 9382 ", "answer": "-7173", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6218", "question": "31818 - 48514 * 70150 - -95924 * -87677 ", "answer": "-11813553830", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6219", "question": "256898 + -383006 - -515707 * 683601 * 337523 ", "answer": "118989622925867253", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6220", "question": "-53066 + 27928 * 12336 ", "answer": "344466742", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6221", "question": "-64145 - 38494 ", "answer": "-102639", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6222", "question": "-7474 + 9393 + -9510 * -8776 + -258 ", "answer": "83461421", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6223", "question": "-824810 + -28772 * -886990 ", "answer": "25519651470", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6224", "question": "-396 - -178 - -711 ", "answer": "493", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6225", "question": "-9041 - 8172 * -7200 - 6440 * 8840 ", "answer": "1899759", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6226", "question": "-14871 + 879859 - -765867 * 364112 - 970681 ", "answer": "278861259411", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6227", "question": "-16754 + 328824 + 662323 + -176534 ", "answer": "797859", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6228", "question": "7592 + 8408 * -7136 + 3237 * 2864 ", "answer": "-50721128", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6229", "question": "-7735 * -8950 + -5129 * 4992 ", "answer": "43624282", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6230", "question": "-78654 + 7116 - 26591 - 99608 ", "answer": "-197737", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6231", "question": "-52 - -74 - -89 * 64 ", "answer": "5718", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6232", "question": "9694 - 8429 + 9658 - -5813 ", "answer": "16736", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6233", "question": "575264 * 288564 * -519232 ", "answer": "-86192761696591872", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6234", "question": "-5940 - -2864 + 584 ", "answer": "-2492", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6235", "question": "-41 + -7 ", "answer": "-48", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6236", "question": "-46 - -5 * -11 * 80 + 40 ", "answer": "-4406", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6237", "question": "-47 * 86 * -83 ", "answer": "335486", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6238", "question": "5928 + -7133 + 8235 ", "answer": "7030", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6239", "question": "410763 + -348568 * -310425 - 573640 * -344057 ", "answer": "305569489643", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6240", "question": "-962249 - -9626 ", "answer": "-952623", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6241", "question": "4691 - -7277 ", "answer": "11968", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6242", "question": "-49 * -8 + 525 + 581 ", "answer": "1498", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6243", "question": "996450 * -545166 - 593975 ", "answer": "-543231254675", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6244", "question": "54 - -94 * 60 + 99 ", "answer": "5793", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6245", "question": "-51610 + -78167 + 99669 - -65951 ", "answer": "35843", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6246", "question": "633 * -17 * 692 ", "answer": "-7446612", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6247", "question": "-80 * 72 + -99 - 59 - 90 ", "answer": "-6008", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6248", "question": "-6554 * 3964 - -82 * 8890 ", "answer": "-25251076", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6249", "question": "492 - -609 * -975 ", "answer": "-593283", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6250", "question": "2046 + -25593 - -23160 + -89720 ", "answer": "-90107", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6251", "question": "-3 + -55 ", "answer": "-58", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6252", "question": "-86528 * 51654 ", "answer": "-4469517312", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6253", "question": "-484986 - -65353 * 78235 ", "answer": "5112406969", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6254", "question": "-399 + 444 + -783 ", "answer": "-738", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6255", "question": "-6888 - 5649 * 8337 - -4125 - -80 ", "answer": "-47098396", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6256", "question": "413 - -550 * 860 + 589 + 459 ", "answer": "474461", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6257", "question": "-22 + -24 * -68 * 67 ", "answer": "109322", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6258", "question": "909146 * -933285 - -442083 * -719611 ", "answer": "-1166620114323", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6259", "question": "35455 - 54774 - -3453 + 2517 - 97610 ", "answer": "-110959", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6260", "question": "85643 - 44154 ", "answer": "41489", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6261", "question": "192841 - 226084 * 916323 - -77183 ", "answer": "-207165699108", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6262", "question": "-22921 * -1773 - 22370 * -34705 + 56294 ", "answer": "817046077", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6263", "question": "41 + 14 + 38 ", "answer": "93", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6264", "question": "70 * 57 - 86 * -6 + 43 ", "answer": "4549", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6265", "question": "-881562 * -760001 - 505099 - -511223 ", "answer": "669988007686", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6266", "question": "4613 - -6136 - -7944 * -3735 * 4619 ", "answer": "-137049599211", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6267", "question": "802276 + -813060 + 472517 + -454287 ", "answer": "7446", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6268", "question": "2495 + -6345 + -7680 + 6779 ", "answer": "-4751", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6269", "question": "714 + 47 * 262 - -261 ", "answer": "13289", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6270", "question": "871369 + 634460 ", "answer": "1505829", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6271", "question": "-157318 + -955904 * 510004 + 458209 + -540087 ", "answer": "-487515102812", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6272", "question": "989 - 1241 ", "answer": "-252", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6273", "question": "7691 + -6160 * -2689 + -4603 * 6878 ", "answer": "-15087503", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6274", "question": "-8099 + 7977 * 7611 - 6477 ", "answer": "60698371", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6275", "question": "1 - 85 - -48 - -7 * -20 ", "answer": "-176", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6276", "question": "-8596 - 9149 - -2786 + -2134 ", "answer": "-17093", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6277", "question": "81259 + -7601 ", "answer": "73658", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6278", "question": "405 - -824 ", "answer": "1229", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6279", "question": "351781 * 547720 * 164188 - -408169 ", "answer": "31635331616880329", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6280", "question": "507 * 390 - -854 + -834 - -964 ", "answer": "198714", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6281", "question": "-39 * 65 * 28 ", "answer": "-70980", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6282", "question": "1804 + 7098 + -4453 * -6629 * 9800 ", "answer": "289285591502", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6283", "question": "4559 * -3213 + -4487 ", "answer": "-14652554", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6284", "question": "-9058 + 1683 * -854 - -8512 ", "answer": "-1437828", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6285", "question": "-828532 * 187488 + -238724 + -385311 + 584545 ", "answer": "-155339847106", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6286", "question": "669 + -3225 * 1298 ", "answer": "-4185381", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6287", "question": "-32848 + -64740 - -37303 ", "answer": "-60285", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6288", "question": "-36357 + -41337 - 56067 + -31059 ", "answer": "-164820", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6289", "question": "-766 + 534 * 647 + 162 ", "answer": "344894", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6290", "question": "-82505 * -8775 * -24208 ", "answer": "-17526141126000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6291", "question": "2749 + 3207 + 1849 - -801 ", "answer": "8606", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6292", "question": "18906 - -9021 ", "answer": "27927", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6293", "question": "55276 + -220108 * -23249 ", "answer": "5117346168", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6294", "question": "8 - 67 + -16 - -17 + 32 ", "answer": "-26", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6295", "question": "-531 * 401 * -582 ", "answer": "123925842", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6296", "question": "-3433 * -9637 - -2203 ", "answer": "33086024", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6297", "question": "-12 * -6 ", "answer": "72", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6298", "question": "-459900 - -907702 - -278004 - -56621 * 299845 ", "answer": "16978249551", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6299", "question": "19 * 48 ", "answer": "912", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6300", "question": "969 + -9652 + 3930 ", "answer": "-4753", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6301", "question": "-5922 + -80 * -8333 ", "answer": "660718", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6302", "question": "-893671 + 655829 ", "answer": "-237842", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6303", "question": "38 * -97 + 9 ", "answer": "-3677", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6304", "question": "37 * 80 * -6 + 12 ", "answer": "-17748", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6305", "question": "828669 - -818364 ", "answer": "1647033", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6306", "question": "641 - -8541 + 7991 * 1744 ", "answer": "13945486", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6307", "question": "9874 * 4800 - -3876 - -9528 - 4480 ", "answer": "47404124", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6308", "question": "6140 + -1407 - -2180 ", "answer": "6913", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6309", "question": "-63 + 40 ", "answer": "-23", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6310", "question": "-36920 - -60839 + -95102 + 99541 + -43531 ", "answer": "-15173", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6311", "question": "-571926 + 728994 + 393249 ", "answer": "550317", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6312", "question": "-535 * 441 ", "answer": "-235935", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6313", "question": "-1 * 46 - 92 * -12 - -30 ", "answer": "1088", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6314", "question": "-3 - -5 + 3 ", "answer": "5", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 1}
{"id": "6315", "question": "7037 - 8014 + 6244 * 1662 ", "answer": "10376551", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6316", "question": "-14 * -91 - 3 + -41 ", "answer": "1230", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6317", "question": "-847132 * 931246 ", "answer": "-788888286472", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6318", "question": "584 * -183 ", "answer": "-106872", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6319", "question": "-692 + 691 * 412 - -466 ", "answer": "284466", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6320", "question": "15952 - 19695 ", "answer": "-3743", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6321", "question": "33174 + -593828 ", "answer": "-560654", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6322", "question": "592141 - -179855 - 393663 - -386243 + 493223 ", "answer": "1257799", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6323", "question": "9976 * -71129 ", "answer": "-709582904", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6324", "question": "-91 + 39 - 94 - -3 ", "answer": "-143", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6325", "question": "-619441 - -727346 - -203376 * 583146 + -962968 ", "answer": "118597045833", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6326", "question": "705167 + 526248 ", "answer": "1231415", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6327", "question": "141 - 215 + -672 ", "answer": "-746", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6328", "question": "995 - 1784 ", "answer": "-789", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6329", "question": "-3 + -52 * -71 ", "answer": "3689", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6330", "question": "9677 - 1476 ", "answer": "8201", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6331", "question": "-14121 * -20953 - 18601 - 18345 + 54517 ", "answer": "295894884", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6332", "question": "-875905 + -659214 - 915778 ", "answer": "-2450897", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6333", "question": "689 * -81 ", "answer": "-55809", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6334", "question": "-504125 + -547471 + 500002 + -880085 ", "answer": "-1431679", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6335", "question": "-3427 * -7571 ", "answer": "25945817", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6336", "question": "9049 - 6597 ", "answer": "2452", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6337", "question": "35 - -184 ", "answer": "219", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6338", "question": "-2702 + -6333 + 4414 * -2885 ", "answer": "-12743425", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6339", "question": "4386 - 4702 * 4095 - -8995 ", "answer": "-19241309", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6340", "question": "1880 + -1255 + 7160 * -6604 ", "answer": "-47284015", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6341", "question": "11706 - 92274 * 34860 * -49614 ", "answer": "159591946758666", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6342", "question": "-6779 * 1777 - -3055 * -4199 ", "answer": "-24874228", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6343", "question": "907 - -710 * -399 ", "answer": "-282383", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6344", "question": "6427 * 7041 ", "answer": "45252507", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6345", "question": "-660 - -205 + 666 ", "answer": "211", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6346", "question": "31 + -70 * 52 ", "answer": "-3609", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6347", "question": "960896 - -151486 - 635029 + -181486 * 135199 ", "answer": "-24536248361", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6348", "question": "-36 - -88 - -116 * 515 + 325 ", "answer": "60117", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6349", "question": "375924 * -100568 + 338318 * -798050 * -544936 ", "answer": "147129783080061568", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6350", "question": "73628 - 46846 + -65129 * 12958 - 16375 ", "answer": "-843931175", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6351", "question": "-761634 * -262707 ", "answer": "200086583238", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6352", "question": "417569 - 662327 - -6150 ", "answer": "-238608", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6353", "question": "-29925 - 756483 * -914008 + -52755 ", "answer": "691431431184", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6354", "question": "20 * 3 * -49 + 23 ", "answer": "-2917", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6355", "question": "-3539 * -4187 + -2479 ", "answer": "14815314", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6356", "question": "-4794 - -23 + 3609 ", "answer": "-1162", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6357", "question": "-386 * -1000 + 947 + 733 ", "answer": "387680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6358", "question": "46 * -25 * 13 ", "answer": "-14950", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6359", "question": "-63253 * 28331 ", "answer": "-1792020743", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6360", "question": "465362 * 90406 - 685576 - -925731 + 929184 ", "answer": "42072686311", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6361", "question": "26 + 13 + 49 - -63 + 21 ", "answer": "172", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6362", "question": "9758 - 5507 + -7696 - -9739 - -4983 ", "answer": "11277", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6363", "question": "-6391 * 3037 - 5716 - 9900 ", "answer": "-19425083", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6364", "question": "-67 + -60 - -8 ", "answer": "-119", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6365", "question": "1255 * -6500 - -6475 * 7700 ", "answer": "41700000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6366", "question": "79317 * 39464 * -70723 - 62263 ", "answer": "-221374736303887", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6367", "question": "-367 * 363 + -198 ", "answer": "-133419", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6368", "question": "-7749 * 8067 + 9962 + -6986 ", "answer": "-62508207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6369", "question": "-9348 * -8612 + -9589 - 3356 ", "answer": "80492031", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6370", "question": "-583 - 291 ", "answer": "-874", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6371", "question": "612783 + -254247 ", "answer": "358536", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6372", "question": "77 * 14 - -16 - 83 ", "answer": "1011", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6373", "question": "56102 - 12858 - -27910 + -45685 + 46557 ", "answer": "72026", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6374", "question": "365 * -422 - -811 ", "answer": "-153219", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6375", "question": "459 - -114 + 118 - -430 ", "answer": "1121", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6376", "question": "-23360 - 13659 ", "answer": "-37019", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6377", "question": "-73 + 95 - 26 ", "answer": "-4", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6378", "question": "907736 - 961118 + 191047 * -254100 ", "answer": "-48545096082", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6379", "question": "-823 - -538 + 861 * -227 ", "answer": "-195732", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6380", "question": "510206 - 903046 * -277824 + 835062 ", "answer": "250889197172", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6381", "question": "4948 * 7640 * 3592 + 9175 + 1892 ", "answer": "135787381307", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6382", "question": "-98 * 33 ", "answer": "-3234", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6383", "question": "-7266 - -2955 + 7398 + -4749 ", "answer": "-1662", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6384", "question": "306848 - 626858 ", "answer": "-320010", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6385", "question": "-33710 - -16754 ", "answer": "-16956", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6386", "question": "-725262 + -211262 * -977167 + -622764 - -46252 ", "answer": "206436952980", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6387", "question": "87 + -43 * 56 ", "answer": "-2321", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6388", "question": "-44 + 1 + 92 ", "answer": "49", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6389", "question": "5460 * -6655 - -1518 - -3869 ", "answer": "-36330913", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6390", "question": "-476 + -560 * -425 ", "answer": "237524", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6391", "question": "-904871 - -79380 - 983115 ", "answer": "-1808606", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6392", "question": "-8166 - -4241 - 8681 - -4443 ", "answer": "-8163", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6393", "question": "-52962 - -17666 - -76681 - -52204 + -24926 ", "answer": "68663", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6394", "question": "-777 + -409 + -161 - 572 * -143 ", "answer": "80449", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6395", "question": "-631116 * -104254 + -90374 + 498272 ", "answer": "65796775362", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6396", "question": "793 - -726 * 606 ", "answer": "440749", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6397", "question": "43109 * 94634 * -57999 - 9121 ", "answer": "-236611392580015", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6398", "question": "-8415 - 3316 ", "answer": "-11731", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6399", "question": "2522 * 9566 + -4783 - 5379 ", "answer": "24115290", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6400", "question": "-7375 + 3092 + 2516 + 6200 - -8330 ", "answer": "12763", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6401", "question": "-85 + -40 ", "answer": "-125", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6402", "question": "283344 * 249404 ", "answer": "70667126976", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6403", "question": "738978 + 128699 + 577518 + -76695 * -341684 ", "answer": "26206899575", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6404", "question": "80 - 95 * 50 ", "answer": "-4670", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6405", "question": "-28690 * 66115 + -48176 - 97950 * -68727 ", "answer": "4834922124", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6406", "question": "-54 - -67 + -34 * -97 - -13 ", "answer": "3324", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6407", "question": "90 - 95 ", "answer": "-5", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6408", "question": "-29554 * 6970 * -31987 * 69628 ", "answer": "458782113830993680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6409", "question": "332 - 769 - -574 * -78 + 832 ", "answer": "-44377", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6410", "question": "-4310 + -7050 * 7832 ", "answer": "-55219910", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6411", "question": "43 * 32 + 92 ", "answer": "1468", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6412", "question": "665371 - -561084 - -584222 ", "answer": "1810677", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6413", "question": "-521 * -19 - 881 - -180 ", "answer": "9198", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6414", "question": "-1870 * 2873 * 3440 ", "answer": "-18481434400", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6415", "question": "-5314 * -314 * 676 * 2870 ", "answer": "3237276471520", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6416", "question": "-91 * 72 ", "answer": "-6552", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6417", "question": "100 - -41 + 94 ", "answer": "235", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6418", "question": "13 + 94 + 65 * -78 + 16 ", "answer": "-4947", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6419", "question": "-6315 - 5099 - -6793 + -5329 * 9967 ", "answer": "-53118764", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6420", "question": "-18297 * -84333 + 77172 ", "answer": "1543118073", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6421", "question": "892 + -2463 - -6819 + -9872 ", "answer": "-4624", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6422", "question": "-62906 - 11599 ", "answer": "-74505", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6423", "question": "-63826 - -51706 + 82927 + -59745 * -39037 ", "answer": "2332336372", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6424", "question": "-229 + 5266 + -9349 * -7565 ", "answer": "70730222", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6425", "question": "67 * 89 ", "answer": "5963", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6426", "question": "915 * -371 - 750 + -948 ", "answer": "-341163", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6427", "question": "153 * 566 + 739 ", "answer": "87337", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6428", "question": "723157 + -821416 - -595210 * -318177 ", "answer": "-189382230429", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6429", "question": "-49475 * -7818 + -28982 * 70767 - -15165 ", "answer": "-1664158479", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6430", "question": "63 * -29 - 65 ", "answer": "-1892", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6431", "question": "-7 * -91 + -40 ", "answer": "597", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6432", "question": "42 * 83 * -75 ", "answer": "-261450", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6433", "question": "-6603 - 8825 * 3354 - -9870 ", "answer": "-29595783", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6434", "question": "-607 + -574 ", "answer": "-1181", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6435", "question": "-42 * -10 - 97 ", "answer": "323", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6436", "question": "17 * 751 - -229 * 771 - 104 ", "answer": "189222", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6437", "question": "222596 * -781675 ", "answer": "-173997728300", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6438", "question": "674103 - 396164 * 910600 ", "answer": "-360746264297", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6439", "question": "-388 + -891 - 29 ", "answer": "-1308", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6440", "question": "63 * -10 - 10 * 85 - 31 ", "answer": "-1511", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6441", "question": "229091 * 565173 * 894557 ", "answer": "115823704840834851", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6442", "question": "-39294 + 11805 * -8657 - 27336 ", "answer": "-102262515", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6443", "question": "388 + 485 ", "answer": "873", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6444", "question": "-250902 + 546325 - -444013 + 281600 + 652655 ", "answer": "1673691", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6445", "question": "-42 - 83 * 74 ", "answer": "-6184", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6446", "question": "-1627 * 35087 - -18105 ", "answer": "-57068444", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6447", "question": "97471 + -69486 + -27536 - -72460 - 46663 ", "answer": "26246", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6448", "question": "-72 + -49 ", "answer": "-121", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6449", "question": "-856 - 416 + -319 ", "answer": "-1591", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6450", "question": "9 - -75 - -86 + 36 ", "answer": "206", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6451", "question": "-9500 * -3544 - -4388 + 8730 ", "answer": "33681118", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6452", "question": "38418 - 79619 + 12951 ", "answer": "-28250", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6453", "question": "-57 * 86 + 5 * 11 ", "answer": "-4847", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6454", "question": "-38 - -48 - 70 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6455", "question": "-97 * 29 ", "answer": "-2813", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6456", "question": "62 - 37 - -75 + -16 ", "answer": "84", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6457", "question": "699 * 621 + -775 - -954 - -377 ", "answer": "434635", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6458", "question": "988 - 334 * -902 - 381 + 181 ", "answer": "302056", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6459", "question": "-197 * 497 * -608 ", "answer": "59528672", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6460", "question": "350507 - -101051 - 857795 + -406573 - 51180 ", "answer": "-863990", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6461", "question": "97 + -61 - -949 ", "answer": "985", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6462", "question": "161207 * -231760 + -921554 ", "answer": "-37362255874", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6463", "question": "8626 * -8450 + -551 + 4430 ", "answer": "-72885821", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6464", "question": "83044 + -28268 * 73317 + 28236 + -29440 ", "answer": "-2072443116", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6465", "question": "-186 + 67 + 346 + -508 ", "answer": "-281", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6466", "question": "-81335 * -54660 + -52036 * 26848 * 42547 ", "answer": "-59436373607716", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6467", "question": "-31529 - -36434 - 14328 ", "answer": "-9423", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6468", "question": "657161 * -345296 - -176746 ", "answer": "-226914887910", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6469", "question": "518708 - 727775 ", "answer": "-209067", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6470", "question": "-71729 * -701243 ", "answer": "50299459147", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6471", "question": "39 + -56 - 43 - 28 ", "answer": "-88", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6472", "question": "-963 * 7698 ", "answer": "-7413174", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6473", "question": "295 - 793 ", "answer": "-498", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6474", "question": "89000 + -84917 ", "answer": "4083", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6475", "question": "570975 * 84756 ", "answer": "48393557100", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6476", "question": "80736 * -25551 * 98142 - -57504 - -91024 ", "answer": "-202455712125584", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6477", "question": "565303 + -150351 ", "answer": "414952", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6478", "question": "414019 * -485667 * 489527 - -716964 - -129777 ", "answer": "-98431820530959930", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6479", "question": "51965 * -72198 * 68855 ", "answer": "-258328059314850", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6480", "question": "4370 + -5549 - -6911 * -4380 ", "answer": "-30271359", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6481", "question": "88 * 48 * 49 ", "answer": "206976", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6482", "question": "602 - -5864 + -5879 - -4191 * -5450 ", "answer": "-22840363", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6483", "question": "-75 + -69 + 20 ", "answer": "-124", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6484", "question": "-58753 * -59521 * -74246 - -88735 * -43915 ", "answer": "-259644929138523", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6485", "question": "-77 - 52 - -27 + 1 * -89 ", "answer": "-191", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6486", "question": "75131 * 71713 ", "answer": "5387869403", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6487", "question": "981477 - 811854 * -823796 - 281770 + -562580 ", "answer": "668802214911", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6488", "question": "74397 * -95097 + 1486 - 65920 * 31523 ", "answer": "-9152926183", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6489", "question": "-37 * -18 + -21 ", "answer": "645", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6490", "question": "-34373 - -14860 ", "answer": "-19513", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6491", "question": "-77401 + -93858 * 59733 * 48801 * -33394 ", "answer": "9136561607262591515", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6492", "question": "202 + -959 + -51 ", "answer": "-808", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6493", "question": "83131 + 250917 * 329401 ", "answer": "82652393848", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6494", "question": "720 * 706 * -989 - 394 - 295 ", "answer": "-502729169", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6495", "question": "936 * -284 - -928 * 128 - -164 ", "answer": "-146876", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6496", "question": "237 + -888 * 70 - -292 ", "answer": "-61631", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6497", "question": "23 * 3 - -43 ", "answer": "112", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6498", "question": "-444 + -844 - 30 + 269 + 118 ", "answer": "-931", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6499", "question": "263363 + 611012 * 888752 * -364948 ", "answer": "-198180682030371389", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6500", "question": "-16191 + 19738 - 47702 + -27395 ", "answer": "-71550", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6501", "question": "587791 - -331338 - -321022 - -694442 - -415596 ", "answer": "2350189", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6502", "question": "-56097 - 447116 - -998214 + -509638 + -198896 ", "answer": "-213533", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6503", "question": "962007 - -380692 ", "answer": "1342699", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6504", "question": "8072 - -2183 * 7222 * -4192 ", "answer": "-66089496120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6505", "question": "74123 + -61342 ", "answer": "12781", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6506", "question": "5456 + 6391 * -837 ", "answer": "-5343811", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6507", "question": "7436 - 2839 - 7044 - 1637 * -12 ", "answer": "17197", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6508", "question": "-9 * 77 ", "answer": "-693", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6509", "question": "227403 * -27471 - -732646 * 253251 ", "answer": "179296344333", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6510", "question": "-361381 - -555373 * -519952 + -17979 ", "answer": "-288767681456", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6511", "question": "421350 - -785983 - 363972 - -241592 + 515482 ", "answer": "1600435", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6512", "question": "87366 * -45948 + -94934 - -2672 * 79833 ", "answer": "-3801074126", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6513", "question": "-1824 - -4633 * 7254 ", "answer": "33605958", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6514", "question": "-905 + 756 ", "answer": "-149", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6515", "question": "-58 * -40 + 7 + -94 ", "answer": "2233", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6516", "question": "49949 - -71769 ", "answer": "121718", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6517", "question": "3859 - -1243 * -3692 + 9617 - -5722 ", "answer": "-4569958", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6518", "question": "3460 + -6188 + -1482 * 7171 ", "answer": "-10630150", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6519", "question": "526 * 744 * -747 * -754 - 866 ", "answer": "220419811006", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6520", "question": "-64289 - -69978 ", "answer": "5689", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6521", "question": "-5257 - 2319 - -3657 + 467 ", "answer": "-3452", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6522", "question": "717 - -381 - 651 ", "answer": "447", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6523", "question": "-2 - -76 ", "answer": "74", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6524", "question": "163 + 823 - -639 + -751 - 579 ", "answer": "295", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6525", "question": "-99643 * -1818 * 6594 ", "answer": "1194509522556", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6526", "question": "10 + 22 ", "answer": "32", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6527", "question": "18989 + -33177 + 319877 - 709988 + -360280 ", "answer": "-764579", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6528", "question": "-77482 * 63554 * -69107 * 54961 * -81533 ", "answer": "-1524943667089458550795148", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6529", "question": "-100 - -22 * 5 - 99 ", "answer": "-89", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6530", "question": "2 - 3 + -40 - 62 + 49 ", "answer": "-54", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6531", "question": "58178 + -84286 + -40817 * -76728 - 68028 ", "answer": "3131712640", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6532", "question": "-56115 - -545350 - -649333 ", "answer": "1138568", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6533", "question": "-83613 - -4117 + 9771 ", "answer": "-69725", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6534", "question": "-408 - 576 * -267 + -908 * -65 ", "answer": "212404", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6535", "question": "-30 + -94 ", "answer": "-124", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6536", "question": "-23922 * -76046 + -47479 - -89132 ", "answer": "1819214065", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6537", "question": "18534 - 93321 ", "answer": "-74787", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6538", "question": "920 * -373 - -3 * -954 ", "answer": "-346022", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6539", "question": "-5 + 59 ", "answer": "54", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6540", "question": "-955167 - 979550 * -904653 ", "answer": "886151890983", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6541", "question": "-628 - 371 - 497 ", "answer": "-1496", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6542", "question": "-51 + 27 ", "answer": "-24", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6543", "question": "23391 + 34750 * 49524 + -88590 ", "answer": "1720893801", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6544", "question": "87377 * 75838 - -10183 * 64138 + 25733 ", "answer": "7279639913", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6545", "question": "-253444 * -843051 ", "answer": "213666217644", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6546", "question": "90782 * -71649 ", "answer": "-6504439518", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6547", "question": "-411100 * 33580 + -364909 * -254269 * 338016 ", "answer": "31362816480104336", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6548", "question": "7361 + -86564 - 1211 - 26840 + -84412 ", "answer": "-191666", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6549", "question": "347 - 982 * -964 - -342 ", "answer": "947337", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6550", "question": "-49953 * -47844 * 81725 ", "answer": "195318772607700", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6551", "question": "878 + -105 * 537 - -944 ", "answer": "-54563", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6552", "question": "12 - 76 * 39 ", "answer": "-2952", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6553", "question": "8046 + -9478 + -9724 * -6584 ", "answer": "64021384", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6554", "question": "-821 - -312 + 423 ", "answer": "-86", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6555", "question": "5151 - -8364 - 2810 + 3939 ", "answer": "14644", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6556", "question": "-97761 * 58591 ", "answer": "-5727914751", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6557", "question": "342 - -991 * 574 + -803 + -520 ", "answer": "567853", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6558", "question": "2273 * -3468 + -3578 ", "answer": "-7886342", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6559", "question": "-91683 * 9578 ", "answer": "-878139774", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6560", "question": "-438 * 328 - 100 ", "answer": "-143764", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6561", "question": "70736 * 3122 * -95406 * -75197 + -82470 ", "answer": "1584344421091877274", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6562", "question": "-934909 * 395712 - 697857 - -280999 - 954837 ", "answer": "-369956081903", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6563", "question": "43 + 64 ", "answer": "107", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6564", "question": "-512 + 949 - 119 * -564 - 17 ", "answer": "67536", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6565", "question": "-25 * -93 - 73 - -79 ", "answer": "2331", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6566", "question": "24983 - 85632 - -86387 - -96154 - -26042 ", "answer": "147934", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6567", "question": "-7178 - 149 - 53 ", "answer": "-7380", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6568", "question": "21453 + -57522 * 56945 + 36418 ", "answer": "-3275532419", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6569", "question": "-493281 + -48675 ", "answer": "-541956", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6570", "question": "647 * 675 * 249 + -482 ", "answer": "108744043", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6571", "question": "92 + -23 * -100 * -38 ", "answer": "-87308", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6572", "question": "-104529 * -200819 + 197171 * 952824 ", "answer": "208860670155", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6573", "question": "334604 - 800751 ", "answer": "-466147", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6574", "question": "-873 + 618 ", "answer": "-255", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6575", "question": "80 + -38 * -58 - 11 * 77 ", "answer": "1437", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6576", "question": "85 - 32 ", "answer": "53", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6577", "question": "345 * -435 ", "answer": "-150075", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6578", "question": "-839 - 634 + 804 + -420 - 232 ", "answer": "-1321", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6579", "question": "311125 * 420249 ", "answer": "130749970125", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6580", "question": "-62060 * 98780 * -1011 + 73637 + -50413 ", "answer": "6197719978024", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6581", "question": "-709 - -540 - 646 - 656 ", "answer": "-1471", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6582", "question": "-16804 - 92432 * 48756 * -35288 ", "answer": "159029415705692", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6583", "question": "925 * -914 - 941 - -804 ", "answer": "-845587", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6584", "question": "-77 * 58 + -61 + 11 + 96 ", "answer": "-4420", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6585", "question": "-815 * 968 + -24 ", "answer": "-788944", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6586", "question": "-99 * -57 ", "answer": "5643", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6587", "question": "-32855 - 58643 * -30861 ", "answer": "1809748768", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6588", "question": "-8902 - 3332 - -3356 ", "answer": "-8878", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6589", "question": "466 * -447 + 89 - 647 ", "answer": "-208860", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6590", "question": "-1110 - -426 * -7739 * -2092 ", "answer": "6896933778", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6591", "question": "319795 + -511233 - 931009 - -240133 * -18196 ", "answer": "-4370582515", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6592", "question": "-5800 + -4363 - -5664 ", "answer": "-4499", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6593", "question": "-17 + -72 * 59 - 26 + -14 ", "answer": "-4305", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6594", "question": "-786 * 303 - 965 + -94 ", "answer": "-239217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6595", "question": "-196 - -834 * -877 + 152 - 937 ", "answer": "-732399", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6596", "question": "-442 - -844 - 48 ", "answer": "354", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6597", "question": "47687 * 20601 + 62315 - -45865 ", "answer": "982508067", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6598", "question": "-81 + 10 - 29 - -40 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6599", "question": "74390 * -68916 * -80539 + -96995 ", "answer": "412896169511365", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6600", "question": "-59900 - 34228 - 53797 * 36402 ", "answer": "-1958412522", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6601", "question": "-817 * 884 - 493 + 395 + 267 ", "answer": "-722059", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6602", "question": "870 - 769 - -405 ", "answer": "506", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6603", "question": "298 - -635 ", "answer": "933", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6604", "question": "-84497 + 867 ", "answer": "-83630", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6605", "question": "71 * -9 ", "answer": "-639", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6606", "question": "923962 - 922548 - -540008 + -942663 ", "answer": "-401241", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6607", "question": "-4683 + 3546 + -1035 - 7610 ", "answer": "-9782", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6608", "question": "-5549 * -516132 ", "answer": "2864016468", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6609", "question": "-1 - -64 + -95 - -78 ", "answer": "46", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6610", "question": "-29117 + 30783 + 75121 ", "answer": "76787", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6611", "question": "433821 * -502455 - 169165 * -954250 - 733891 ", "answer": "-56550563196", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6612", "question": "-80 * -89 + 41 + 82 - 98 ", "answer": "7145", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6613", "question": "-70 - 48 + -36 - 16 ", "answer": "-170", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6614", "question": "79258 + 853965 + 948323 ", "answer": "1881546", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6615", "question": "221 - 598 - 272 - -523 ", "answer": "-126", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6616", "question": "214 * -106 * 480 + -841 ", "answer": "-10889161", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6617", "question": "4888 + -1470 + -9222 * 795 - 7223 ", "answer": "-7335295", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6618", "question": "-4296 * 9579 * 4434 ", "answer": "-182465236656", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6619", "question": "850 - -449 ", "answer": "1299", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6620", "question": "645213 * -226969 ", "answer": "-146443349397", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6621", "question": "76421 + 98935 ", "answer": "175356", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6622", "question": "-775 - 195 * -295 * -766 ", "answer": "-44064925", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6623", "question": "73861 * -36190 ", "answer": "-2673029590", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6624", "question": "-958834 * 106735 ", "answer": "-102341146990", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6625", "question": "767 * -927 ", "answer": "-711009", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6626", "question": "-700069 - -660185 - -695683 + -422941 + -350958 ", "answer": "-118100", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6627", "question": "-405 + -446 ", "answer": "-851", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6628", "question": "77103 + 79195 + 23219 * -16660 * 89675 ", "answer": "-34688849168202", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6629", "question": "205115 + 145858 + -781007 ", "answer": "-430034", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6630", "question": "-145726 - -244933 * -106071 + -2218 - 48743 ", "answer": "-25980484930", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6631", "question": "47 - -67 + 56 ", "answer": "170", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6632", "question": "91924 * 238142 * 765293 ", "answer": "16753002436925944", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6633", "question": "438 - -680 ", "answer": "1118", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6634", "question": "-568 + -892 - -78 - 288 + 263 ", "answer": "-1407", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6635", "question": "-49 - 125 ", "answer": "-174", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6636", "question": "50 - -63 * 26 + -8 ", "answer": "1680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6637", "question": "54392 + -71612 - -57411 + 34824 * -36030 ", "answer": "-1254668529", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6638", "question": "-37859 + -12394 - 26414 + 67623 ", "answer": "-9044", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6639", "question": "-7040 - -9237 * -7221 + 5752 * 1751 ", "answer": "-56635665", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6640", "question": "8618 * 7779 + 5915 * -4014 * 9419 ", "answer": "-223566487968", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6641", "question": "347 * 412 * -254 ", "answer": "-36312856", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6642", "question": "789748 - -456708 - -16285 + 987146 + -150463 ", "answer": "2099424", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6643", "question": "540 * -590 + 357 - -970 + -702 ", "answer": "-317975", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6644", "question": "5806 * 4381 + 8130 ", "answer": "25444216", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6645", "question": "-862895 * -920687 * 911186 ", "answer": "723897375130863890", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6646", "question": "-48 + 70 ", "answer": "22", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6647", "question": "-66450 - 61186 ", "answer": "-127636", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6648", "question": "2159 + -9578 - -1688 - 9632 ", "answer": "-15363", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6649", "question": "-59799 - 44891 ", "answer": "-104690", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6650", "question": "-330 + 240 * -189 ", "answer": "-45690", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6651", "question": "-47207 + -20311 * -155 - -81943 - 47587 ", "answer": "3135354", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6652", "question": "-177798 - -37447 ", "answer": "-140351", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6653", "question": "-679706 + 949031 + -170040 * 338569 * -922462 ", "answer": "53106388951004445", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6654", "question": "21162 + 33716 ", "answer": "54878", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6655", "question": "-655430 * 263339 + -404712 * -171938 * -140764 ", "answer": "-9795287884218754", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6656", "question": "458811 - 238774 + -151563 - 86816 ", "answer": "-18342", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6657", "question": "-2136 - -1945 * 6444 - 8664 ", "answer": "12522780", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6658", "question": "431731 - 338321 + -831531 ", "answer": "-738121", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6659", "question": "-1 - -262 + -507 + 278 ", "answer": "32", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6660", "question": "-249026 + 138448 ", "answer": "-110578", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6661", "question": "-739 * 5048 - 7691 * 8814 ", "answer": "-71518946", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6662", "question": "-126 - 413 - 709 + 997 * -649 ", "answer": "-648301", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6663", "question": "100 - 75 ", "answer": "25", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6664", "question": "26 + 442 - -795 ", "answer": "1263", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6665", "question": "584975 + -222533 * 33978 - -749145 * 136177 ", "answer": "94455677366", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6666", "question": "82111 - -226619 - -179831 + -795233 ", "answer": "-306672", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6667", "question": "69 + 47 ", "answer": "116", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6668", "question": "-3190 * 3490 - 1826 * 8542 + 1565 ", "answer": "-26729227", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6669", "question": "4044 + -2775 - 7813 * -4640 * 8416 ", "answer": "305099526389", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6670", "question": "-34 + -22 + 84 * 100 - -16 ", "answer": "8360", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6671", "question": "732170 + 256634 ", "answer": "988804", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6672", "question": "-5047 * -56860 - -53209 ", "answer": "287025629", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6673", "question": "74164 * -90458 + -38946 + 72243 - 42549 ", "answer": "-6708736364", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6674", "question": "-43 + 960 + -874 - -59 ", "answer": "102", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6675", "question": "-500783 - -173201 ", "answer": "-327582", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6676", "question": "-6842 + 9833 - -4548 + 563 * -8606 ", "answer": "-4837639", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6677", "question": "2155 - 5371 * 2368 + -9891 ", "answer": "-12726264", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6678", "question": "93841 + -24019 - -70408 - -78275 * 80248 ", "answer": "6281552430", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6679", "question": "8590 + 153 - -2128 ", "answer": "10871", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6680", "question": "13067 - -97707 * 14371 ", "answer": "1404160364", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6681", "question": "-25800 + -6088 ", "answer": "-31888", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6682", "question": "-10 * 30 - 11 - 93 * -92 ", "answer": "8245", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6683", "question": "-53 * -33 * 58 - 66 - 62 ", "answer": "101314", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6684", "question": "203 + -60 - -902 ", "answer": "1045", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6685", "question": "34 - 39 - -13 * 11 ", "answer": "138", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6686", "question": "-8379 - 8833 ", "answer": "-17212", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6687", "question": "99638 * 60490 - 18925 + 17172 ", "answer": "6027100867", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6688", "question": "8370 + 1322 ", "answer": "9692", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6689", "question": "63 + -5 * 67 * -38 ", "answer": "12793", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6690", "question": "-831 - -290 - 561 - -125 - -110 ", "answer": "-867", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6691", "question": "490326 * -247441 + -667093 + 148028 * 755152 ", "answer": "-9543782603", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6692", "question": "-17 + 59 + -16 + 56 ", "answer": "82", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6693", "question": "-7303 * -4327 ", "answer": "31600081", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6694", "question": "77380 + 91677 - 73694 ", "answer": "95363", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6695", "question": "375922 + -257246 * 765918 * 320047 ", "answer": "-63058649763649994", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6696", "question": "-805922 + 58726 + -527689 ", "answer": "-1274885", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6697", "question": "-18485 + 72221 * 26424 * 727 ", "answer": "1387383302323", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6698", "question": "-339 + -209 ", "answer": "-548", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6699", "question": "-63203 + 25144 * -49334 * 75268 + -43642 ", "answer": "-93366499004573", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6700", "question": "97187 * 15254 + 93273 - -9054 - -80337 ", "answer": "1482673162", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6701", "question": "-1575 - 78 ", "answer": "-1653", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6702", "question": "56881 - -862200 ", "answer": "919081", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6703", "question": "-809 + 158 - -577 * -2 ", "answer": "-1805", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6704", "question": "54 + 38 ", "answer": "92", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6705", "question": "-595560 - -610865 - 902602 * 9173 * 647313 ", "answer": "-5359472095276393", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6706", "question": "-3323 + -2312 - -9032 ", "answer": "3397", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6707", "question": "-15407 + 78844 ", "answer": "63437", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6708", "question": "28 + -125 - -6 + -775 ", "answer": "-866", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6709", "question": "-87314 * 91086 + 39377 - -3902 - 36183 ", "answer": "-7953075908", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6710", "question": "-8702 * -8322 - 451 ", "answer": "72417593", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6711", "question": "-917 + 296 * -122 * 91 ", "answer": "-3287109", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6712", "question": "-433655 + -447446 * -903228 - 145086 - -926058 ", "answer": "404146103005", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6713", "question": "-257422 * 359667 - 893801 - 984099 * -870979 ", "answer": "764542470646", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6714", "question": "52 * 54 - 56 ", "answer": "2752", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6715", "question": "-274 - -241 + 56 ", "answer": "23", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6716", "question": "-6068 - -6022 * -2518 ", "answer": "-15169464", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6717", "question": "-37 - -90 * 44 - 15 + -2 ", "answer": "3906", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6718", "question": "787055 - 157448 + -720577 ", "answer": "-90970", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6719", "question": "700 + 674 ", "answer": "1374", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6720", "question": "612 + 281 * 234 ", "answer": "66366", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6721", "question": "-403675 * -858342 - -813682 + -494521 ", "answer": "346491526011", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6722", "question": "34 * -1 - -7 ", "answer": "-27", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6723", "question": "2934 + -74757 * 35402 ", "answer": "-2646544380", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6724", "question": "809219 * 970626 + 970099 * -983165 ", "answer": "-168318382241", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6725", "question": "-390 + -5034 + 3525 ", "answer": "-1899", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6726", "question": "61999 + -21884 - -76147 * 51923 ", "answer": "3953820796", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6727", "question": "424 - -544 - 182 - -886 + -916 ", "answer": "756", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6728", "question": "-93499 * -792428 ", "answer": "74091225572", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6729", "question": "-4593 + -8458 ", "answer": "-13051", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6730", "question": "74382 + -68415 * 2930 - 10769 - -77630 ", "answer": "-200314707", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6731", "question": "7755 - 2241 * -1618 - -6222 * -3501 ", "answer": "-18149529", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6732", "question": "61 + 0 - -41 * -85 ", "answer": "-3424", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6733", "question": "-77 + 94 ", "answer": "17", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6734", "question": "-9864 + 3155 - 8895 ", "answer": "-15604", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6735", "question": "13 * 85 + -55 * -9 - -66 ", "answer": "1666", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6736", "question": "82318 * 72107 + -38507 - 31502 ", "answer": "5935634017", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6737", "question": "-44 * 66 - 43 * -63 ", "answer": "-195", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6738", "question": "-1772 - -3707 ", "answer": "1935", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6739", "question": "-35 + -31 + 93 - 92 ", "answer": "-65", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6740", "question": "25074 - 82324 - 95561 + -60345 - -94198 ", "answer": "-118958", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6741", "question": "71 * -34 * -75 + 16 ", "answer": "181066", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6742", "question": "-484 - -936 * -8265 + 4538 ", "answer": "-7731986", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6743", "question": "-357 - 481 * 517 ", "answer": "-249034", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6744", "question": "-480635 + -749128 ", "answer": "-1229763", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6745", "question": "-1463 * 7207 - -5283 - 1873 ", "answer": "-10540431", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6746", "question": "929816 * 684930 + -134580 - 827000 ", "answer": "636857911300", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6747", "question": "4373 * 3594 * 5235 ", "answer": "82276202070", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6748", "question": "-225 * -497 * 601 + -15 - 588 ", "answer": "67206222", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6749", "question": "-429 + -170 ", "answer": "-599", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6750", "question": "585611 + 77394 + -780743 ", "answer": "-117738", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6751", "question": "-1454 - -6218 ", "answer": "4764", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6752", "question": "-119 * 214 * -982 + 570 * -916 ", "answer": "24485492", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6753", "question": "-4584 * 3845 + 9001 * -8151 ", "answer": "-90992631", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6754", "question": "-13804 - 40313 + 38106 ", "answer": "-16011", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6755", "question": "-72729 - -38832 + 4516 ", "answer": "-29381", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6756", "question": "-7399 + 897 ", "answer": "-6502", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6757", "question": "-342880 - -239063 ", "answer": "-103817", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6758", "question": "24462 + 8085 ", "answer": "32547", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6759", "question": "44072 - 60081 - 87071 * -50162 ", "answer": "4367639493", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6760", "question": "818 * -1123 ", "answer": "-918614", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6761", "question": "3955 + -999 * -8877 - 1170 + -3652 ", "answer": "8867256", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6762", "question": "646 + -801 + -644 ", "answer": "-799", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6763", "question": "-2028 - 3242 - -3487 ", "answer": "-1783", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6764", "question": "83 * 50 * -22 - 71 - 20 ", "answer": "-91391", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6765", "question": "843 - -252 * 487 * -362 ", "answer": "-44425245", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6766", "question": "-7846 - -1137 * -4822 ", "answer": "-5490460", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6767", "question": "-82354 - 25641 * 2817 * -91989 ", "answer": "6644429503979", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6768", "question": "886 - 9 ", "answer": "877", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6769", "question": "-98865 * -74442 - 79094 - 17293 + 42034 ", "answer": "7359653977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6770", "question": "-52521 * -70426 * -924504 - 535696 * 819745 ", "answer": "-3420035157570304", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6771", "question": "5261 + -9330 ", "answer": "-4069", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6772", "question": "-595701 - 806280 + -878134 ", "answer": "-2280115", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6773", "question": "156103 + -860154 - 521598 ", "answer": "-1225649", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6774", "question": "-1 * 73 * 26 ", "answer": "-1898", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6775", "question": "438986 + -269498 * 456484 ", "answer": "-123021086046", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6776", "question": "35630 - 90882 - -12468 ", "answer": "-42784", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6777", "question": "-489456 + -594346 + 449449 - -66837 ", "answer": "-567516", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6778", "question": "-24511 * 40330 ", "answer": "-988528630", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6779", "question": "138690 - -578237 - -31118 ", "answer": "748045", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6780", "question": "878 - 894 + -886 + 646 ", "answer": "-256", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6781", "question": "795 + -228 - -331 ", "answer": "898", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6782", "question": "6394 * 1895 * -5171 - 1277 ", "answer": "-62655095007", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6783", "question": "74436 + 8680 + 62595 ", "answer": "145711", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6784", "question": "-617414 + -699996 ", "answer": "-1317410", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6785", "question": "-32333 * -82704 * -2678 + 76062 ", "answer": "-7161155184834", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6786", "question": "93619 * 34323 * -73738 ", "answer": "-236941204684506", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6787", "question": "-2952 - 6304 ", "answer": "-9256", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6788", "question": "-8983 + 2019 + -6431 ", "answer": "-13395", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6789", "question": "-753060 + -839225 - -319908 * -940376 ", "answer": "-300835397693", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6790", "question": "-95 * -59 * -68 - -48 - -57 ", "answer": "-381035", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6791", "question": "4415 - 9941 - -8883 * 7586 - -7530 ", "answer": "67388442", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6792", "question": "224001 - 127038 - -849284 ", "answer": "946247", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6793", "question": "585456 + 973444 * -33176 + 477016 ", "answer": "-32293915672", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6794", "question": "56 - 61 - -42 * -5 * -27 ", "answer": "5665", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6795", "question": "4445 + -704 + 9215 * -9919 + 322 ", "answer": "-91399522", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6796", "question": "13434 - 717319 * 422519 * 558041 ", "answer": "-169131572178193567", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6797", "question": "2629 - 4200 ", "answer": "-1571", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6798", "question": "-41 * -74 - -43 + -30 ", "answer": "3047", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6799", "question": "-53125 + 18293 + -21406 ", "answer": "-56238", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6800", "question": "-2800 * -5491 - -7569 + 9438 ", "answer": "15391807", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6801", "question": "8 - -6 * -31 * -43 * -2 ", "answer": "-15988", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6802", "question": "802 - -707 ", "answer": "1509", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6803", "question": "-3767 - -3293 + 8330 * -8397 ", "answer": "-69947484", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6804", "question": "583 - -878 ", "answer": "1461", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6805", "question": "-3961 + 9605 ", "answer": "5644", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6806", "question": "799 - -694 * -464 ", "answer": "-321217", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6807", "question": "-52824 * 38189 - -34992 * 83390 ", "answer": "900687144", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6808", "question": "451665 * 516511 - 258430 + -88694 - -187168 ", "answer": "233289780859", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6809", "question": "-91 + 96 - 15 ", "answer": "-10", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6810", "question": "-77899 - 67390 - 92647 ", "answer": "-237936", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6811", "question": "610764 * 368220 - -65590 - 302739 + 806678 ", "answer": "224896089609", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6812", "question": "52 + 35 ", "answer": "87", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6813", "question": "-443 * 372 ", "answer": "-164796", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6814", "question": "9749 * -5204 * 7194 ", "answer": "-364978928424", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6815", "question": "-9145 + 8832 - 988 - -1795 * -9936 ", "answer": "-17836421", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6816", "question": "581175 + -486449 + -108675 + 372042 ", "answer": "358093", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6817", "question": "-39 - -91 - -77 ", "answer": "129", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6818", "question": "4284 - -9105 + -9289 * -7991 - 1965 ", "answer": "74239823", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6819", "question": "-54 + 3 + 56 * -66 ", "answer": "-3747", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6820", "question": "-629 - -518 + -714 + 750 ", "answer": "-75", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6821", "question": "-63311 * -16620 ", "answer": "1052228820", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6822", "question": "28 + -485 ", "answer": "-457", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6823", "question": "6214 + 8391 * 7968 ", "answer": "66865702", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6824", "question": "-142587 + -444693 * 519472 ", "answer": "-231005704683", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6825", "question": "-311126 + -223593 + 883684 * 779561 ", "answer": "688885048005", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6826", "question": "93034 + 764933 - -47693 + 344097 ", "answer": "1249757", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6827", "question": "830158 * 623432 - 974106 * -429991 ", "answer": "936403875302", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6828", "question": "-28 - 44 ", "answer": "-72", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6829", "question": "663027 + -421641 - 455748 * -970805 ", "answer": "442442678526", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6830", "question": "921669 * -140931 ", "answer": "-129891733839", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6831", "question": "-363485 + 577880 * 927240 * -16999 ", "answer": "-9108632837312285", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6832", "question": "389474 - 817237 * -263273 + -241885 ", "answer": "215156584290", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6833", "question": "52068 + 78370 - 83116 ", "answer": "47322", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6834", "question": "4113 * -4526 + 2937 - -8559 - 9066 ", "answer": "-18613008", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6835", "question": "720383 + -625146 + -629962 - -294750 ", "answer": "-239975", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6836", "question": "956 * 816 * -260 + -297 - -577 ", "answer": "-202824680", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6837", "question": "-751006 - -346770 + -930492 + -74276 ", "answer": "-1409004", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6838", "question": "-42275 * -31090 * 14213 ", "answer": "18680568736750", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6839", "question": "-9766 + 5766 - 3317 + 1212 * 2002 ", "answer": "2419107", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6840", "question": "30 * 926 + 44 - -367 - 51 ", "answer": "28140", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6841", "question": "680 - -922 - 449 + -315 ", "answer": "838", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6842", "question": "-32 - -8 + -64 + -11 ", "answer": "-99", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6843", "question": "-485 + -39768 - -81135 * -32605 - -15585 ", "answer": "-2645431343", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6844", "question": "-52 * -57 - 43 - -49 ", "answer": "2970", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6845", "question": "8364 - -4016 * 4195 - 21 + -7995 ", "answer": "16847468", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6846", "question": "106818 - 425695 * -97733 ", "answer": "41604556253", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6847", "question": "-6171 - 2983 ", "answer": "-9154", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6848", "question": "-416567 + -443223 * 193427 - -573489 ", "answer": "-85731138299", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6849", "question": "83 * -59 + 30 ", "answer": "-4867", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6850", "question": "4483 - -8013 - 7695 ", "answer": "4801", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6851", "question": "19 * -83 ", "answer": "-1577", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6852", "question": "-95 - 35 * 64 * 25 + -86 ", "answer": "-56181", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6853", "question": "-3339 + -5381 * 942 * 3799 - 1452 ", "answer": "-19256763489", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6854", "question": "35763 * -82087 + -71598 * -78471 ", "answer": "2682689277", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6855", "question": "-955 * -534 - 419 - -716 ", "answer": "510267", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6856", "question": "11063 + 69743 * 71076 - 26420 ", "answer": "4957038111", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6857", "question": "-334414 - -145107 * -371184 - 803597 ", "answer": "-53862534699", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6858", "question": "-833 - -936 ", "answer": "103", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6859", "question": "-871 - 627 ", "answer": "-1498", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6860", "question": "-8 * -413 + 693 - -389 * -237 ", "answer": "-88196", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6861", "question": "-281 - -640 * -287 * -155 + 244 ", "answer": "28470363", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6862", "question": "-8530 + -8603 ", "answer": "-17133", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6863", "question": "49 + 89 ", "answer": "138", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6864", "question": "44 + 13 + 92 ", "answer": "149", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6865", "question": "-857456 * -651030 * -999031 + -82662 + -781408 ", "answer": "-557688655218154150", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6866", "question": "-89873 + 86484 - 52908 - -40458 ", "answer": "-15839", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6867", "question": "-4259 * 6118 - -7994 - -4698 ", "answer": "-26043870", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6868", "question": "-710637 - 974276 + -526684 ", "answer": "-2211597", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6869", "question": "-769 - 28 + -618 - 203 * -874 ", "answer": "176007", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6870", "question": "-8202 - -2365 * -8355 ", "answer": "-19767777", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6871", "question": "905 * -209 - -374 ", "answer": "-188771", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6872", "question": "-961 * 726 ", "answer": "-697686", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6873", "question": "347 + -421 + -407 * -181 ", "answer": "73593", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6874", "question": "2699 * 3210 * 3819 - 3001 + 6690 ", "answer": "33087017699", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6875", "question": "-91559 + -95090 ", "answer": "-186649", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6876", "question": "838 * -951 * 632 + 467 ", "answer": "-503664349", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6877", "question": "-57736 * -9102 * 30714 ", "answer": "16140608493408", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6878", "question": "-4444 - 406 * 2819 - 3963 ", "answer": "-1152921", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6879", "question": "33 + -3 + -20 ", "answer": "10", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6880", "question": "-882539 * 774019 - -503710 * 631037 - 406227 ", "answer": "-365242713198", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6881", "question": "-1659 - -7900 * 7088 * -5611 + -6651 ", "answer": "-314189075510", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6882", "question": "-53273 * 43120 + -43670 * -84903 + -64864 ", "answer": "1410517386", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6883", "question": "64 + 59 * 78 ", "answer": "4666", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6884", "question": "-95411 + -543591 - 4624 ", "answer": "-643626", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6885", "question": "1495 + -2927 * -7594 - -7258 ", "answer": "22236391", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6886", "question": "-269 * 402 - -722 ", "answer": "-107416", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6887", "question": "2141 * 1661 - -2513 ", "answer": "3558714", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6888", "question": "3788 + -1753 * -2464 ", "answer": "4323180", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6889", "question": "498218 - -488898 * -709332 - 43533 ", "answer": "-346790541451", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6890", "question": "292 - 171 + -237 * -816 ", "answer": "193513", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6891", "question": "-96 + 9 ", "answer": "-87", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6892", "question": "-53 * -24 ", "answer": "1272", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6893", "question": "92 + 49 - -11 ", "answer": "152", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6894", "question": "-205680 * -264897 ", "answer": "54484014960", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6895", "question": "-50124 + 16061 - 23612 ", "answer": "-57675", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6896", "question": "48198 * 30653 * -69461 * 62960 - -14377 ", "answer": "-6461119199123046263", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6897", "question": "17110 - 60612 ", "answer": "-43502", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6898", "question": "50 + -91 * 90 - 59 + 94 ", "answer": "-8105", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6899", "question": "71104 - -26153 + -56390 ", "answer": "40867", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6900", "question": "-14030 * 27931 + 18803 ", "answer": "-391853127", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6901", "question": "-264 * 736 + -951 + 420 * 71 ", "answer": "-165435", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6902", "question": "564 - 745 + -438 + 833 ", "answer": "214", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6903", "question": "34 + -7 + 6 ", "answer": "33", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6904", "question": "903 * 6007 ", "answer": "5424321", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6905", "question": "-858 - -737 ", "answer": "-121", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6906", "question": "-801357 + 577523 * -873020 * -892162 - -620048 ", "answer": "449818382117111211", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6907", "question": "48214 * -44491 * 40911 ", "answer": "-87757739106414", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6908", "question": "-447574 - -608831 - -583915 + -283009 * 247393 ", "answer": "-70013700365", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6909", "question": "902879 * -228884 * -811266 * -691317 ", "answer": "-115900550390672267537592", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6910", "question": "-6920 * -2043 * -5645 * -4368 ", "answer": "348594906441600", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6911", "question": "587 * -593 + 902 * -53 * 37 ", "answer": "-2116913", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6912", "question": "557973 * 363658 * 42573 + -794414 * -953128 ", "answer": "8639301878874074", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6913", "question": "-1936 * -5575 - -5088 ", "answer": "10798288", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6914", "question": "9371 - 37730 + -77571 - -19218 - -93937 ", "answer": "7225", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6915", "question": "-657308 * 145369 ", "answer": "-95552206652", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6916", "question": "-27 - -70 + -85 ", "answer": "-42", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6917", "question": "-592999 + 357013 + 720340 ", "answer": "484354", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6918", "question": "-542679 * 857566 * -638587 ", "answer": "297187571698149318", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6919", "question": "-5134 * 8425 - -9381 * 7800 - -1294 ", "answer": "29919144", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6920", "question": "-5516 + 790 * 8746 - -9444 * 4251 ", "answer": "47050268", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6921", "question": "-99191 * 51559 - -7785 + 96245 ", "answer": "-5114084739", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6922", "question": "7587 - -2966 ", "answer": "10553", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6923", "question": "-21637 - 15465 + -76997 + 74091 ", "answer": "-40008", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6924", "question": "545757 + 57224 ", "answer": "602981", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6925", "question": "421 * 255 * 916 * -899 - 876 ", "answer": "-88405125696", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6926", "question": "487516 * 152900 + 337998 * -694283 - -798631 ", "answer": "-160124270403", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6927", "question": "-837 * -5433 - 3011 ", "answer": "4544410", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6928", "question": "666191 * -872854 + -739987 - -368037 ", "answer": "-581487851064", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6929", "question": "739396 + 721842 * -39405 * -526290 + 387664 ", "answer": "14969889603749960", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6930", "question": "81507 + -98326 + -79715 * -83879 * 76387 ", "answer": "510755143248876", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6931", "question": "-8592 * -4030 + 7940 ", "answer": "34633700", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6932", "question": "-89 * -15 ", "answer": "1335", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6933", "question": "94 + 17 ", "answer": "111", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6934", "question": "97 + -72 ", "answer": "25", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6935", "question": "-6952 * 6675 - -1672 ", "answer": "-46402928", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6936", "question": "69237 * 41166 - 60748 ", "answer": "2850149594", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6937", "question": "-42283 + -66867 + -88737 ", "answer": "-197887", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6938", "question": "-6188 + -5249 ", "answer": "-11437", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6939", "question": "-131 * -784 ", "answer": "102704", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6940", "question": "6522 * 73826 - -16188 * 58672 - 99277 ", "answer": "1431176231", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6941", "question": "-49 * -23 - -33 + 74 ", "answer": "1234", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6942", "question": "-349588 * -400366 - 114212 ", "answer": "139963034996", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6943", "question": "-958 - 215 + -237 ", "answer": "-1410", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6944", "question": "64834 * -22034 * -70311 * -3010 * -59326 ", "answer": "17936223193674321542160", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6945", "question": "-46188 * 7341 ", "answer": "-339066108", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6946", "question": "95 + -88 + -15 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6947", "question": "3 + -82 * 37 - 43 ", "answer": "-3074", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6948", "question": "54 + 53 - 7 ", "answer": "100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6949", "question": "-428 - 621 ", "answer": "-1049", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6950", "question": "870866 * -564553 * -780500 + 3391 ", "answer": "383732835066892391", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6951", "question": "-80 * -66 * -62 + 14 ", "answer": "-327346", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6952", "question": "952 - 138 * 686 - -688 ", "answer": "-93028", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6953", "question": "154553 + -602573 ", "answer": "-448020", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6954", "question": "408512 + 371535 ", "answer": "780047", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6955", "question": "727 + 1395 - 1606 ", "answer": "516", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6956", "question": "-733573 * -243964 - 217374 ", "answer": "178965185998", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6957", "question": "-325 + -380 ", "answer": "-705", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6958", "question": "-3431 + -8710 * -9350 * 3084 ", "answer": "251156330569", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6959", "question": "396 + 317 ", "answer": "713", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6960", "question": "380811 - 719771 + 160179 ", "answer": "-178781", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6961", "question": "-288 - -69 * -8 + 613 ", "answer": "-227", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6962", "question": "-521819 - 464032 - -54453 - -834420 - 709743 ", "answer": "-806721", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6963", "question": "-497173 - 70779 * -99431 * 860872 ", "answer": "6058495814167955", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6964", "question": "64 * -64 ", "answer": "-4096", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6965", "question": "-26202 * 69211 + -39270 - 35943 ", "answer": "-1813541835", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6966", "question": "-236 * -969 * -403 * 641 ", "answer": "-59074336932", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6967", "question": "-64132 + -84571 - 79813 * 21666 - 56118 ", "answer": "-1729433279", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6968", "question": "7867 * -176 * 9146 - 6644 ", "answer": "-12663485076", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6969", "question": "96 - -99 ", "answer": "195", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6970", "question": "185 + 508 + -513 - -378 ", "answer": "558", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6971", "question": "-106 + -640 - 568 ", "answer": "-1314", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6972", "question": "-26 - -38 - -2 ", "answer": "14", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6973", "question": "-370876 - -740077 ", "answer": "369201", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6974", "question": "253 + 330 ", "answer": "583", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6975", "question": "-1654 + -8700 * -2269 ", "answer": "19738646", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6976", "question": "-66196 + -378985 * -725385 + 757128 + 991784 ", "answer": "274911716941", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6977", "question": "-50597 + -42243 * -38765 * -23812 + 3109 ", "answer": "-38993338147228", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6978", "question": "1773 * 5928 ", "answer": "10510344", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6979", "question": "38001 - 2055 * -87807 + -35885 ", "answer": "180445501", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6980", "question": "9444 * -5490 + -5077 + -6178 * -8146 ", "answer": "-1526649", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6981", "question": "-679453 + 464200 + 909908 * 896872 ", "answer": "816070792523", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6982", "question": "-366 + 625 * -163 + -34 ", "answer": "-102275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6983", "question": "7535 + 6920 ", "answer": "14455", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6984", "question": "463 + 9109 ", "answer": "9572", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6985", "question": "-31280 * 27854 + 94003 - -43505 ", "answer": "-871135612", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6986", "question": "8262 + -5133 * -8200 - -9559 ", "answer": "42108421", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6987", "question": "395 - 208 * -909 * -387 - -214 ", "answer": "-73170255", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6988", "question": "588 * 109 + -184 ", "answer": "63908", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "6989", "question": "5 - 49 ", "answer": "-44", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6990", "question": "-7066 + -1948 ", "answer": "-9014", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6991", "question": "67 - -48 ", "answer": "115", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "6992", "question": "-410744 + 306889 ", "answer": "-103855", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6993", "question": "625927 - -182432 - -444014 + -189932 ", "answer": "1062441", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6994", "question": "-98570 - 92721 - 69468 ", "answer": "-260759", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6995", "question": "-5462 - -2329 * -8967 * 1201 ", "answer": "-25081861205", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6996", "question": "84213 - 46364 ", "answer": "37849", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "6997", "question": "-4884 * -6444 * -8906 - 8903 - -6242 ", "answer": "-280294052037", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "6998", "question": "-254385 * 228415 * -218886 * 846838 ", "answer": "10770464720940782744700", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "6999", "question": "2245 - -5164 + 9380 ", "answer": "16789", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7000", "question": "7524 * -6867 + 9212 ", "answer": "-51658096", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7001", "question": "74035 - 10478 - -22425 ", "answer": "85982", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7002", "question": "-833 * 224 + -601 ", "answer": "-187193", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7003", "question": "356179 + 904686 * 43787 * -515260 ", "answer": "-20411244735203141", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7004", "question": "-6774 - 6589 ", "answer": "-13363", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7005", "question": "-394 + 2904 * 8476 ", "answer": "24613910", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7006", "question": "-4190 - -7606 + 4874 * -3787 * -6173 ", "answer": "113940237390", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7007", "question": "-3 - 71 * 83 * -63 + 89 ", "answer": "371345", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7008", "question": "-64841 - -6648 + 52994 + -5453 + -15085 ", "answer": "-25737", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7009", "question": "8622 * -2998 - -4222 + 7997 ", "answer": "-25836537", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7010", "question": "5900 - -991 ", "answer": "6891", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7011", "question": "9950 * -9321 ", "answer": "-92743950", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7012", "question": "5810 * 9334 ", "answer": "54230540", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7013", "question": "-58725 - -16423 - -61622 - 34457 * 98893 ", "answer": "-3407536781", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7014", "question": "-106459 * 29738 * 202827 - 207761 ", "answer": "-642125484984395", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7015", "question": "-519 - -424 * -147 - 562 - 534 ", "answer": "-63943", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7016", "question": "49829 * 472697 - 544059 - 429677 + -928694 ", "answer": "23552116383", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7017", "question": "-619 * -772 * -338 * -722 ", "answer": "116616995248", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7018", "question": "164017 + -832774 ", "answer": "-668757", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7019", "question": "87 - -94 * -61 - 45 ", "answer": "-5692", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7020", "question": "-11449 - 4943 - 81737 * 74757 ", "answer": "-6110429301", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7021", "question": "1226 + 4532 ", "answer": "5758", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7022", "question": "-121 * -2410 * 6904 * -7031 - -3607 ", "answer": "-14155339615033", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7023", "question": "-481 + 301 + 980 ", "answer": "800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7024", "question": "91316 + 76326 ", "answer": "167642", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7025", "question": "133 - -824 - 304 ", "answer": "653", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7026", "question": "979742 + -212311 - 368631 - -55385 * -622283 ", "answer": "-34464745155", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7027", "question": "842674 + 790891 + -292798 + -141739 ", "answer": "1199028", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7028", "question": "-79520 * 7091 ", "answer": "-563876320", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7029", "question": "-13320 * -15863 - 907 * -39734 ", "answer": "247333898", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7030", "question": "1428 + -4245 - 5622 ", "answer": "-8439", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7031", "question": "-73804 - 97826 ", "answer": "-171630", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7032", "question": "9274 * 9922 ", "answer": "92016628", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7033", "question": "-40 + 68 + -66 * -15 ", "answer": "1018", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7034", "question": "34576 + 17432 ", "answer": "52008", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7035", "question": "-255424 - 366291 * 874305 * 653255 + -836020 ", "answer": "-209204948213558969", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7036", "question": "997 - 607 * -48 * 864 - -810 ", "answer": "25175311", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7037", "question": "-91 - -93 * -50 * -100 - -65 ", "answer": "464974", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7038", "question": "712268 - -557885 * -116292 ", "answer": "-64876850152", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7039", "question": "838 * -302 + 737 - -680 + 885 ", "answer": "-250774", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7040", "question": "4266 * 4687 * 9703 * -430 ", "answer": "-83423862099180", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7041", "question": "40 - -32 * -90 + -14 + -95 ", "answer": "-2949", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7042", "question": "-435 - 92 - 471 + 336 ", "answer": "-662", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7043", "question": "-424900 * 55875 * 409684 + 805735 ", "answer": "-9726425627344265", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7044", "question": "974981 - 508436 ", "answer": "466545", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7045", "question": "-1650 * -7510 - 3218 - 719 - -6139 ", "answer": "12393702", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7046", "question": "-842313 - -423120 ", "answer": "-419193", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7047", "question": "5877 * 7575 - -1955 ", "answer": "44520230", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7048", "question": "1735 + 7432 ", "answer": "9167", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7049", "question": "381 + 355 + -839 + 465 ", "answer": "362", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7050", "question": "-275196 + -967131 - -786751 ", "answer": "-455576", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7051", "question": "-379933 * -853650 ", "answer": "324329805450", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7052", "question": "-124 + 4893 * -4025 - 3682 - -7514 ", "answer": "-19690617", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7053", "question": "-6872 + 8186 ", "answer": "1314", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7054", "question": "-252 + 678 + 227 * -496 - 302 ", "answer": "-112468", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7055", "question": "7705 + -5509 ", "answer": "2196", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7056", "question": "6301 + -5725 * 4609 - -1044 + -9992 ", "answer": "-26389172", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7057", "question": "-51308 + -57705 - -42157 - 36882 - 21564 ", "answer": "-125302", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7058", "question": "-6959 + -1567 ", "answer": "-8526", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7059", "question": "-54482 * 29847 * -94240 ", "answer": "153245949696960", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7060", "question": "-94 + -34 ", "answer": "-128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7061", "question": "-278227 + -577879 - 446139 + 920804 ", "answer": "-381441", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7062", "question": "-34 * -17 ", "answer": "578", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7063", "question": "-627 - 3268 * 6148 * 8408 + 5424 ", "answer": "-168930706115", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7064", "question": "-94 + 173 + 942 ", "answer": "1021", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7065", "question": "-205 - -582 ", "answer": "377", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7066", "question": "-38 - -38 ", "answer": "0", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7067", "question": "59589 * 2091 + -963628 ", "answer": "123636971", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7068", "question": "-243 * -751 - -184 ", "answer": "182677", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7069", "question": "-82 * 90 + -100 ", "answer": "-7480", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7070", "question": "270920 * 939807 + 622748 ", "answer": "254613135188", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7071", "question": "5819 + -7762 - 2337 - 2351 * 1680 ", "answer": "-3953960", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7072", "question": "-83 - -94 ", "answer": "11", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7073", "question": "-166 * 115 + -675 + 749 ", "answer": "-19016", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7074", "question": "-49813 - -96928 - -22235 ", "answer": "69350", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7075", "question": "71 + -74 + -5 + -66 * -39 ", "answer": "2566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7076", "question": "-275445 + -855614 + 725173 + -975456 ", "answer": "-1381342", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7077", "question": "-930579 * 608265 * -482287 ", "answer": "272993075368039845", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7078", "question": "70819 + 84167 + -91677 * 31987 * 88048 ", "answer": "-258198312022566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7079", "question": "-57177 - 3284 - 85937 - 65464 ", "answer": "-211862", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7080", "question": "930 - 87 * 382 ", "answer": "-32304", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7081", "question": "-1261 * 1142 ", "answer": "-1440062", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7082", "question": "-27 - -95 ", "answer": "68", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7083", "question": "-796 - -506 - 305 * 767 ", "answer": "-234225", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7084", "question": "922891 - -310655 + -217655 ", "answer": "1015891", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7085", "question": "61 * -24 ", "answer": "-1464", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7086", "question": "-72052 - -42523 + -69971 - -71373 * -8172 ", "answer": "-583359656", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7087", "question": "29 - -229 + 908 * 390 ", "answer": "354378", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7088", "question": "3286 + -8699 ", "answer": "-5413", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7089", "question": "380522 - 400788 ", "answer": "-20266", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7090", "question": "-737 - 607 + 38 - -805 * -81 ", "answer": "-66511", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7091", "question": "778937 * -158797 ", "answer": "-123692858789", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7092", "question": "-78 - 77 * 55 + -91 ", "answer": "-4404", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7093", "question": "478 * 509 * -618 ", "answer": "-150360636", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7094", "question": "949 * -940 + -870 * 982 ", "answer": "-1746400", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7095", "question": "-50 + -41 ", "answer": "-91", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7096", "question": "-311 * 95 * 525 * -128 ", "answer": "1985424000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7097", "question": "80 * 29 - -87 - 34 + 90 ", "answer": "2463", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7098", "question": "-453847 * -488493 + -64544 * 960202 + 572789 ", "answer": "159726377472", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7099", "question": "828863 - -12075 * -387932 * 28763 ", "answer": "-134733913171837", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7100", "question": "57 * 189 + 928 ", "answer": "11701", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7101", "question": "3834 - -55580 * -60127 - 30802 ", "answer": "-3341885628", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7102", "question": "84 * 66 ", "answer": "5544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7103", "question": "-166706 - -458587 * -55995 * 933631 ", "answer": "-23974317451201721", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7104", "question": "50 + 55 * -74 + -68 ", "answer": "-4088", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7105", "question": "-975 * -759 * 244 ", "answer": "180566100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7106", "question": "43 + 74 * -72 - 58 * 85 ", "answer": "-10215", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7107", "question": "40 - 46 - -86 * 7 - -32 ", "answer": "628", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7108", "question": "601 + 163 - -72 * 682 ", "answer": "49868", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7109", "question": "-42 + 60 * -4 ", "answer": "-282", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7110", "question": "-5779 + -1215 ", "answer": "-6994", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7111", "question": "508 * 4113 - -6675 * -7636 * -3322 ", "answer": "169325426004", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7112", "question": "73172 * -206466 - -843589 * 724454 ", "answer": "596033895254", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7113", "question": "1455 * -23973 * -24738 ", "answer": "862879127670", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7114", "question": "-706399 * -416491 + -848976 ", "answer": "294207976933", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7115", "question": "-3 - -93 * -19 ", "answer": "-1770", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7116", "question": "-131 + -306 + 838 - 483 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7117", "question": "-625 + -797 ", "answer": "-1422", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7118", "question": "841 + 6643 + 7164 - 1138 ", "answer": "13510", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7119", "question": "90106 + -35655 + 8925 + -94904 + -3646 ", "answer": "-35174", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7120", "question": "95 * -7 + -51 * -83 - -66 ", "answer": "3634", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7121", "question": "26151 * 47735 ", "answer": "1248317985", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7122", "question": "-90 + 86 ", "answer": "-4", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7123", "question": "91308 - 96902 - -16427 * -30547 ", "answer": "-501801163", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7124", "question": "-6444 * 9654 + 191 - 5429 ", "answer": "-62215614", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7125", "question": "-6904 * -5713 * 3314 + 9425 ", "answer": "130712626753", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7126", "question": "105 * -592 + -128 * 8 ", "answer": "-63184", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7127", "question": "-298753 * 767162 - -14025 + 653447 * 139122 ", "answer": "-138283081427", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7128", "question": "-169811 - 772088 - 867384 - 405517 ", "answer": "-2214800", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7129", "question": "-938 - 85 - -599 + 510 * -440 ", "answer": "-224824", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7130", "question": "-9448 * -69545 * -63158 + 59874 + -8380 ", "answer": "-41498668691786", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7131", "question": "2087 + 1528 - -541 + -6020 ", "answer": "-1864", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7132", "question": "91 + -96 ", "answer": "-5", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7133", "question": "92 * -13 - -95 + -55 ", "answer": "-1156", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7134", "question": "-24 * -72 * 24 ", "answer": "41472", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7135", "question": "-514 * 337 ", "answer": "-173218", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7136", "question": "-9646 - 63923 * 59214 ", "answer": "-3785146168", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7137", "question": "-2859 - -73195 ", "answer": "70336", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7138", "question": "-202047 * 867838 * 572064 ", "answer": "-100308026848912704", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7139", "question": "-501 - 246 + -910 * 897 ", "answer": "-817017", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7140", "question": "61976 - 550536 * -19934 - -310296 ", "answer": "10974756896", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7141", "question": "-7263 + -3080 + 5838 + -1404 ", "answer": "-5909", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7142", "question": "64 * 18 + 23 ", "answer": "1175", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7143", "question": "47 + -34 * -20 + -66 ", "answer": "661", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7144", "question": "-320 - -837 * 737 ", "answer": "616549", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7145", "question": "-535 + -678 * -164 + -676 ", "answer": "109981", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7146", "question": "-42080 * -41576 * 46692 * -83519 - -69212 ", "answer": "-6822541680444126628", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7147", "question": "-84387 - 98714 ", "answer": "-183101", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7148", "question": "-3495 * 7849 + 2899 - 624 + 6895 ", "answer": "-27423085", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7149", "question": "74 + -50 + -38 - -49 - 43 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7150", "question": "-911 + 624 - 214 * -180 * 636 ", "answer": "24498433", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7151", "question": "253698 - 222619 ", "answer": "31079", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7152", "question": "-1963 - 6443 + -1992 ", "answer": "-10398", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7153", "question": "3 + -26 - -83 + 19 * -71 ", "answer": "-1289", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7154", "question": "366662 * 554250 + 87763 * -139456 + 850040 ", "answer": "190984186612", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7155", "question": "466018 * -214674 * -168983 * 13003 - -996895 ", "answer": "219820766941031394163", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7156", "question": "-88 + 70 ", "answer": "-18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7157", "question": "-705 - 490 * -1000 ", "answer": "489295", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7158", "question": "-38 - -463 * -968 ", "answer": "-448222", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7159", "question": "35 - 11 - -18 + -35 ", "answer": "7", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7160", "question": "4 + -844 ", "answer": "-840", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7161", "question": "-803463 + 962057 ", "answer": "158594", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7162", "question": "655243 + 843650 + 670717 - -902573 ", "answer": "3072183", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7163", "question": "-435534 - 999468 + 777126 * 571784 + -891661 ", "answer": "444345886121", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7164", "question": "-18483 * 81048 - -23183 - -84354 ", "answer": "-1497902647", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7165", "question": "-520 - -660 * -215 + 35 ", "answer": "-142385", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7166", "question": "-709050 * 129414 - 493149 - 518331 ", "answer": "-91762008180", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7167", "question": "-70968 * 1252 ", "answer": "-88851936", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7168", "question": "815 + 69 * -41 - 247 * -856 ", "answer": "209418", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7169", "question": "-64118 - 44416 ", "answer": "-108534", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7170", "question": "204342 * 785312 + 934099 - 107900 ", "answer": "160473050903", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7171", "question": "4 * -19 - -16 * -61 ", "answer": "-1052", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7172", "question": "-72200 * 93879 * -76990 ", "answer": "521843131962000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7173", "question": "6567 - 2344 + 7914 + 7259 ", "answer": "19396", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7174", "question": "84 * 40 ", "answer": "3360", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7175", "question": "97640 - -37881 * 14394 * -37753 - -57496 ", "answer": "-20585167175706", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7176", "question": "74714 + 931401 * -543798 * -580782 ", "answer": "294162598887695150", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7177", "question": "74 * 96 - 98 + -36 ", "answer": "6970", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7178", "question": "24921 * 491342 ", "answer": "12244733982", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7179", "question": "228343 - 410519 - -334576 + 352981 ", "answer": "505381", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7180", "question": "-7331 * -4966 ", "answer": "36405746", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7181", "question": "-8 * -66 + 88 + -33 + 7 ", "answer": "590", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7182", "question": "-60 * -76 * -14 + 63 * -74 ", "answer": "-68502", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7183", "question": "-73 * 95 - 81 + -27 * 83 ", "answer": "-9257", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7184", "question": "514383 * -51692 * -203439 * 643037 - 845216 ", "answer": "3478404768665465205532", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7185", "question": "-80 * 75 * -80 + -77 ", "answer": "479923", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7186", "question": "198716 + -106121 - 131194 ", "answer": "-38599", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7187", "question": "89 - -87 ", "answer": "176", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7188", "question": "6049 + -2370 * 2105 * 1176 * -5725 ", "answer": "33587931516049", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7189", "question": "-5170 - 2492 * 3480 * 3869 - 1496 ", "answer": "-33552593706", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7190", "question": "-583517 - -58846 * 73609 + 393019 + 862872 ", "answer": "4332267588", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7191", "question": "8443 - -4223 * 7777 + -7494 ", "answer": "32843220", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7192", "question": "-931 - -612 * 150 * 51 ", "answer": "4680869", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7193", "question": "-23183 + -53576 + -82657 ", "answer": "-159416", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7194", "question": "631653 * -689702 * 505284 - 758806 * 926100 ", "answer": "-220128858384089904", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7195", "question": "-482 + 876 + 745 * -108 ", "answer": "-80066", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7196", "question": "439492 + 524103 ", "answer": "963595", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7197", "question": "63127 - 82873 - 95719 - 11781 ", "answer": "-127246", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7198", "question": "40 + 16 + -62 ", "answer": "-6", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7199", "question": "674942 + 418863 - 759274 + 555929 * 146224 ", "answer": "81290496627", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7200", "question": "5576 + -8152 * -8787 + 7070 * 4298 ", "answer": "102024060", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7201", "question": "18103 - 55242 * 42020 + -34242 * -52198 ", "answer": "-533886821", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7202", "question": "-26 * 93 ", "answer": "-2418", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7203", "question": "46 * 77 - 69 * -31 ", "answer": "5681", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7204", "question": "45 - 63 + -56 ", "answer": "-74", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7205", "question": "-50515 - 26762 - -23649 - 79330 - -92298 ", "answer": "-40660", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7206", "question": "32195 + -67405 ", "answer": "-35210", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7207", "question": "-150 - 744 - -106 ", "answer": "-788", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7208", "question": "-89 * 13 ", "answer": "-1157", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7209", "question": "-3 - -68 + 64 - -81 ", "answer": "210", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7210", "question": "5964 - 6139 * 6001 - -9985 ", "answer": "-36824190", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7211", "question": "-8343 * -49 ", "answer": "408807", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7212", "question": "305 + 569 ", "answer": "874", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7213", "question": "-47 + -89 - -79 - -97 + 37 ", "answer": "77", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7214", "question": "-874 * -990554 * 713904 * -146212 ", "answer": "-90367532045007115008", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7215", "question": "787 + 284 ", "answer": "1071", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7216", "question": "725 - 619 ", "answer": "106", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7217", "question": "-823568 * 968146 - -350052 ", "answer": "-797333714876", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7218", "question": "25715 * -90217 * 4791 - -22703 - 31947 ", "answer": "-11114785381849", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7219", "question": "-840247 - 105586 * 755576 ", "answer": "-79779087783", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7220", "question": "-861 * -149 ", "answer": "128289", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7221", "question": "72021 + 88526 * 9661 * 94284 ", "answer": "80636361466845", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7222", "question": "-535955 + 353989 + -976947 + -375839 ", "answer": "-1534752", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7223", "question": "-568168 + -440498 * -479799 + -551623 + -47156 ", "answer": "211349332955", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7224", "question": "99899 * 74471 ", "answer": "7439578429", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7225", "question": "-494 + -326 * 903 * -527 * 618 ", "answer": "95874792814", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7226", "question": "-3049 - 3346 ", "answer": "-6395", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7227", "question": "-1187 - -1224 * -8959 * -4633 + -7959 ", "answer": "50804616382", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7228", "question": "329 + 824 - 456 ", "answer": "697", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7229", "question": "-6153 + 5418 + -947 * 9768 * 5801 ", "answer": "-53660967831", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7230", "question": "585 + -9895 + -4208 ", "answer": "-13518", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7231", "question": "189 * 248 + -713 ", "answer": "46159", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7232", "question": "-717226 * 177491 ", "answer": "-127301159966", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7233", "question": "463 - -243 - -109 + 219 ", "answer": "1034", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7234", "question": "-3569 + 8173 - 5214 - -7543 ", "answer": "6933", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7235", "question": "54 + 519 - -490 ", "answer": "1063", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7236", "question": "48 - 28 * -61 * -76 ", "answer": "-129760", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7237", "question": "649543 - 843144 - -7839 ", "answer": "-185762", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7238", "question": "883 + 338 * -430 + 460 * 188 ", "answer": "-57977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7239", "question": "52958 + 10454 - -98512 * 12287 ", "answer": "1210480356", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7240", "question": "23468 - 99238 - 9063 * 60436 - -5259 ", "answer": "-547801979", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7241", "question": "5084 - 4103 + -3714 ", "answer": "-2733", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7242", "question": "403 - 659 * 133 ", "answer": "-87244", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7243", "question": "-461103 - -65349 * 270389 + -154230 + -312359 ", "answer": "17668723069", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7244", "question": "-8970 * -2578 ", "answer": "23124660", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7245", "question": "1509 + -4453 * -3399 * 565 - -3371 ", "answer": "8551701935", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7246", "question": "-93811 - -38362 * 79509 * -36909 - 27602 ", "answer": "-112577036359935", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7247", "question": "-2644 - -6468 - -9717 ", "answer": "13541", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7248", "question": "4114 - 7339 + 1082 * 8418 - 884 ", "answer": "9104167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7249", "question": "63401 * 36725 ", "answer": "2328401725", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7250", "question": "144514 + 66200 - 849746 ", "answer": "-639032", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7251", "question": "-337608 - -466891 ", "answer": "129283", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7252", "question": "-90473 - 59187 ", "answer": "-149660", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7253", "question": "-32098 - 20808 - -46752 - -78292 - -85790 ", "answer": "157928", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7254", "question": "-212 - 25 ", "answer": "-237", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7255", "question": "-431202 - -534239 + -65455 - -252070 * 427236 ", "answer": "107693416102", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7256", "question": "63 * 16 * -20 * -57 + -69 ", "answer": "1149051", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7257", "question": "79 - -44 * -34 ", "answer": "-1417", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7258", "question": "-950 * 670 - 106 ", "answer": "-636606", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7259", "question": "85 + 13 ", "answer": "98", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7260", "question": "69 - 32 + -66 + 34 - -89 ", "answer": "94", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7261", "question": "517 + -234 + -185 - -235 + 526 ", "answer": "859", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7262", "question": "-155 - -328 - -448 - -787 ", "answer": "1408", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7263", "question": "-59706 + -60847 * -513286 ", "answer": "31231853536", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7264", "question": "-3383 * 8046 + 6105 + 1475 * 9355 ", "answer": "-13414888", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7265", "question": "-90413 - -22201 + 7303 + -4218 * 98507 ", "answer": "-415563435", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7266", "question": "478061 - -334906 * 990935 + 373542 - -299658 ", "answer": "331871228371", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7267", "question": "-596 + -914 ", "answer": "-1510", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7268", "question": "-23335 * -28798 * 29582 + -205 ", "answer": "19879143343855", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7269", "question": "-114616 - 365015 * -982076 + 730790 ", "answer": "358473087314", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7270", "question": "-7275 - -8861 ", "answer": "1586", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7271", "question": "-273855 * -785157 * 158382 + -19748 ", "answer": "34055166220140022", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7272", "question": "-213905 - -400880 ", "answer": "186975", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7273", "question": "20914 + 70550 + -92117 + 69590 - -88686 ", "answer": "157623", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7274", "question": "-17627 - 596610 ", "answer": "-614237", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7275", "question": "14 - -79 + 82 - -78 + 47 ", "answer": "300", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7276", "question": "-537 - 60 * -646 ", "answer": "38223", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7277", "question": "757 - -238 - -492 ", "answer": "1487", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7278", "question": "-36746 * 40721 - 27587 * 47104 * 3829 ", "answer": "-4977121199658", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7279", "question": "-72176 * -15997 * -43542 + -9217 ", "answer": "-50273570219041", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7280", "question": "95671 - -11360 * 29135 - 68841 ", "answer": "331000430", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7281", "question": "34 + 19 - 93 + -41 * -6 ", "answer": "206", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7282", "question": "6591 - -9296 - -3213 ", "answer": "19100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7283", "question": "-49 * -850 - 635 * 389 ", "answer": "-205365", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7284", "question": "36 * -26 - -37 ", "answer": "-899", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7285", "question": "-240 * 7 ", "answer": "-1680", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7286", "question": "8699 * -7539 ", "answer": "-65581761", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7287", "question": "74 * 59 + 11 * 66 ", "answer": "5092", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7288", "question": "-33 - 68 ", "answer": "-101", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7289", "question": "60649 - -35466 - -1202 * 35091 - 92040 ", "answer": "42183457", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7290", "question": "68 - 329 * 81 ", "answer": "-26581", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7291", "question": "-532 + 38 - 44 - 683 ", "answer": "-1221", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7292", "question": "755 * 86 - 918 - -169 - 569 ", "answer": "63612", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7293", "question": "-1721 + 8898 * 3195 + -2620 - -2206 ", "answer": "28426975", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7294", "question": "4 + 1 + 74 ", "answer": "79", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7295", "question": "-81 * 13 + 51 ", "answer": "-1002", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7296", "question": "972 - -924 * 546 + -484 ", "answer": "504992", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7297", "question": "955 + -649 * 160 ", "answer": "-102885", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7298", "question": "10606 * -9148 * -19538 - -44389 ", "answer": "1895648860533", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7299", "question": "6245 * -933 + 1804 ", "answer": "-5824781", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7300", "question": "26 - 713 ", "answer": "-687", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7301", "question": "-1647 * 4349 - 6870 * -61 ", "answer": "-6743733", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7302", "question": "-348958 + -81355 - 18304 - 868612 ", "answer": "-1317229", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7303", "question": "962243 - -809861 - 424902 + 221560 * 508110 ", "answer": "112578198802", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7304", "question": "89 + -74 + -27 + 14 * -98 ", "answer": "-1384", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7305", "question": "675034 * -272185 + -621191 * 914979 * 17090 ", "answer": "-9713741878741300", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7306", "question": "-226 - -4272 * 6482 - 7474 ", "answer": "27683404", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7307", "question": "48200 + 38043 + -81935 ", "answer": "4308", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7308", "question": "-123 + 123 + -732 ", "answer": "-732", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7309", "question": "-1419 + 6073 ", "answer": "4654", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7310", "question": "21 - -54 + 33 * 24 ", "answer": "867", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7311", "question": "4348 * 7476 * 324 ", "answer": "10531829952", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7312", "question": "14 + -71 ", "answer": "-57", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7313", "question": "-717 * -382 - 65 * 637 ", "answer": "232489", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7314", "question": "-7 * -38 * 75 * -97 ", "answer": "-1935150", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7315", "question": "-124 + 467 + -662 - -586 * -647 ", "answer": "-379461", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7316", "question": "155 - -584 + 282 ", "answer": "1021", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7317", "question": "46383 + -30890 ", "answer": "15493", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7318", "question": "-66 - -68 - 84 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7319", "question": "201189 - -245049 - 123063 + -530071 ", "answer": "-206896", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7320", "question": "96247 + 78334 * 48178 ", "answer": "3774071699", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7321", "question": "-928514 * 355461 ", "answer": "-330050514954", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7322", "question": "107656 + 665807 ", "answer": "773463", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7323", "question": "1386 - -6741 - 768 * -4984 + -1052 ", "answer": "3834787", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7324", "question": "29 + 89 * 48 - 90 ", "answer": "4211", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7325", "question": "-795 * 313 + 196 * -879 ", "answer": "-421119", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7326", "question": "34 + -22 + -27 * 51 ", "answer": "-1365", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7327", "question": "-19668 - -84574 + -68028 * 24772 + -49324 ", "answer": "-1685174034", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7328", "question": "-666126 + 678561 * 181493 ", "answer": "123153405447", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7329", "question": "-552 - -8017 ", "answer": "7465", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7330", "question": "-1595 + -6150 ", "answer": "-7745", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7331", "question": "19953 - 52766 - -14869 ", "answer": "-17944", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7332", "question": "26 * -97 - -87 ", "answer": "-2435", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7333", "question": "-697828 + 155723 ", "answer": "-542105", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7334", "question": "876 - 434 ", "answer": "442", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7335", "question": "3679 * 6748 - -9450 + -5193 + -4936 ", "answer": "24825213", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7336", "question": "13906 - 28586 - -94882 ", "answer": "80202", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7337", "question": "-413586 * -292955 - -691387 + 682540 * 374735 ", "answer": "376934404917", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7338", "question": "-4295 - 3153 * -3209 - -8726 ", "answer": "10122408", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7339", "question": "423 + 972 * 228 + 441 + 413 ", "answer": "222893", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7340", "question": "-47 * 57 ", "answer": "-2679", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7341", "question": "-57 - -51 ", "answer": "-6", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7342", "question": "-95546 * 48267 + -22942 - 91482 ", "answer": "-4611833206", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7343", "question": "-11 - -81 ", "answer": "70", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7344", "question": "-107 + 631 + 170 * 687 ", "answer": "117314", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7345", "question": "868 + 903 - 228 + 959 + 105 ", "answer": "2607", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7346", "question": "-685 - 412 - 370 - -14 + -269 ", "answer": "-1722", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7347", "question": "-5502 * 1331 - -8889 ", "answer": "-7314273", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7348", "question": "-10017 * 84899 - -69820 * 20994 - -95761 ", "answer": "615463558", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7349", "question": "-111633 + 569191 - 331178 ", "answer": "126380", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7350", "question": "-55419 * -810357 + -192369 - 755150 + -332618 ", "answer": "44907894446", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7351", "question": "-58757 + -29405 - 70792 ", "answer": "-158954", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7352", "question": "-5574 + -4864 * -3454 * -7773 - 9359 ", "answer": "-130588404821", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7353", "question": "3787 - 8697 + 4355 + -7823 ", "answer": "-8378", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7354", "question": "902 * -727 ", "answer": "-655754", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7355", "question": "243 + 591 - -195 ", "answer": "1029", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7356", "question": "42 + 73 + 65 ", "answer": "180", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7357", "question": "11 + -91 + 75 - 76 ", "answer": "-81", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7358", "question": "768 + 941 * 197 - -763 ", "answer": "186908", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7359", "question": "54728 - -65674 - 36365 ", "answer": "84037", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7360", "question": "7085 + -9715 ", "answer": "-2630", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7361", "question": "727529 * 992111 ", "answer": "721789523719", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7362", "question": "-891646 + -849105 + 547804 + 388844 * -395535 ", "answer": "-153802604487", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7363", "question": "4878 + -91672 - 40373 ", "answer": "-127167", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7364", "question": "-622809 - 847708 + 885256 - -910581 + 217638 ", "answer": "542958", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7365", "question": "14241 + 70204 ", "answer": "84445", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7366", "question": "90513 - -46525 ", "answer": "137038", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7367", "question": "11 - 32 ", "answer": "-21", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7368", "question": "80178 * -10610 ", "answer": "-850688580", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7369", "question": "-640063 - -836513 ", "answer": "196450", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7370", "question": "3345 * -5003 - 3811 - -1800 ", "answer": "-16737046", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7371", "question": "703 * -156 + -241 * -715 ", "answer": "62647", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7372", "question": "-90 - -34 + 42 ", "answer": "-14", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7373", "question": "-64305 + -54748 + 21035 + -65248 ", "answer": "-163266", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7374", "question": "-17844 + 8706 + 95350 + 86766 ", "answer": "172978", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7375", "question": "-161593 - 661044 ", "answer": "-822637", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7376", "question": "-628 - -462 + -128 * -316 ", "answer": "40282", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7377", "question": "-74 * -89 ", "answer": "6586", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7378", "question": "-44 + -39 + 6 + 2 * 5 ", "answer": "-67", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7379", "question": "593 - 24 + 249 * -766 ", "answer": "-190165", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7380", "question": "6472 + -1029 ", "answer": "5443", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7381", "question": "782698 + 481744 - 2424 * 199138 ", "answer": "-481446070", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7382", "question": "-308744 * 768357 + -871150 + -166048 ", "answer": "-237226650806", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7383", "question": "784070 + -213513 * 949201 * -650688 ", "answer": "131872824250375814", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7384", "question": "96 * 9 ", "answer": "864", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7385", "question": "10959 * 38794 ", "answer": "425143446", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7386", "question": "3934 + -6729 ", "answer": "-2795", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7387", "question": "-713276 - -98955 + 89040 - 979468 ", "answer": "-1504749", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7388", "question": "-416 + 2057 + 8218 ", "answer": "9859", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7389", "question": "15094 + 24016 ", "answer": "39110", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7390", "question": "-340 - 20 ", "answer": "-360", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7391", "question": "3 - 82 - 36 * -78 + 96 ", "answer": "2825", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7392", "question": "38656 - 631910 * 802886 + 710905 ", "answer": "-507350942699", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7393", "question": "-83 - 3 + 5 ", "answer": "-81", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7394", "question": "5380 - -21272 ", "answer": "26652", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7395", "question": "48 - -59 ", "answer": "107", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7396", "question": "-278 * -426 ", "answer": "118428", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7397", "question": "137893 - -797293 - -678582 - 575498 ", "answer": "1038270", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7398", "question": "94 + 21 * -63 * 67 ", "answer": "-88547", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7399", "question": "-394 - 407 - -526 * -786 ", "answer": "-414237", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7400", "question": "255 - -98 ", "answer": "353", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7401", "question": "82527 + -37474 ", "answer": "45053", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7402", "question": "-2167 * 8422 ", "answer": "-18250474", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7403", "question": "90 * 2360 * 251 - -7130 * 7259 ", "answer": "105069070", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7404", "question": "46514 - -37133 - -56159 ", "answer": "139806", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7405", "question": "720 + 805 * -831 ", "answer": "-668235", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7406", "question": "5554 + 3316 + 6986 - 9649 ", "answer": "6207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7407", "question": "-366009 * -942411 + -872616 - 916225 ", "answer": "344929118858", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7408", "question": "478552 + -691131 ", "answer": "-212579", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7409", "question": "70 + -5 - 41 * -62 ", "answer": "2607", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7410", "question": "-66 * 28 + -30 + 43 + -32 ", "answer": "-1867", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7411", "question": "99597 * 5907 + -49248 * 59038 * -43042 ", "answer": "125145350695287", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7412", "question": "2 - 23 - -100 - 51 ", "answer": "28", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7413", "question": "-856 * -776 * -384 ", "answer": "-255074304", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7414", "question": "-7 - 77 * -83 + 66 ", "answer": "6450", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7415", "question": "-920096 * -637842 + -801243 ", "answer": "586875071589", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7416", "question": "60 - 39 ", "answer": "21", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7417", "question": "616040 * 716276 ", "answer": "441254667040", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7418", "question": "7621 - -4704 * 5815 * 2675 * 2854 ", "answer": "208830913039621", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7419", "question": "573187 + 431276 ", "answer": "1004463", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7420", "question": "7646 + 143 + -1187 + -2695 + -5892 ", "answer": "-1985", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7421", "question": "-52765 * 73023 + 16398 - -40981 ", "answer": "-3853001216", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7422", "question": "-62451 - -7419 + -80617 - 91970 ", "answer": "-227619", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7423", "question": "409 * -229 * 264 + 108 - 86 ", "answer": "-24726482", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7424", "question": "-9378 - 8341 - 9043 - -7714 ", "answer": "-19048", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7425", "question": "-518817 * 2407 + 155003 ", "answer": "-1248637516", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7426", "question": "680 - 973 + -290 - -491 ", "answer": "-92", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7427", "question": "309727 * -37238 - -502972 * 121656 - -821273 ", "answer": "49656768879", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7428", "question": "-818 + -847 ", "answer": "-1665", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7429", "question": "-330 + -5993 * -4318 - 7789 ", "answer": "25869655", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7430", "question": "-679 - 237 * -484 * 287 * -924 ", "answer": "-30419185783", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7431", "question": "5 * -88 ", "answer": "-440", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7432", "question": "276668 - 937487 + -476876 * -174622 ", "answer": "83272380053", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7433", "question": "-2462 + -5838 + -3834 + 7457 ", "answer": "-4677", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7434", "question": "-70 * 57 * 58 ", "answer": "-231420", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7435", "question": "-1 - 49 + -60 + -57 + 0 ", "answer": "-167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7436", "question": "-24363 - 3600 + 68281 * -19852 ", "answer": "-1355542375", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7437", "question": "-72368 * -70887 + 61751 + -93150 + -74508 ", "answer": "5129844509", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7438", "question": "11994 - 91424 * -86727 - -36643 + 54632 ", "answer": "7929032517", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7439", "question": "68 - -36 * 52 ", "answer": "1940", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7440", "question": "-47610 + -473704 * 727000 - -662396 * -934477 ", "answer": "-963376682502", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7441", "question": "133297 * -313790 - -799827 + 270814 + -839164 ", "answer": "-41827034153", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7442", "question": "458196 * -107337 + -799477 + -126643 + -112523 ", "answer": "-49182422695", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7443", "question": "5412 + -9129 ", "answer": "-3717", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7444", "question": "-6 * 8 + -13 + -21 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7445", "question": "-779911 + -538446 * -148504 + -474873 ", "answer": "79960130000", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7446", "question": "-75 * -51 + 58 * 62 ", "answer": "7421", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7447", "question": "-67409 + -7648 * -91033 * -37418 * -25055 ", "answer": "652712172800800751", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7448", "question": "147 * 156 ", "answer": "22932", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7449", "question": "21117 - 14813 - 56107 - 84393 ", "answer": "-134196", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7450", "question": "-994 - -2204 * 7291 * -6190 ", "answer": "-99469364154", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7451", "question": "904 + -796 * -247 - -297 + 872 ", "answer": "198685", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7452", "question": "702528 - 472386 * 859422 * -947352 * -365437 ", "answer": "-140548876432625015136480", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7453", "question": "189 * -622 ", "answer": "-117558", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7454", "question": "72680 - 85176 * -66348 ", "answer": "5651329928", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7455", "question": "-92942 + -19612 * -41791 * 64839 ", "answer": "53142374467246", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7456", "question": "459276 - -397519 ", "answer": "856795", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7457", "question": "-59637 * -77764 + -68997 + -18462 ", "answer": "4637524209", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7458", "question": "18 * 20 + 43 - 70 + -27 ", "answer": "306", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7459", "question": "12 + -68 + 5 ", "answer": "-51", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7460", "question": "926 * 149 * -968 + 239 ", "answer": "-133558593", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7461", "question": "-48 + -27 - -48 * 74 ", "answer": "3477", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7462", "question": "584 * 259 ", "answer": "151256", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7463", "question": "-3790 - 48233 ", "answer": "-52023", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7464", "question": "-95932 * -39260 * 59085 + -40173 ", "answer": "222531263517027", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7465", "question": "77420 * -56102 ", "answer": "-4343416840", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7466", "question": "-49 * -20 + -85 * 67 ", "answer": "-4715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7467", "question": "-92 * 11 ", "answer": "-1012", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7468", "question": "65 + 73 ", "answer": "138", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7469", "question": "-888 * -633 * 192 ", "answer": "107923968", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7470", "question": "-39 - 9 * -66 + 90 * 53 ", "answer": "5325", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7471", "question": "-1722 - 5768 ", "answer": "-7490", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7472", "question": "-472546 - -805956 ", "answer": "333410", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7473", "question": "692 + -969 * -646 * -961 - 20 ", "answer": "-601560342", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7474", "question": "727070 * -631166 + 601933 * 114533 ", "answer": "-389960671331", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7475", "question": "-835 * -1575 - -817 - -3532 ", "answer": "1319474", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7476", "question": "647 + 16 ", "answer": "663", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7477", "question": "-14236 + -78088 + -21557 ", "answer": "-113881", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7478", "question": "-74 - 12 - 14 + -80 - -2 ", "answer": "-178", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7479", "question": "-16 * 23 + 8 - -92 - -31 ", "answer": "-237", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7480", "question": "-82 + -95 - 97 * -2 * 59 ", "answer": "11269", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7481", "question": "-48647 + -18334 * -23701 ", "answer": "434485487", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7482", "question": "852119 + -828869 * 311487 - -137590 ", "answer": "-258180928494", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7483", "question": "-32262 * 15999 * 81744 - 73650 - 45243 ", "answer": "-42192961741965", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7484", "question": "-12396 + -8976 - 72613 ", "answer": "-93985", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7485", "question": "-727 - -19 + 346 ", "answer": "-362", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7486", "question": "426662 - 113128 ", "answer": "313534", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7487", "question": "830 + -813 + 497 * 187 + 814 ", "answer": "93770", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7488", "question": "-348 + 980 ", "answer": "632", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7489", "question": "-67906 - 38247 - -21994 ", "answer": "-84159", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7490", "question": "6986 + 98278 + -4816 + -69156 ", "answer": "31292", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7491", "question": "-4693 * 5571 + -8368 - -2816 ", "answer": "-26150255", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7492", "question": "-18489 - 24202 + -40689 - -44049 + -4151 ", "answer": "-43482", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7493", "question": "-6146 * 6809 ", "answer": "-41848114", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7494", "question": "713193 - -209378 - -778262 + -676842 * 787478 ", "answer": "-532996483643", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7495", "question": "63 - -80 * 29 + 85 ", "answer": "2468", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7496", "question": "75057 - -15210 ", "answer": "90267", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7497", "question": "83 - -40 + -59 * 53 - -50 ", "answer": "-2954", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7498", "question": "-292491 - 186429 * 660365 ", "answer": "-123111479076", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7499", "question": "-581424 - 896175 + 454191 ", "answer": "-1023408", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7500", "question": "8773 * -6172 + 5792 ", "answer": "-54141164", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7501", "question": "4823 * -6774 + -3809 ", "answer": "-32674811", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7502", "question": "7384 + -5579 + -3832 * 9431 * -9027 ", "answer": "326232098789", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7503", "question": "-39 + -53 + -55 * -100 - 10 ", "answer": "5398", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7504", "question": "534082 + 184006 - -730428 - -370849 * 672346 ", "answer": "249340290270", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7505", "question": "41 * 3 + -100 * -96 ", "answer": "9723", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7506", "question": "562409 * 734571 ", "answer": "413129341539", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7507", "question": "28 - -973 ", "answer": "1001", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7508", "question": "-34 - 59 ", "answer": "-93", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7509", "question": "-279910 * 825045 - 822612 ", "answer": "-230939168562", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7510", "question": "496843 * 122111 - 853781 * -545033 + 316856 ", "answer": "526009132202", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7511", "question": "-782096 + 951107 ", "answer": "169011", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7512", "question": "-382 + 508 + 439 - 366 + 96 ", "answer": "295", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7513", "question": "-21 * -16 - 32 ", "answer": "304", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7514", "question": "56236 * -3219 + 43146 + -18220 + 36266 ", "answer": "-180962492", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7515", "question": "-26760 - -46292 - 22003 ", "answer": "-2471", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7516", "question": "-3301 - 97 + -4348 ", "answer": "-7746", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7517", "question": "-922902 - -749904 + -362218 + 238934 ", "answer": "-296282", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7518", "question": "90 - -31 + -767 ", "answer": "-646", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7519", "question": "-543935 - 598646 - -358811 + 23628 ", "answer": "-760142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7520", "question": "-975 * 984 ", "answer": "-959400", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7521", "question": "754081 * -460037 ", "answer": "-346905160997", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7522", "question": "-17 - -75 ", "answer": "58", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7523", "question": "97062 * 32778 * -46848 - -96387 ", "answer": "-149046829263741", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7524", "question": "-472916 + 975024 + -273028 - 29895 ", "answer": "199185", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7525", "question": "-458 * 686 ", "answer": "-314188", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7526", "question": "40 * 13 + 55 ", "answer": "575", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7527", "question": "62 - -83 - -70 * 79 - -52 ", "answer": "5727", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7528", "question": "49158 + -78183 - 63801 ", "answer": "-92826", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7529", "question": "-658 * 305 ", "answer": "-200690", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7530", "question": "30 + 25 - 37 ", "answer": "18", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7531", "question": "-890 + 408 - -720 * 605 ", "answer": "435118", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7532", "question": "-84 - -83 ", "answer": "-1", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7533", "question": "3020 * 7293 * -1735 + 3063 + 2534 ", "answer": "-38213126503", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7534", "question": "-26 + 9 + 77 ", "answer": "60", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7535", "question": "68 * -29 - 19 * 50 + -52 ", "answer": "-2974", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7536", "question": "-4515 - 7651 ", "answer": "-12166", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7537", "question": "-53 + -88 * 56 - 59 ", "answer": "-5040", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7538", "question": "30220 * -60136 ", "answer": "-1817309920", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7539", "question": "-56110 - -44131 + 94086 - 35085 ", "answer": "47022", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7540", "question": "-4367 + 2952 ", "answer": "-1415", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7541", "question": "1261 + -9635 + -855 ", "answer": "-9229", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7542", "question": "4585 * 2814 * 944 ", "answer": "12179667360", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7543", "question": "-735525 + -834732 ", "answer": "-1570257", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7544", "question": "74 + -5 - -73 + 47 ", "answer": "189", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7545", "question": "-86 * -9 + 64 ", "answer": "838", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7546", "question": "210 * 918 ", "answer": "192780", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7547", "question": "-979785 + -284939 * 560464 ", "answer": "-159699031481", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7548", "question": "1429 - -5096 - 9761 - 6234 ", "answer": "-9470", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7549", "question": "99 - -76 * 85 * -63 + -80 ", "answer": "-406961", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7550", "question": "-3979 * -3201 * -874 + 9730 ", "answer": "-11131935116", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7551", "question": "395097 * -683877 + -799942 ", "answer": "-270198551011", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7552", "question": "51 - 371 * -467 + 696 ", "answer": "174004", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7553", "question": "33 * 63 - 5 * 75 ", "answer": "1704", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7554", "question": "-935874 + -141566 - 386735 ", "answer": "-1464175", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7555", "question": "5855 - 7774 - 8797 - -615 * 135 ", "answer": "72309", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7556", "question": "-410 + -872 ", "answer": "-1282", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7557", "question": "-12865 + -25054 * -29991 * -19016 - 45505 ", "answer": "-14288518136594", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7558", "question": "32 * -24 + -35 + -71 ", "answer": "-874", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7559", "question": "-2220 - -2917 ", "answer": "697", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7560", "question": "23307 + 94820 * -78390 - -24441 * -39282 ", "answer": "-8393007855", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7561", "question": "962 * -784 - -855 ", "answer": "-753353", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7562", "question": "-397870 - -101180 * -50047 * -191889 ", "answer": "971678971066070", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7563", "question": "-516 + 298 ", "answer": "-218", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7564", "question": "-994 + -212 - 283 * 436 * -588 ", "answer": "72550938", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7565", "question": "-6966 + 4996 * 1555 - -2234 * 4770 ", "answer": "18417994", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7566", "question": "-510 - -97 - 132 - 551 ", "answer": "-1096", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7567", "question": "1 + 44 + 32 ", "answer": "77", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7568", "question": "-687594 + -907293 ", "answer": "-1594887", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7569", "question": "-2627 + 1176 - -4879 + -1785 - -6421 ", "answer": "8064", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7570", "question": "-7816 * 9354 - -8520 * -9170 + -9014 ", "answer": "-151248278", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7571", "question": "895497 * -47193 ", "answer": "-42261189921", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7572", "question": "287426 * 54989 - 733642 * -686898 ", "answer": "519742490830", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7573", "question": "56 + -66 ", "answer": "-10", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7574", "question": "-166235 * -709592 ", "answer": "117959026120", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7575", "question": "-8493 * -72329 + -20540 * -23957 ", "answer": "1106366977", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7576", "question": "-33553 - -62143 * 41598 + -55972 ", "answer": "2584934989", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7577", "question": "-328189 - 129977 * 277204 + -881970 ", "answer": "-36031354467", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7578", "question": "34 + -48 - -98 + -47 - -35 ", "answer": "72", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7579", "question": "653 - 476 + 121 - -638 ", "answer": "936", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7580", "question": "-582 * 211 ", "answer": "-122802", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7581", "question": "158 * 287 ", "answer": "45346", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7582", "question": "229126 + -103904 * 892094 - 121999 - -247635 ", "answer": "-92691780214", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7583", "question": "-4415 * 1622 * 4873 ", "answer": "-34896186490", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7584", "question": "-933039 * 776372 * 533157 * -194709 ", "answer": "75198781441783296689004", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7585", "question": "-79440 - 80498 + 71021 - -89630 ", "answer": "713", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7586", "question": "33625 * -50900 + 25441 * 63025 ", "answer": "-108093475", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7587", "question": "-518 - -516 * -70 ", "answer": "-36638", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7588", "question": "-5174 - -7830 + 8860 ", "answer": "11516", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7589", "question": "-49409 * 99872 - -38832 + -68520 ", "answer": "-4934605336", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7590", "question": "-77507 * -53832 - -97976 ", "answer": "4172454800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7591", "question": "-56 * -98 - 57 - -77 + 34 ", "answer": "5542", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7592", "question": "-2241 * -4890 - -8869 ", "answer": "10967359", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7593", "question": "-736827 * -262673 * -547835 ", "answer": "-106030483244743785", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7594", "question": "-229164 + -782336 - -868002 ", "answer": "-143498", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7595", "question": "-18373 + -58736 - -19038 * -2853 ", "answer": "-54392523", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7596", "question": "-109 + 860 ", "answer": "751", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7597", "question": "-94101 - 943700 - 46298 + -363853 ", "answer": "-1447952", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7598", "question": "-89 + 53 + 699 ", "answer": "663", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7599", "question": "9268 * 6054 - -781 ", "answer": "56109253", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7600", "question": "2461 * -9636 * -2026 * 736 + 3646 ", "answer": "35361091370302", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7601", "question": "-35 - 26 + -16 + -98 ", "answer": "-175", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7602", "question": "873161 - 792791 ", "answer": "80370", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7603", "question": "-664477 + 73319 + 109553 ", "answer": "-481605", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7604", "question": "-83 * 4 ", "answer": "-332", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7605", "question": "293 + -148 * 61 * 32 - 905 ", "answer": "-289508", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7606", "question": "-579 + 433 + 723 * 931 ", "answer": "672967", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7607", "question": "-636 * -162 ", "answer": "103032", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7608", "question": "40902 - -7229 - -8857 ", "answer": "56988", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7609", "question": "68542 + 83884 - 6329 ", "answer": "146097", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7610", "question": "-358425 + 298813 - -418707 + -823954 ", "answer": "-464859", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7611", "question": "74241 - -88787 - 13181 ", "answer": "149847", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7612", "question": "969 - -159 ", "answer": "1128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7613", "question": "-940840 * -671862 * 48698 + -470353 + 222763 ", "answer": "30782718937160250", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7614", "question": "-780 - -3992 ", "answer": "3212", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7615", "question": "-2010 + 9672 ", "answer": "7662", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7616", "question": "-56 * 94 ", "answer": "-5264", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7617", "question": "-20 - -23 - -55 * 68 - 19 ", "answer": "3724", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7618", "question": "785197 + 345151 * 37872 ", "answer": "13072343869", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7619", "question": "174600 - 319808 ", "answer": "-145208", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7620", "question": "30 - 95 * -29 - -53 * -84 ", "answer": "-1667", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7621", "question": "-76661 + -35932 * -41344 * -87431 + 25169 ", "answer": "-129885098741540", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7622", "question": "-73538 * 71538 + 18394 * -56565 ", "answer": "-6301218054", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7623", "question": "-47 * -77 ", "answer": "3619", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7624", "question": "-542427 + 913867 * -430694 * 264020 + 130493 ", "answer": "-103917488837357894", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7625", "question": "-559 * 682 + -292 - 445 ", "answer": "-381975", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7626", "question": "456148 + 639112 + 601375 * -304917 ", "answer": "-183368365615", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7627", "question": "12401 - 906 ", "answer": "11495", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7628", "question": "364528 * -554315 + -333756 ", "answer": "-202063672076", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7629", "question": "-483103 + -604532 - 239785 + 512654 ", "answer": "-814766", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7630", "question": "-94 + 84 * -47 - -45 * -62 ", "answer": "-6832", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7631", "question": "434 + 546 + -58 + -880 - -293 ", "answer": "335", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7632", "question": "53 * 18 + -4 * 50 ", "answer": "754", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7633", "question": "-4833 * 3229 ", "answer": "-15605757", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7634", "question": "3499 * -9245 - 673 + -4974 * 7359 ", "answer": "-68952594", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7635", "question": "280537 * 601164 - 523930 * -673350 ", "answer": "521437010568", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7636", "question": "-96404 * -17815 * 9170 - 66590 * -49693 ", "answer": "15752208731070", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7637", "question": "56784 - -296908 + 337025 ", "answer": "690717", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7638", "question": "740865 + -348551 + 94271 ", "answer": "486585", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7639", "question": "44 * 12 * -32 * 29 + 37 ", "answer": "-489947", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7640", "question": "-525337 * -834807 - -528051 ", "answer": "438555533010", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7641", "question": "442 + 996 + 553 - -717 ", "answer": "2708", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7642", "question": "-90 - -3 + -2 - 74 ", "answer": "-163", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7643", "question": "398 - 651 + -981 ", "answer": "-1234", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7644", "question": "-597261 - 773750 * -24793 ", "answer": "19182986489", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7645", "question": "-738949 - 377775 + -103238 ", "answer": "-1219962", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7646", "question": "-348419 + -482925 * 228161 ", "answer": "-110184999344", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7647", "question": "83 + 10 - 55 - -89 - 67 ", "answer": "60", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7648", "question": "-95796 - 36705 + -86445 ", "answer": "-218946", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7649", "question": "-918373 * 688452 - -528105 - -8071 * 643704 ", "answer": "-627059865507", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7650", "question": "-756 + 199 * 189 * 832 ", "answer": "31291596", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7651", "question": "-814093 - 63512 * -854914 + -147824 - -263809 ", "answer": "54296599860", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7652", "question": "-28475 + -94688 * 60120 - -11910 - 51461 ", "answer": "-5692710586", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7653", "question": "2128 - 9969 ", "answer": "-7841", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7654", "question": "448 * 668 + -530 * 936 * 108 ", "answer": "-53277376", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7655", "question": "789 + 8137 ", "answer": "8926", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7656", "question": "-852 - -112 ", "answer": "-740", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7657", "question": "-89680 + 69735 ", "answer": "-19945", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7658", "question": "6647 + 67466 * -92155 + 81174 ", "answer": "-6217241409", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7659", "question": "-32068 + 76136 + 99028 + 53878 * 67538 ", "answer": "3638955460", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7660", "question": "618 + -6990 + -1341 ", "answer": "-7713", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7661", "question": "410867 - -739867 + 259295 + -570809 + -587933 ", "answer": "251287", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7662", "question": "371 + -841 - -875 * -389 - -379 ", "answer": "-340466", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7663", "question": "-24051 + -68197 + -420 * -15209 ", "answer": "6295532", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7664", "question": "-55 * 6 - 100 * -85 ", "answer": "8170", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7665", "question": "-75 + 82 ", "answer": "7", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7666", "question": "23695 - 41291 * 87543 * -33941 * 74099 ", "answer": "9091044989010289762", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7667", "question": "-94013 + -16049 - 96737 * 31141 ", "answer": "-3012596979", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7668", "question": "407 * 144 ", "answer": "58608", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7669", "question": "174 - 7521 ", "answer": "-7347", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7670", "question": "4484 + 7449 + -4222 ", "answer": "7711", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7671", "question": "89 + 18 * -62 - -13 - 97 ", "answer": "-1111", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7672", "question": "-747 + -481 ", "answer": "-1228", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7673", "question": "998 * 95 - 420 ", "answer": "94390", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7674", "question": "337151 - 491859 ", "answer": "-154708", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7675", "question": "-252402 - -583000 ", "answer": "330598", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7676", "question": "-86 * -10 + 68 * -43 ", "answer": "-2064", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7677", "question": "75 + 42 + -4 * 19 + 100 ", "answer": "141", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7678", "question": "27 - 94 ", "answer": "-67", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7679", "question": "-335936 - -572194 - 521909 ", "answer": "-285651", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7680", "question": "-33 - -87 ", "answer": "54", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7681", "question": "30842 - -46149 + -36551 ", "answer": "40440", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7682", "question": "-727560 * -524361 * 965033 + -160627 ", "answer": "368164035674181653", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7683", "question": "-98 * 3 + -8 + 73 ", "answer": "-229", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7684", "question": "-708032 * 777332 - 779181 * 275824 ", "answer": "-765292750768", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7685", "question": "-265 + -183 - 421 - -183 ", "answer": "-686", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7686", "question": "34167 + -60890 - 41724 ", "answer": "-68447", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7687", "question": "30270 * 55338 - -69303 - -42907 ", "answer": "1675193470", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7688", "question": "-116 - -20 ", "answer": "-96", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7689", "question": "79 - 861 + -756 - -928 ", "answer": "-610", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7690", "question": "55675 - -93173 - 96019 ", "answer": "52829", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7691", "question": "67 - 8 * 35 + -43 - -42 ", "answer": "-214", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7692", "question": "-543171 * -432951 ", "answer": "235166427621", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7693", "question": "61 + -67 ", "answer": "-6", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7694", "question": "8178 + 3433 + -7888 - 5747 ", "answer": "-2024", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7695", "question": "7518 * -8227 - 289 ", "answer": "-61850875", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7696", "question": "342 * 510 + -952 ", "answer": "173468", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7697", "question": "605489 * 910770 + -778613 * 177911 + 41361 ", "answer": "412937440448", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7698", "question": "-20 * 73 - -29 + -73 ", "answer": "-1504", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7699", "question": "-55895 * -74603 + 93119 * -40810 ", "answer": "369748295", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7700", "question": "593355 * 320346 * 965166 - 446103 ", "answer": "183457692398041677", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7701", "question": "-5098 + 7944 - -366 ", "answer": "3212", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7702", "question": "-2343 * 914 + -8394 + -2177 ", "answer": "-2152073", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7703", "question": "-437 * -186 + -586 ", "answer": "80696", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7704", "question": "-286 - -295 * -510 * -241 ", "answer": "36258164", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7705", "question": "-96 + -75 + 96 ", "answer": "-75", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7706", "question": "-311893 - 993080 * 692921 * 290547 ", "answer": "-199932941052225853", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7707", "question": "6836 + 5439 * 9990 ", "answer": "54342446", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7708", "question": "-839 + -122 * -297 ", "answer": "35395", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7709", "question": "59 * 8 - -36 + -38 * 54 ", "answer": "-1544", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7710", "question": "770155 + 436131 * -268949 - -557291 ", "answer": "-117295668873", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7711", "question": "104 + 965 - 173 + -312 - 103 ", "answer": "481", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7712", "question": "-5026 + 93106 * -51756 ", "answer": "-4818799162", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7713", "question": "-52 - 37 + 44 ", "answer": "-45", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7714", "question": "717 * 880 - 476 - -845 ", "answer": "631329", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7715", "question": "-21 * 90 ", "answer": "-1890", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7716", "question": "-2621 - 3446 + 4478 ", "answer": "-1589", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7717", "question": "2967 + 9015 - -9158 - 1544 ", "answer": "19596", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7718", "question": "-94994 - -29208 + -73229 ", "answer": "-139015", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7719", "question": "-81077 - 14591 * 48330 * -17324 + 92252 ", "answer": "12216590822895", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7720", "question": "-30 + 15 + 57 + 100 ", "answer": "142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7721", "question": "211 + 982 ", "answer": "1193", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7722", "question": "-5698 * 81715 + 3604 - -73621 ", "answer": "-465534845", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7723", "question": "33 * 97 + -27 ", "answer": "3174", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7724", "question": "37 * -76 + 85 - -56 ", "answer": "-2671", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7725", "question": "756515 + -387060 * -806247 ", "answer": "312066720335", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7726", "question": "-5470 - -8903 + -1973 ", "answer": "1460", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7727", "question": "-35532 + -61291 - 88790 * 49962 ", "answer": "-4436222803", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7728", "question": "-287 - 85 - 318 ", "answer": "-690", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7729", "question": "530593 * -612803 + -779918 + -779838 + -136185 ", "answer": "-325150678120", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7730", "question": "-190573 - -629006 * -114685 * 123362 ", "answer": "-8899032826946393", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7731", "question": "97625 * 24790 + 52102 - 44521 + -90177 ", "answer": "2420041154", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7732", "question": "81666 + -40177 ", "answer": "41489", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7733", "question": "-726 + 74 + -544 ", "answer": "-1196", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7734", "question": "-77780 * -13260 + 12636 ", "answer": "1031375436", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7735", "question": "743613 - -408249 + -180884 + -864159 ", "answer": "106819", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7736", "question": "-586351 + -289028 - 288466 ", "answer": "-1163845", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7737", "question": "811477 + 506730 - 487151 ", "answer": "831056", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7738", "question": "5826 + 7915 * -9033 ", "answer": "-71490369", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7739", "question": "-481 - 74 * 787 + 915 - -636 ", "answer": "-57168", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7740", "question": "-267 + -730 + -434 - 209 ", "answer": "-1640", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7741", "question": "57707 * 70273 + 8946 + -42543 - 82603 ", "answer": "4055127811", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7742", "question": "-37 - 13 - 43 + -94 - -53 ", "answer": "-134", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7743", "question": "-291762 - -166446 - 389109 ", "answer": "-514425", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7744", "question": "-88823 - -15776 * 62807 * 80385 - -55460 ", "answer": "79648933170957", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7745", "question": "944023 - 441502 * 517986 - -424753 + -340170 ", "answer": "-228690826366", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7746", "question": "-84712 - 57064 ", "answer": "-141776", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7747", "question": "53 + 45 * 19 ", "answer": "908", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7748", "question": "-14750 - -56585 ", "answer": "41835", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7749", "question": "97794 + -79690 * 51197 - -74355 + -85139 ", "answer": "-4079801920", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7750", "question": "-45 * 12 ", "answer": "-540", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7751", "question": "251820 - -109384 * -141860 + -19257 - -960166 ", "answer": "-15516021511", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7752", "question": "-842 + -321 - -925 * -533 + 978 ", "answer": "-493210", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7753", "question": "-1 - 42 - 50 * 74 ", "answer": "-3743", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7754", "question": "-12 + 2 * 43 ", "answer": "74", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7755", "question": "22168 * 45380 + -45031 * -34683 ", "answer": "2567794013", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7756", "question": "76022 - -58589 - -7227 ", "answer": "141838", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7757", "question": "-89 - -9 + -81 + 50 + -81 ", "answer": "-192", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7758", "question": "-43 + -40 - -68 - -75 + 79 ", "answer": "139", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7759", "question": "-92 * 59 * -26 * 94 ", "answer": "13266032", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7760", "question": "-789658 + 560803 ", "answer": "-228855", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7761", "question": "-9009 + 7585 * 1201 - 8897 * 7707 ", "answer": "-59468603", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7762", "question": "42817 - 22244 + -33381 + -99346 * -32646 ", "answer": "3243236708", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7763", "question": "-77399 - 42246 + -91618 * -59287 ", "answer": "5431636721", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7764", "question": "77 + -18 ", "answer": "59", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7765", "question": "2931 - 8113 * -32 ", "answer": "262547", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7766", "question": "-901 + -970 * 591 ", "answer": "-574171", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7767", "question": "-858719 * -23732 - 408067 + -431855 + -895244 ", "answer": "20377384142", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7768", "question": "-768214 - -115701 ", "answer": "-652513", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7769", "question": "66082 * -38831 + -36397 - -31548 * 24327 ", "answer": "-1798598343", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7770", "question": "-20045 - -97522 + 70238 - 85102 ", "answer": "62613", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7771", "question": "-6615 + 5832 * 4971 ", "answer": "28984257", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7772", "question": "931108 + 633233 + 726341 ", "answer": "2290682", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7773", "question": "99861 - -40237 ", "answer": "140098", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7774", "question": "-15 + 75 * 88 * -40 ", "answer": "-264015", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7775", "question": "43938 - 44654 - 7403 - 70107 ", "answer": "-78226", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7776", "question": "41098 * -4695 ", "answer": "-192955110", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7777", "question": "-7 - 19 ", "answer": "-26", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7778", "question": "410 * 530 + -601 * -213 + -599 ", "answer": "344714", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7779", "question": "777 * -992 ", "answer": "-770784", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7780", "question": "-886956 * 782311 ", "answer": "-693875435316", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7781", "question": "-54358 * -8238 - 17509 ", "answer": "447783695", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7782", "question": "-4234 - -3425 - -1075 ", "answer": "266", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7783", "question": "-54110 * -73773 - 1518 + 45055 ", "answer": "3991900567", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7784", "question": "-699 - -818 * -228 * 185 - 640 ", "answer": "-34504579", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7785", "question": "62 + -40 - 54 - 15 * 44 ", "answer": "-692", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7786", "question": "-58 + 976 - -152 * 123 - -412 ", "answer": "20026", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7787", "question": "-1316 - -5917 + -297 * 1931 ", "answer": "-568906", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7788", "question": "-5378 - 4482 + -3920 ", "answer": "-13780", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7789", "question": "-54107 * -54385 - -64005 ", "answer": "2942673200", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7790", "question": "56 - -4 * 19 ", "answer": "132", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7791", "question": "341 * 360 * 201 - -247 ", "answer": "24675007", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7792", "question": "874138 + -589362 * -393332 - 243984 + -740161 ", "answer": "231814824177", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7793", "question": "654819 * -439581 - 85648 * 953908 - 277671 ", "answer": "-369546580894", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7794", "question": "980854 - 408977 + -168686 - -310454 + -635658 ", "answer": "77987", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7795", "question": "52 + -26 ", "answer": "26", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7796", "question": "-55788 * -92351 + -66892 * 26366 - 91976 ", "answer": "3388311140", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7797", "question": "4756 + -80220 ", "answer": "-75464", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7798", "question": "-51233 * -88137 * 99767 ", "answer": "450500175259407", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7799", "question": "91553 + -65718 - -14066 * 76232 - 15682 ", "answer": "1072289465", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7800", "question": "13085 * 31846 + -10758 - -51814 ", "answer": "416745966", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7801", "question": "-578922 - 927120 + 456277 + 803389 ", "answer": "-246376", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7802", "question": "-3244 * -801 * 3827 + -8522 * -1266 ", "answer": "9955034040", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7803", "question": "-65409 - 74755 ", "answer": "-140164", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7804", "question": "878442 + -171957 * 506065 ", "answer": "-87020540763", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7805", "question": "-2081 + -4857 * 5541 ", "answer": "-26914718", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7806", "question": "-493 * 786 ", "answer": "-387498", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7807", "question": "89271 + 92607 - 62252 + 32355 * 82066 ", "answer": "2655365056", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7808", "question": "-612 * 35 - -755 + 716 ", "answer": "-19949", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7809", "question": "9289 - 7358 + 414 ", "answer": "2345", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7810", "question": "-715 + 574 + 213 ", "answer": "72", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7811", "question": "-347957 * -959871 * 607097 - -473541 ", "answer": "202766654365356600", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7812", "question": "72025 - -11867 * 821 ", "answer": "9814832", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7813", "question": "-76667 * -11350 - 25604 ", "answer": "870144846", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7814", "question": "-87672 - -97723 ", "answer": "10051", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7815", "question": "-3383 + 9269 + -6925 ", "answer": "-1039", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7816", "question": "-215471 - -884687 - -458658 * 133756 - 752650 ", "answer": "61348176014", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7817", "question": "-5087 + 9947 - 2452 - 804 + 1467 ", "answer": "3071", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7818", "question": "55 * 71 - -87 * 16 ", "answer": "5297", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7819", "question": "-524 + -39 + -380 + -38 * -738 ", "answer": "27101", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7820", "question": "-568 - -834 - 580 * 487 - 721 ", "answer": "-282915", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7821", "question": "632086 * 111720 + -778535 * -208810 ", "answer": "233182541270", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7822", "question": "4755 + -1040 + 1494 + 8744 ", "answer": "13953", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7823", "question": "52599 + 1264 + 56094 * 87673 ", "answer": "4917983125", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7824", "question": "-53 + 82 ", "answer": "29", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7825", "question": "-94 - 4 * -27 + -17 + -83 ", "answer": "-86", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7826", "question": "-601 + 305 ", "answer": "-296", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7827", "question": "100 + -82 - 87 - -36 + 10 ", "answer": "-23", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7828", "question": "-4392 + -1957 + 6444 + 8173 - 9739 ", "answer": "-1471", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7829", "question": "94 - -93 ", "answer": "187", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7830", "question": "-50 * 50 - 43 ", "answer": "-2543", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7831", "question": "-5590 - -7005 - 4022 - -6354 ", "answer": "3747", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7832", "question": "8868 * 3206 * 6021 + -6879 + 4157 ", "answer": "171181892246", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7833", "question": "-400098 - 618404 + 248926 ", "answer": "-769576", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7834", "question": "-897405 - 951234 ", "answer": "-1848639", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7835", "question": "-144 + 301 + -775 * -250 * -710 ", "answer": "-137562343", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7836", "question": "4414 - -7742 - -9357 ", "answer": "21513", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7837", "question": "-90 + 73 * 14 - 96 + -89 ", "answer": "747", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7838", "question": "8341 - 15683 * -81723 ", "answer": "1281670150", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7839", "question": "80 + -67 * -24 + -75 - -37 ", "answer": "1650", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7840", "question": "71381 + 14250 * -63117 + 57100 ", "answer": "-899288769", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7841", "question": "-38 - -67 * 11 - 73 ", "answer": "626", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7842", "question": "-510 * 679 ", "answer": "-346290", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7843", "question": "90 * 35 ", "answer": "3150", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7844", "question": "61 - -99 + -15 - 84 - -97 ", "answer": "158", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7845", "question": "327113 - 667232 + -753800 ", "answer": "-1093919", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7846", "question": "-908 - 8758 + 9699 ", "answer": "33", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7847", "question": "-216 - 824 * 465 ", "answer": "-383376", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7848", "question": "-94 + -85 - 93 ", "answer": "-272", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7849", "question": "-822747 - -864874 * 831246 ", "answer": "718922230257", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7850", "question": "-6838 * -1213 + -1987 + -3671 ", "answer": "8288836", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7851", "question": "6892 + -4048 ", "answer": "2844", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7852", "question": "5958 - -3067 * 6887 * 9252 ", "answer": "195424719066", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7853", "question": "918 - -58788 + 54424 ", "answer": "114130", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7854", "question": "7111 + 4903 + -4871 + -1722 ", "answer": "5421", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7855", "question": "-4416 - 6563 * -1804 * 1487 ", "answer": "17605558108", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7856", "question": "25120 + -45046 + -35289 + 85908 ", "answer": "30693", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7857", "question": "-3567 * 4938 - 4019 * -6511 + 1734 ", "answer": "8555597", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7858", "question": "27356 - -80958 + -47459 * -41481 ", "answer": "1968755093", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7859", "question": "62 + -65 ", "answer": "-3", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7860", "question": "19077 + -74338 - 25832 ", "answer": "-81093", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7861", "question": "67179 + 465604 * -126185 + 241383 ", "answer": "-58751932178", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7862", "question": "8778 * 6708 * 5807 + -503 * 6723 ", "answer": "341929177299", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7863", "question": "8996 + -3951 ", "answer": "5045", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7864", "question": "6876 - -602 ", "answer": "7478", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7865", "question": "-425581 * 643150 ", "answer": "-273712420150", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7866", "question": "6711 + -8449 * -99657 * 80784 ", "answer": "68020289009223", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7867", "question": "44 + 670 + 115 - -921 ", "answer": "1750", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7868", "question": "-702 + -3898 - -3053 * 8046 * 1443 ", "answer": "35446479434", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7869", "question": "-5381 + -6422 - 1781 * -2705 ", "answer": "4805802", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7870", "question": "612204 - -860600 + 489756 + 618804 ", "answer": "2581364", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7871", "question": "-903 - -737 - -3174 * -7914 ", "answer": "-25119202", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7872", "question": "79358 - 89247 + -94351 + 49764 * -37227 ", "answer": "-1852668668", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7873", "question": "9455 + -5439 + -4524 ", "answer": "-508", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7874", "question": "-57 + 90 * -96 - -48 + 0 ", "answer": "-8649", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7875", "question": "12196 - -66494 - 48867 * 93824 ", "answer": "-4584818718", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7876", "question": "85 + 82 - -57 ", "answer": "224", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7877", "question": "-9053 + -6147 ", "answer": "-15200", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7878", "question": "34 * -25 - -88 * 15 ", "answer": "470", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7879", "question": "8647 + -6061 + 1808 * -9583 ", "answer": "-17323478", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7880", "question": "-67383 + -71172 * 73714 - -717 * -42329 ", "answer": "-5276790084", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7881", "question": "11418 + 99337 * -69606 ", "answer": "-6914439804", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7882", "question": "-17787 * 90930 ", "answer": "-1617371910", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7883", "question": "39 * -78 + 22 ", "answer": "-3020", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7884", "question": "604 - 210 * -424 + -660 * 956 ", "answer": "-541316", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7885", "question": "7870 * -5258 * 3475 - 8141 + 3738 ", "answer": "-143797102903", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7886", "question": "14 - -12 - -59 ", "answer": "85", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7887", "question": "619 * -572 + 8 ", "answer": "-354060", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7888", "question": "-64 - 39 ", "answer": "-103", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7889", "question": "894 * -266 - 18 * 52 ", "answer": "-238740", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7890", "question": "-8463 * -4403 - 803 * 9001 * 7603 ", "answer": "-54915723620", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7891", "question": "-58880 - -510728 * -169569 * -407443 - 190101 ", "answer": "35286045357025795", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7892", "question": "-108496 - 131157 ", "answer": "-239653", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7893", "question": "801477 - 549558 - 197603 ", "answer": "54316", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7894", "question": "-20 + 86 - -56 ", "answer": "122", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7895", "question": "-5241 + 9395 + 6129 * 6244 * -5882 ", "answer": "-225101053678", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7896", "question": "9247 - 8135 - 8090 + 1171 ", "answer": "-5807", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7897", "question": "152913 + 416529 + 228998 * -158629 + -600612 ", "answer": "-36325754912", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7898", "question": "-9331 * -4677 - 8320 * 2852 * -1029 ", "answer": "24460411647", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7899", "question": "5534 - -373 - 4458 ", "answer": "1449", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7900", "question": "189039 - -377476 * -225208 - 578585 - -414134 ", "answer": "-85010590420", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7901", "question": "805 + 395 * 598 * 931 + -56 ", "answer": "219912259", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7902", "question": "-9444 + -8442 * 7125 ", "answer": "-60158694", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7903", "question": "66 - 25 ", "answer": "41", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7904", "question": "-442 - 567 + 49 ", "answer": "-960", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7905", "question": "22600 - 25693 * 72120 ", "answer": "-1852956560", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7906", "question": "-384 + -43 * 235 + 756 - -548 ", "answer": "-9185", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7907", "question": "67722 + 24344 ", "answer": "92066", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7908", "question": "-965 * 518 ", "answer": "-499870", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7909", "question": "-404756 - -660681 + -860053 ", "answer": "-604128", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7910", "question": "54 + 922 ", "answer": "976", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7911", "question": "-1131 + -6426 * 9705 + -5171 + 2850 ", "answer": "-62367782", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7912", "question": "997868 - 778416 ", "answer": "219452", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7913", "question": "85101 * -74554 ", "answer": "-6344619954", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7914", "question": "576 + -885 + -760 * 481 + 158 ", "answer": "-365711", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7915", "question": "-599 * -141 - 231 * -10 ", "answer": "86769", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7916", "question": "2338 * 6896 + 8337 + -9532 - -1979 ", "answer": "16123632", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7917", "question": "30 - 19 * -98 * 80 - 67 ", "answer": "148923", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7918", "question": "-1101 * -8422 + -2455 + -5334 ", "answer": "9264833", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7919", "question": "-6106 + 4541 ", "answer": "-1565", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7920", "question": "84 + 17 - -60 - -43 + -26 ", "answer": "178", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7921", "question": "49 * 4 ", "answer": "196", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7922", "question": "4326 - -9917 - -1450 * -2003 ", "answer": "-2890107", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7923", "question": "-7359 * 8261 + -4314 + 8662 ", "answer": "-60788351", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7924", "question": "8852 * 7957 - 3734 * -5608 ", "answer": "91375636", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7925", "question": "-525 * -551 - -748 + -275 ", "answer": "289748", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7926", "question": "-36208 * 84326 - -15048 * 20869 - 68460 ", "answer": "-2739307556", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7927", "question": "618343 + -134518 - 578333 * -983283 ", "answer": "568665491064", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7928", "question": "-9299 + -2557 ", "answer": "-11856", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7929", "question": "-207 * -474 - -838 + 283 * -984 ", "answer": "-179516", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7930", "question": "-760 * 322 + 496 - -503 ", "answer": "-243721", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7931", "question": "-2126 + -411 ", "answer": "-2537", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7932", "question": "-21 + 19 + -91 - 81 ", "answer": "-174", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7933", "question": "846 + 936 - -151 - 224 * -782 ", "answer": "177101", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7934", "question": "-69424 + 15032 + 21564 * 44732 ", "answer": "964546456", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7935", "question": "-26654 * 54009 * 83300 * 8052 ", "answer": "-965555622706197600", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7936", "question": "-993289 - -444577 * 981953 + -39537 ", "answer": "436552686055", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7937", "question": "-280869 + 461302 ", "answer": "180433", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7938", "question": "-8161 - -4644 * -1882 - 8683 * 6599 ", "answer": "-66047286", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7939", "question": "-12161 + -3197 - 1334 * -18644 * -25709 ", "answer": "-639411022422", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7940", "question": "-528 + -3335 + 4537 ", "answer": "674", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7941", "question": "211846 * -572112 * 433714 - 732032 ", "answer": "-52565980122416960", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7942", "question": "8449 * -7418 * 5671 - 8353 + -5458 ", "answer": "-355428135433", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7943", "question": "-7878 - 9014 + -2299 - -9899 - 6704 ", "answer": "-15996", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7944", "question": "55397 * 22034 - 20494 ", "answer": "1220597004", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7945", "question": "-72987 * 75737 ", "answer": "-5527816419", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7946", "question": "9635 * -8584 ", "answer": "-82706840", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7947", "question": "-768 * -842 * -285 * -74 + -221 ", "answer": "13637974819", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7948", "question": "48003 + 186179 * 56494 ", "answer": "10518044429", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7949", "question": "362518 * 331220 * 777293 - -349227 - -534436 ", "answer": "93332067144907943", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7950", "question": "76310 * -81808 + 53777 - 55918 ", "answer": "-6242770621", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7951", "question": "534594 + -681313 * -271516 + 363479 ", "answer": "184988278581", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7952", "question": "112539 - 756822 * 26727 ", "answer": "-20227469055", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7953", "question": "582197 * -352080 ", "answer": "-204979919760", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7954", "question": "6663 + -4581 - 3829 - 8263 * -1563 ", "answer": "12913322", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7955", "question": "-594 + -555 + 855 - -289 ", "answer": "-5", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7956", "question": "100 - 23 ", "answer": "77", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7957", "question": "-305 * 374 * 830 - -342 ", "answer": "-94677758", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7958", "question": "-323659 - -755246 * -823810 - 999145 ", "answer": "-622180530064", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7959", "question": "42787 * 34556 - -62451 ", "answer": "1478610023", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7960", "question": "-6217 - -90 + -7374 + -5433 ", "answer": "-18934", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7961", "question": "747 + -96 * -195 * -854 * -696 ", "answer": "11126869227", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7962", "question": "828 * -342 + 61 - -575 ", "answer": "-282540", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7963", "question": "110703 - -705406 * 286689 + 476035 - -702916 ", "answer": "202233430388", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7964", "question": "-5861 - 25221 ", "answer": "-31082", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7965", "question": "8769 + 3598 ", "answer": "12367", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7966", "question": "4821 - 5393 * -3341 + 7893 ", "answer": "18030727", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7967", "question": "-607 * -4651 + -1724 + -5143 ", "answer": "2816290", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7968", "question": "43 + 97 + 49 * -8 + 85 ", "answer": "-167", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7969", "question": "348 * 226 ", "answer": "78648", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7970", "question": "-48 * 83 * 50 * 93 + 25 ", "answer": "-18525575", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7971", "question": "4881 * -2036 ", "answer": "-9937716", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7972", "question": "97 - -99 - 46 * -65 ", "answer": "3186", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7973", "question": "-4774 + 4121 - -8685 - -6314 - 7176 ", "answer": "7170", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7974", "question": "-19 + -49 - 3 + 12 ", "answer": "-59", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7975", "question": "-5892 + 2400 - 3216 ", "answer": "-6708", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7976", "question": "-81 + 15 ", "answer": "-66", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7977", "question": "-5733 * -429981 - 987528 ", "answer": "2464093545", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7978", "question": "-630 * -327 * 894 + -915 ", "answer": "184172025", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7979", "question": "497 * -232 + -251 * 588 ", "answer": "-262892", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7980", "question": "-688 - 254 + -634 - 310 * -432 ", "answer": "132344", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7981", "question": "-785 * 389 + -266 * -873 ", "answer": "-73147", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7982", "question": "-36 * 92 + 11 + -33 - -44 ", "answer": "-3290", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7983", "question": "-12 + -63 - 25 ", "answer": "-100", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7984", "question": "596275 * -544493 ", "answer": "-324667563575", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7985", "question": "675439 + -209717 + -276623 ", "answer": "189099", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7986", "question": "250120 * -901078 * 138696 ", "answer": "-31258975681714560", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7987", "question": "-67430 - -19661 ", "answer": "-47769", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7988", "question": "795608 + -740543 + -105078 * -315203 ", "answer": "33120955899", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7989", "question": "47 + -25 * -8 + -1 ", "answer": "246", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7990", "question": "2703 + -9156 ", "answer": "-6453", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7991", "question": "1348 * -6869 * 8786 * -6701 ", "answer": "545147751868232", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7992", "question": "-23353 + -36127 * 96280 * 88107 - 77295 ", "answer": "-306463244289568", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "7993", "question": "-78 * 18 - 84 * -92 ", "answer": "6324", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "7994", "question": "809 * 252 - -917 + -228 - -723 ", "answer": "205280", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "7995", "question": "-785166 - -355266 + 494087 ", "answer": "64187", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7996", "question": "-79274 * 688262 + -964355 - 443235 ", "answer": "-54562689378", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7997", "question": "-1259 - 492 ", "answer": "-1751", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "7998", "question": "-913137 + -739233 + -127670 - 322500 ", "answer": "-2102540", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "7999", "question": "-704700 * -416443 + -432630 ", "answer": "293466949470", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8000", "question": "-2380 - 2045 - -9458 ", "answer": "5033", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8001", "question": "405129 - 618969 * -91609 + -205 + -597491 ", "answer": "56702938554", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8002", "question": "9784 + -9437 ", "answer": "347", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8003", "question": "74780 + -3061 * -8547 * -24194 ", "answer": "-632972232418", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8004", "question": "965539 + -960836 * 434345 + 217079 - 464476 ", "answer": "-417333594278", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8005", "question": "-530 + 826 - 943 ", "answer": "-647", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8006", "question": "15 - 96 ", "answer": "-81", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8007", "question": "667 - 98 + 529 ", "answer": "1098", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8008", "question": "-792 * -222 ", "answer": "175824", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8009", "question": "37655 - 62178 * 66673 + 27486 ", "answer": "-4145528653", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8010", "question": "-607202 - 612394 * 763081 + -675503 * -497283 ", "answer": "-131390674767", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8011", "question": "49 + -81 * -43 ", "answer": "3532", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8012", "question": "-99219 - 918550 * -374549 - 154182 ", "answer": "344041730549", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8013", "question": "5545 - 8193 + 7530 * 4301 ", "answer": "32383882", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8014", "question": "-776 - -829 * 119 - -150 ", "answer": "98025", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8015", "question": "66115 * -90808 - 22905 + 50635 ", "answer": "-6003743190", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8016", "question": "915 + 559 - 887 - 994 ", "answer": "-407", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8017", "question": "-485 - -646 * -636 * -753 ", "answer": "309374083", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8018", "question": "87 - 38 + -29 - 99 * 32 ", "answer": "-3148", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8019", "question": "-234748 * -514345 + 274109 * 49643 - 999129 ", "answer": "134348054018", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8020", "question": "-36298 - -91450 ", "answer": "55152", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8021", "question": "4357 - 9561 - -8515 * -1604 ", "answer": "-13663264", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8022", "question": "-284 * -247 ", "answer": "70148", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8023", "question": "-5005 - 3830 + -2160 ", "answer": "-10995", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8024", "question": "-8059 * 3535 + 4443 ", "answer": "-28484122", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8025", "question": "-113 + -495 ", "answer": "-608", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8026", "question": "-624 - -367 + 205 - -829 * 44 ", "answer": "36424", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8027", "question": "861180 * 919437 + 480164 ", "answer": "791801235824", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8028", "question": "-387 * 3527 ", "answer": "-1364949", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8029", "question": "33 * -84 ", "answer": "-2772", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8030", "question": "-982 + 58 - 68 - -616 ", "answer": "-376", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8031", "question": "-923624 + -571384 + -520149 + 122109 ", "answer": "-1893048", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8032", "question": "28 - 89 ", "answer": "-61", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8033", "question": "875375 + -224691 + -754164 + 826559 * -555284 ", "answer": "-458975091236", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8034", "question": "65 * 68 + -40 ", "answer": "4380", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8035", "question": "-463754 * -408701 + -601679 * -398459 * 937331 ", "answer": "224720059600671345", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8036", "question": "5833 + -3094 ", "answer": "2739", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8037", "question": "938 * -744 ", "answer": "-697872", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8038", "question": "8725 + -2261 ", "answer": "6464", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8039", "question": "46907 * -78832 ", "answer": "-3697772624", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8040", "question": "-96 * 9 - -33 ", "answer": "-831", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8041", "question": "-167276 * 612956 - 688950 + 164857 - -109211 ", "answer": "-102533242738", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8042", "question": "-579 - -978 + -854 ", "answer": "-455", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8043", "question": "-7119 + 3960 ", "answer": "-3159", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8044", "question": "-474258 - -620702 - 52692 ", "answer": "93752", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8045", "question": "64448 * 39288 ", "answer": "2532033024", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8046", "question": "885020 + -116415 + -888265 - -36731 - 6294 ", "answer": "-89223", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8047", "question": "-76 * 54 ", "answer": "-4104", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8048", "question": "72991 - -26673 * 47802 * 77712 ", "answer": "99084567710143", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8049", "question": "-458 - -512 * -126 - 228 * 826 ", "answer": "-253298", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8050", "question": "-85990 - -23162 * 80469 - -76839 - -25305 ", "answer": "1863839132", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8051", "question": "3483 - -3909 * 8490 * -506 * -2749 ", "answer": "46163488189023", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8052", "question": "69734 * 81312 - -65756 + -11618 ", "answer": "5670265146", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8053", "question": "-557737 - -948589 + -327902 ", "answer": "62950", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8054", "question": "37 - 73 * -21 ", "answer": "1570", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8055", "question": "-902555 * -324399 + 639587 ", "answer": "292788579032", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8056", "question": "-62242 * -58239 ", "answer": "3624911838", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8057", "question": "704607 * 639823 + -849801 - 987753 ", "answer": "450821927007", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8058", "question": "8294 * -326 * -917 ", "answer": "2479424948", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8059", "question": "-17 - -76 ", "answer": "59", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8060", "question": "59 + -234 ", "answer": "-175", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8061", "question": "-44 + 48 + -10 + 18 - 95 ", "answer": "-83", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8062", "question": "27 + -84 - -7 ", "answer": "-50", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8063", "question": "89126 + -73915 ", "answer": "15211", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8064", "question": "18366 - -52854 * -87575 ", "answer": "-4628670684", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8065", "question": "957854 - 509029 + 764588 * 934880 * -13795 ", "answer": "-9860638815675975", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8066", "question": "590218 * 307725 ", "answer": "181624834050", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8067", "question": "-601095 - -60227 * -895487 * 29697 + 560737 ", "answer": "-1601633320359011", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8068", "question": "290 * 219 * -272 + 59 ", "answer": "-17274661", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8069", "question": "1768 + -2497 ", "answer": "-729", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8070", "question": "-15 * -75 ", "answer": "1125", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8071", "question": "58633 - -56415 * 35395 - 89619 * -79455 ", "answer": "9117545203", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8072", "question": "-88671 * 74491 - 60427 * -91013 ", "answer": "-1105548910", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8073", "question": "-7223 + -9505 + -3279 * 6297 + 7701 ", "answer": "-20656890", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8074", "question": "-367955 + 112087 + -901178 + 485994 + 207782 ", "answer": "-463270", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8075", "question": "39511 + 36952 - -44945 * -87894 - 17506 ", "answer": "-3950336873", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8076", "question": "-130 + -3712 * -4161 + -8925 ", "answer": "15436577", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8077", "question": "-86437 - 90544 ", "answer": "-176981", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8078", "question": "-47844 - -39332 * 2279 ", "answer": "89589784", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8079", "question": "12534 + -320160 ", "answer": "-307626", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8080", "question": "1140 * -4840 - -8747 + 3338 - -4881 ", "answer": "-5500634", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8081", "question": "-754626 - -999482 - 878212 * 730320 - 408410 ", "answer": "-641375951394", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8082", "question": "70 + 9 * -4 - 28 * -95 ", "answer": "2694", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8083", "question": "27 - 88 * 85 ", "answer": "-7453", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8084", "question": "2124 - -3358 + -8589 + 5520 ", "answer": "2413", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8085", "question": "906 - 978 + -88 - 453 - 634 ", "answer": "-1247", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8086", "question": "23513 + -52698 - 89055 ", "answer": "-118240", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8087", "question": "-892 + -649 + -40 - 150 - 671 ", "answer": "-2402", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8088", "question": "8979 * -3578 - -316 ", "answer": "-32126546", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8089", "question": "26 - -73 - 78 + -91 + 14 ", "answer": "-56", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8090", "question": "250201 * 967345 * -950698 + -765802 * 506406 ", "answer": "-230098477253546422", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8091", "question": "52 - -4 ", "answer": "56", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8092", "question": "-2331 - -5197 ", "answer": "2866", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8093", "question": "64581 + -64616 - -82689 + 80211 - 92221 ", "answer": "70644", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8094", "question": "25859 * 2353 + 99083 * 77361 - 16547 ", "answer": "7725989643", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8095", "question": "-54 + -26 + 56 - -31 * 13 ", "answer": "379", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8096", "question": "162 * -35 + 261 ", "answer": "-5409", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8097", "question": "-6509 * 2032 ", "answer": "-13226288", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8098", "question": "758139 - 26125 ", "answer": "732014", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8099", "question": "38121 - 86006 + -80120 ", "answer": "-128005", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8100", "question": "9020 - -8 * -99835 ", "answer": "-789660", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8101", "question": "-638 - -329 + -554 ", "answer": "-863", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8102", "question": "-754 - 880 - -3422 ", "answer": "1788", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8103", "question": "-9901 + -7686 * 2641 ", "answer": "-20308627", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8104", "question": "43745 - 2998 - 43120 + 72837 ", "answer": "70464", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8105", "question": "195094 + -768193 * 612625 ", "answer": "-470614041531", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8106", "question": "-9745 * -5166 - -4556 + 3769 * 8162 ", "answer": "81109804", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8107", "question": "-639 - -204 ", "answer": "-435", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8108", "question": "-8103 + 7559 * -921 ", "answer": "-6969942", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8109", "question": "9364 + -3276 ", "answer": "6088", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8110", "question": "27 + -9 * 23 * 13 ", "answer": "-2664", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8111", "question": "11 + -99 * 26 - 18 ", "answer": "-2581", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8112", "question": "-119402 + 252117 + -129180 * 747267 - -250325 ", "answer": "-96531568020", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8113", "question": "-77 - 47 ", "answer": "-124", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8114", "question": "8616 + 41018 + 96760 * -55862 ", "answer": "-5405157486", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8115", "question": "-516611 - -120908 - -385046 - 2678 * 593556 ", "answer": "-1589553625", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8116", "question": "-8871 * 34724 - 31381 + -97571 ", "answer": "-308165556", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8117", "question": "-699791 + -877946 ", "answer": "-1577737", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8118", "question": "-52131 * -59821 * -49107 ", "answer": "-153141581553957", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8119", "question": "-9089 * -8628 + -261 * 3254 ", "answer": "77570598", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8120", "question": "68 * -58 - -5 - 34 ", "answer": "-3973", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8121", "question": "94 * -49 + -674 + 517 ", "answer": "-4763", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8122", "question": "54 * 60 - -10 ", "answer": "3250", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8123", "question": "12 + -62 * -66 + 44 * -8 ", "answer": "3752", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8124", "question": "-11 - 39 * 16 ", "answer": "-635", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8125", "question": "29 - 26 - 96 - 44 + 56 ", "answer": "-81", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8126", "question": "-5962 - 3330 ", "answer": "-9292", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8127", "question": "-9573 - -583 + 2575 ", "answer": "-6415", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8128", "question": "61360 - 39042 + 98029 + -12635 ", "answer": "107712", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8129", "question": "-58 + -33 ", "answer": "-91", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8130", "question": "-87238 + -9710 * 67665 ", "answer": "-657114388", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8131", "question": "18 + -79 - -63 * 52 * 19 ", "answer": "62183", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8132", "question": "-45832 - -22377 + -42645 - 88298 - -15908 ", "answer": "-138490", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8133", "question": "993 * 192 * -113 + -908 - -341 ", "answer": "-21544695", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8134", "question": "-198 * -1982 + 4961 + -6539 ", "answer": "390858", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8135", "question": "-2 - 57 * 68 + 88 + 63 ", "answer": "-3727", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8136", "question": "-159 + 651 - -460 ", "answer": "952", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8137", "question": "44043 - 81841 - 83709 - 55821 + -91216 ", "answer": "-268544", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8138", "question": "29 * 56 * -98 - 69 ", "answer": "-159221", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8139", "question": "377802 + 612908 * -66 * -852273 ", "answer": "34476086410146", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8140", "question": "-1674 * 2813 * -3789 ", "answer": "17842257018", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8141", "question": "37 * -10 * -8 * -5 + -75 ", "answer": "-14875", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8142", "question": "51 * -22 - 36 - 98 ", "answer": "-1256", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8143", "question": "-153832 * -735444 ", "answer": "113134821408", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8144", "question": "-399 * 431 ", "answer": "-171969", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8145", "question": "314596 - -682604 * 870651 ", "answer": "594310169800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8146", "question": "746237 + -454013 * -553212 - -563995 ", "answer": "251166749988", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8147", "question": "-482384 - -731395 - -908125 * -597044 + -314189 ", "answer": "-542190647678", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8148", "question": "-8669 + 1140 ", "answer": "-7529", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8149", "question": "61656 + -93250 + 21433 * -46905 ", "answer": "-1005346459", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8150", "question": "-339 - 681 ", "answer": "-1020", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8151", "question": "92093 - 28680 - -53823 + -12019 ", "answer": "105217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8152", "question": "52 + 14 - -23 ", "answer": "89", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8153", "question": "90 + -42 - -74 * -66 - 75 ", "answer": "-4911", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8154", "question": "139885 * 907316 - -505367 + -725441 ", "answer": "126919678586", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8155", "question": "587602 + -134939 + -578938 + 897149 ", "answer": "770874", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8156", "question": "-914 - 793 - -225 ", "answer": "-1482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8157", "question": "-867 * 945 * 883 - 849 ", "answer": "-723455994", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8158", "question": "-882451 + 334532 - -419759 * -893953 ", "answer": "-375245365246", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8159", "question": "226 * 1580 * -8205 - 6742 ", "answer": "-2929848142", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8160", "question": "-441003 - 435909 * 840839 ", "answer": "-366529728654", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8161", "question": "8620 + 1426 * -6283 + 806 - 2532 ", "answer": "-8952664", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8162", "question": "689 + 674 - -496 - 886 ", "answer": "973", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8163", "question": "890126 - -201151 - 189942 ", "answer": "901335", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8164", "question": "7518 - -6678 - -1226 * -5102 ", "answer": "-6240856", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8165", "question": "319783 - 486283 * -156222 * -277211 - 702944 ", "answer": "-21059193752881447", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8166", "question": "-32 - 74 - -88 - 72 - -24 ", "answer": "-66", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8167", "question": "9976 + -8995 + -8469 * 7341 ", "answer": "-62169948", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8168", "question": "-812710 - 253332 ", "answer": "-1066042", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8169", "question": "-9151 * -9742 - -1717 - 3676 + 8202 ", "answer": "89155285", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8170", "question": "-37 - 41 * 9 - 96 * -27 ", "answer": "2186", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8171", "question": "13 + -32 * 62 ", "answer": "-1971", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8172", "question": "4474 + -8139 * -7808 * 9518 - 5768 ", "answer": "604862350322", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8173", "question": "23667 + -16583 - -72133 + 25600 ", "answer": "104817", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8174", "question": "-751873 - -91743 - 473869 * -221745 * -810434 ", "answer": "-85158849826039900", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8175", "question": "836409 - 632471 ", "answer": "203938", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8176", "question": "-21289 * -78834 * 6075 * -3508 ", "answer": "-35766355750788600", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8177", "question": "-490 + 908 * 71 - -665 + -332 ", "answer": "64311", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8178", "question": "8 - 39 * 84 * 61 + -31 ", "answer": "-199859", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8179", "question": "441674 - -582386 - -232494 + -644728 * 108292 ", "answer": "-69817628022", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8180", "question": "-92362 - -61134 - 28632 ", "answer": "-59860", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8181", "question": "-31 + -63 - -50 ", "answer": "-44", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8182", "question": "-770 * 436 ", "answer": "-335720", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8183", "question": "13 + 41 ", "answer": "54", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8184", "question": "-4761 * 656 - 3055 * -542 - -889 ", "answer": "-1466517", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8185", "question": "486755 + 217285 ", "answer": "704040", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8186", "question": "47 * -911 * -137 ", "answer": "5865929", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8187", "question": "20 * 92 + -22 ", "answer": "1818", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8188", "question": "7629 * -27626 * -30159 * 66195 + -88843 ", "answer": "420753508570454927", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8189", "question": "-4001 - 3899 - -2002 * 4838 - -7225 ", "answer": "9685001", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8190", "question": "-752 + -690 * -959 ", "answer": "660958", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8191", "question": "12231 + 53610 - -93459 + 79808 ", "answer": "239108", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8192", "question": "-842 * 931 - 620 - 13 ", "answer": "-784535", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8193", "question": "558 * 811 ", "answer": "452538", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8194", "question": "-5218 - 1675 * -7850 ", "answer": "13143532", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8195", "question": "-61 + 52 + 61 ", "answer": "52", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8196", "question": "-273 + -481 - -611 - 250 ", "answer": "-393", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8197", "question": "71 - 50 - 17 ", "answer": "4", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8198", "question": "3368 * -7413 - -3754 * 7945 ", "answer": "4858546", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8199", "question": "64055 - 42376 ", "answer": "21679", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8200", "question": "520 - 609 - 30 + 128 ", "answer": "9", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8201", "question": "-19304 + -55485 * 26080 ", "answer": "-1447068104", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8202", "question": "-72 - 56 - 38 + -47 + -54 ", "answer": "-267", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8203", "question": "2 - -88 * -94 ", "answer": "-8270", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8204", "question": "-858294 - -222676 * -619946 ", "answer": "-138047953790", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8205", "question": "18 + -830 ", "answer": "-812", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8206", "question": "-72 + -799 - 320 * 355 ", "answer": "-114471", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8207", "question": "-7616 - -2433 ", "answer": "-5183", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8208", "question": "-8197 - 75093 * 15403 - 47783 * -86633 ", "answer": "2982918963", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8209", "question": "-63 * 47 ", "answer": "-2961", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8210", "question": "19 * 13 + -46 + 79 ", "answer": "280", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8211", "question": "-801585 * -184765 + 423170 ", "answer": "148105275695", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8212", "question": "-4596 * -4624 - -7446 - 7893 ", "answer": "21251457", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8213", "question": "787 - -764 * -837 + -155 ", "answer": "-638836", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8214", "question": "-695 - 966 ", "answer": "-1661", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8215", "question": "19 - -694 * -985 ", "answer": "-683571", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8216", "question": "-44 + 81 + 60 * -54 ", "answer": "-3203", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8217", "question": "-693 + -844 ", "answer": "-1537", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8218", "question": "31 * 32 + -80 ", "answer": "912", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8219", "question": "7405 - -4417 * -4859 + 4914 ", "answer": "-21449884", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8220", "question": "43596 * -94098 + -54908 + -19314 + -21237 ", "answer": "-4102391867", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8221", "question": "-12 + 83 - -89 * -35 * -100 ", "answer": "311571", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8222", "question": "-918672 + 836839 - -926031 + 156413 ", "answer": "1000611", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8223", "question": "16781 - 81063 * -87897 ", "answer": "7125211292", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8224", "question": "1982 * 8848 ", "answer": "17536736", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8225", "question": "33 + 963 + 543 - 675 ", "answer": "864", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8226", "question": "-628309 - -787584 ", "answer": "159275", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8227", "question": "-86 - 77 + 6 + 80 ", "answer": "-77", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8228", "question": "82645 - -68593 * -89192 - -29465 ", "answer": "-6117834746", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8229", "question": "79970 - -11176 ", "answer": "91146", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8230", "question": "-1788 + 4697 + -9366 ", "answer": "-6457", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8231", "question": "-78 * 59 + 83 ", "answer": "-4519", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8232", "question": "-1363 * -70441 * -47800 * -64234 - 17385 ", "answer": "294791008279154215", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8233", "question": "19642 * -67340 - 68169 ", "answer": "-1322760449", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8234", "question": "-70 - -9 * -54 + 38 - 100 ", "answer": "-618", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8235", "question": "-557 * -492 ", "answer": "274044", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8236", "question": "13625 - -29711 - -46495 + -11252 ", "answer": "78579", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8237", "question": "64 - 30 ", "answer": "34", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8238", "question": "-2483 - -8106 ", "answer": "5623", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8239", "question": "-339 + 649 ", "answer": "310", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8240", "question": "6310 * 8383 + 922 * -5282 + -9499 ", "answer": "48017227", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8241", "question": "61 - 68 ", "answer": "-7", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8242", "question": "488 * 4313 ", "answer": "2104744", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8243", "question": "809 - 51 * 585 * -480 ", "answer": "14321609", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8244", "question": "-542 + 864 ", "answer": "322", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8245", "question": "-65285 - -85968 - 9652 ", "answer": "11031", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8246", "question": "4040 - -8027 ", "answer": "12067", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8247", "question": "47767 + 65762 + -35539 - 5708 - 49561 ", "answer": "22721", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8248", "question": "-916679 - -139383 ", "answer": "-777296", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8249", "question": "-2191 - -8375 + -8675 + 1004 ", "answer": "-1487", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8250", "question": "-5480 + 5626 - 7793 - 3199 ", "answer": "-10846", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8251", "question": "-380 + -720 + 93 * 374 + -433 ", "answer": "33249", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8252", "question": "-253 - 739 ", "answer": "-992", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8253", "question": "1615 + 2190 + -4618 * -4388 - -7388 ", "answer": "20274977", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8254", "question": "753 * 241 + -862 ", "answer": "180611", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8255", "question": "-719298 - -884719 ", "answer": "165421", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8256", "question": "-10 * 63 * -18 - 19 ", "answer": "11321", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8257", "question": "687989 * -353218 ", "answer": "-243010098602", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8258", "question": "-83 - -18 + -3 ", "answer": "-68", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8259", "question": "74404 + 12923 ", "answer": "87327", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8260", "question": "554 - -870 * -534 + -736 - 169 ", "answer": "-464931", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8261", "question": "-85698 * -94840 - 22765 + -82587 ", "answer": "8127492968", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8262", "question": "-600 * -584 + -279 ", "answer": "350121", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8263", "question": "-659 + 827 * 6 + 881 + 588 ", "answer": "5772", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8264", "question": "3421 - -5416 ", "answer": "8837", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8265", "question": "-812 + 711 ", "answer": "-101", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8266", "question": "-67173 - 78749 ", "answer": "-145922", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8267", "question": "546 + 233 + 37 + -670 ", "answer": "146", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8268", "question": "100 - -65 + 56 * 44 * 30 ", "answer": "74085", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8269", "question": "4712 - 3285 ", "answer": "1427", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8270", "question": "190 * 849 - -677 ", "answer": "161987", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8271", "question": "-3148 - -56832 ", "answer": "53684", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8272", "question": "-5192 - 8858 ", "answer": "-14050", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8273", "question": "-15 * -80 - 55 + -83 ", "answer": "1062", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8274", "question": "72402 + 7164 + 35143 * -24915 ", "answer": "-875508279", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8275", "question": "-88 - -83 - 10 * 64 ", "answer": "-645", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8276", "question": "-2884 - -7474 * -2455 ", "answer": "-18351554", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8277", "question": "173981 * -532087 ", "answer": "-92573028347", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8278", "question": "-322719 + 58523 - -409484 ", "answer": "145288", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8279", "question": "-457 - -408 + 840 - 444 - 421 ", "answer": "-74", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8280", "question": "-2154 * 2470 - 6266 * -6858 + -9801 ", "answer": "37642047", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8281", "question": "-3323 + -994 - 1058 ", "answer": "-5375", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8282", "question": "81 * -42 ", "answer": "-3402", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8283", "question": "86 * 94 * -34 + -92 + 98 ", "answer": "-274850", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8284", "question": "76 + -17 * 62 ", "answer": "-978", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8285", "question": "670 * -857 ", "answer": "-574190", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8286", "question": "-17143 + -279267 - -228926 - 626077 ", "answer": "-693561", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8287", "question": "-774877 * 467516 ", "answer": "-362267395532", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8288", "question": "-571667 + 216206 * -808859 ", "answer": "-174880740621", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8289", "question": "-70 * -10 - 15 - -20 ", "answer": "705", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8290", "question": "96288 + -51645 - -78967 - -16810 - 81597 ", "answer": "58823", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8291", "question": "-840042 * 923439 ", "answer": "-775727544438", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8292", "question": "-71 + 63 + 71 + -16 * 92 ", "answer": "-1409", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8293", "question": "-82180 + -48988 - 45574 * -39586 ", "answer": "1803961196", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8294", "question": "26228 * 72073 * -79858 ", "answer": "-150958024568552", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8295", "question": "-2176 + 807 * -3016 * -1514 + -2849 ", "answer": "3684937743", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8296", "question": "-4564 - -580 - 2881 * 568 ", "answer": "-1640392", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8297", "question": "42 * -45 * 73 + -79 + -42 ", "answer": "-138091", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8298", "question": "-31 * -364 ", "answer": "11284", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8299", "question": "-39344 - 71723 + 86267 + 87037 * -97826 ", "answer": "-8514506362", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8300", "question": "-194 + 1506 + -9265 ", "answer": "-7953", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8301", "question": "-5859 + -88673 - -28821 * 85307 - 14101 ", "answer": "2458524414", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8302", "question": "77 + -75 + -46 ", "answer": "-44", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8303", "question": "-972020 - -858742 + 745562 - 258123 ", "answer": "374161", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8304", "question": "994 - 335 - 981 - -38 * 820 ", "answer": "30838", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8305", "question": "-94 + 10 + 63 ", "answer": "-21", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8306", "question": "-7085 * -9891 - -7484 - 6078 - 9323 ", "answer": "70069818", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8307", "question": "-17 * -58 * -71 - -27 ", "answer": "-69979", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8308", "question": "-7616 * 1649 ", "answer": "-12558784", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8309", "question": "65821 - -29302 + 28681 - 81767 ", "answer": "42037", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8310", "question": "91 - -89 - 0 - 8 + 11 ", "answer": "183", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8311", "question": "-523599 * -691006 ", "answer": "361810050594", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8312", "question": "-124 * -127 * 87 ", "answer": "1370076", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8313", "question": "-7401 - -615631 + 352693 * 536761 ", "answer": "189312455603", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8314", "question": "-263945 * 406475 ", "answer": "-107287043875", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8315", "question": "-2559 + 8224 * -8894 + -9111 ", "answer": "-73155926", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8316", "question": "-95 * 1 - -2 ", "answer": "-93", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8317", "question": "494 * 9424 ", "answer": "4655456", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8318", "question": "-372198 + -12745 - 982688 ", "answer": "-1367631", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8319", "question": "6911 - 1905 + 4002 + -8444 ", "answer": "564", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8320", "question": "-8798 * 54245 * 73734 ", "answer": "-35189367902340", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8321", "question": "-431 + -935 - 591 ", "answer": "-1957", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8322", "question": "3261 + 604 * -8982 ", "answer": "-5421867", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8323", "question": "-2154 * -1679 + 162 ", "answer": "3616728", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8324", "question": "-5258 + -4228 + -901 ", "answer": "-10387", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8325", "question": "738927 * 294857 ", "answer": "217877798439", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8326", "question": "-803347 - 989032 - -962298 * -903652 + 523489 ", "answer": "-869583781186", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8327", "question": "-92346 - 72691 + -27061 ", "answer": "-192098", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8328", "question": "95655 * -18914 ", "answer": "-1809218670", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8329", "question": "46 + 91 ", "answer": "137", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8330", "question": "511 + 839 ", "answer": "1350", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8331", "question": "-486011 * -443163 - -789044 * 101320 + -739581 ", "answer": "295327291292", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8332", "question": "-462 * -17 - 534 - 97 ", "answer": "7223", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8333", "question": "-351419 - -974100 * 244474 * 266302 ", "answer": "63417723745315381", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8334", "question": "299002 - 348561 - 377663 - -987030 ", "answer": "559808", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8335", "question": "-818 - 380 * -624 - 310 * 503 ", "answer": "80372", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8336", "question": "-49415 - -7723 ", "answer": "-41692", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8337", "question": "-9451 - 6531 * 7767 ", "answer": "-50735728", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8338", "question": "-26 + 0 ", "answer": "-26", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8339", "question": "-37 * 68 ", "answer": "-2516", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8340", "question": "-347130 * -181435 + -377015 ", "answer": "62981154535", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8341", "question": "-477401 + 638057 ", "answer": "160656", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8342", "question": "9477 + -55086 - 6116 - 86750 ", "answer": "-138475", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8343", "question": "-62 + -68 + 84 + 61 - 16 ", "answer": "-1", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8344", "question": "154919 - -469714 - -609204 - 108732 - -673108 ", "answer": "1798213", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8345", "question": "-818 - -167 - -419 ", "answer": "-232", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8346", "question": "381815 - 307763 * 939489 * -508232 ", "answer": "146950176647858639", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8347", "question": "5710 * 219 ", "answer": "1250490", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8348", "question": "889 + -585 - -198 - -675 - -965 ", "answer": "2142", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8349", "question": "-39 + 100 + 49 ", "answer": "110", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8350", "question": "-5902 - -3203 + 9346 - -1517 - -7098 ", "answer": "15262", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8351", "question": "-441378 - 804847 ", "answer": "-1246225", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8352", "question": "-494 + 416 ", "answer": "-78", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8353", "question": "235 * 559 * 894 - 885 - -671 ", "answer": "117440096", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8354", "question": "56 + 31 * -100 - 51 + -77 ", "answer": "-3172", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8355", "question": "54971 + -23316 * -40255 + -3439 ", "answer": "938637112", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8356", "question": "36810 * -27078 - 31317 * -15344 * 21275 ", "answer": "10222237480020", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8357", "question": "92669 - -90331 * -69753 + -88181 ", "answer": "-6300853755", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8358", "question": "345586 + -424894 * 716825 + 413573 * 830645 ", "answer": "38958048621", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8359", "question": "1000 - 238 + 936 ", "answer": "1698", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8360", "question": "8797 * -6577 - -918 ", "answer": "-57856951", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8361", "question": "-8301 * 1761 + -2019 * -3302 ", "answer": "-7951323", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8362", "question": "-70 + 62 * -100 ", "answer": "-6270", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8363", "question": "13747 * 90196 - -94128 * -79368 ", "answer": "-6230826692", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8364", "question": "-7222 + 4331 + -4952 ", "answer": "-7843", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8365", "question": "36944 * -98983 * 89474 * 19386 * 41355 ", "answer": "-262311671426823864901440", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8366", "question": "33791 * 80947 ", "answer": "2735280077", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8367", "question": "-959115 - 908225 - -388640 + 702044 - 3639 ", "answer": "-780295", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8368", "question": "1 * -31 * -83 + -43 * 30 ", "answer": "1283", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8369", "question": "-423517 * 307371 ", "answer": "-130176843807", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8370", "question": "-494 * 30 * 537 - 329 ", "answer": "-7958669", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8371", "question": "76 * 18 + -9 * -67 ", "answer": "1971", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8372", "question": "49 + 62 * -6 ", "answer": "-323", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8373", "question": "13 - 50 ", "answer": "-37", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8374", "question": "884194 + -766547 * 156 - -104666 + -316307 ", "answer": "-118908779", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8375", "question": "91 * -50 - -2 - -27 - -6 ", "answer": "-4515", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8376", "question": "-486234 + -598335 + 371950 * -410772 ", "answer": "-152787729969", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8377", "question": "78 + 84 * -99 - -81 ", "answer": "-8157", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8378", "question": "-342 - -296 - 69 - 753 ", "answer": "-868", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8379", "question": "-803 - -567 - -826 - 323 - -18 ", "answer": "285", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8380", "question": "1138 * -10388 ", "answer": "-11821544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8381", "question": "-54464 + 61475 - 45292 + 35174 + 79443 ", "answer": "76336", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8382", "question": "-94 * 66 ", "answer": "-6204", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8383", "question": "53 * -30 * -95 ", "answer": "151050", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8384", "question": "-7311 - -4481 ", "answer": "-2830", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8385", "question": "46 + 40 - 17 + 31 ", "answer": "100", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8386", "question": "76 * 70 - 16 + 48 ", "answer": "5352", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8387", "question": "-24 - 37 - 81 * -89 * -9 ", "answer": "-64942", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8388", "question": "-8528 - 522444 * -427957 * -306377 * -428341 ", "answer": "29341727934934144399228", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8389", "question": "8701 * 4937 * -3493 + -3092 ", "answer": "-150048234733", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8390", "question": "-7 * -27 - 30 + 58 ", "answer": "217", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8391", "question": "7296 - -6873 - 6467 * -3375 ", "answer": "21840294", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8392", "question": "-3 + -27 + 44 * -59 - 80 ", "answer": "-2706", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8393", "question": "51679 * 34065 - -55654 - 86799 - 69092 ", "answer": "1760344898", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8394", "question": "67946 + 88445 - -13368 - -66175 ", "answer": "235934", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8395", "question": "-271314 + -565645 * 224515 - 507108 ", "answer": "-126996565597", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8396", "question": "-316623 * 980761 ", "answer": "-310531490103", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8397", "question": "93547 * 70893 * -35164 ", "answer": "-233201581190244", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8398", "question": "790267 - 235879 + 479276 ", "answer": "1033664", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8399", "question": "78 - -83 * 17 + 11 * -27 ", "answer": "1192", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8400", "question": "-67 - 30 * -76 * 61 ", "answer": "139013", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8401", "question": "-273 * -665 + 672 ", "answer": "182217", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8402", "question": "437269 + 520609 * 412718 * 390123 - 918926 ", "answer": "83823663410445569", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8403", "question": "-5919 + 3959 ", "answer": "-1960", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8404", "question": "63879 * 27506 * 48519 - 22079 - -12497 ", "answer": "85250589089124", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8405", "question": "-7676 + -2558 ", "answer": "-10234", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8406", "question": "2215 + -4979 + -564 ", "answer": "-3328", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8407", "question": "-83 + -20 * 11 * -40 * 55 ", "answer": "483917", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8408", "question": "-64 * -29 * 39 * -55 ", "answer": "-3981120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8409", "question": "66 * -6 * -4 + -34 ", "answer": "1550", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8410", "question": "10 - 8 + 54 ", "answer": "56", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8411", "question": "-44 + -73 + 12 + 70 ", "answer": "-35", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8412", "question": "-99434 * -445619 * 354824 - 901303 ", "answer": "15722137769811001", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8413", "question": "-471517 - 653023 ", "answer": "-1124540", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8414", "question": "832947 * -117292 ", "answer": "-97698019524", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8415", "question": "981 * 48 + 945 - 885 ", "answer": "47148", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8416", "question": "7377 * 4228 ", "answer": "31189956", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8417", "question": "37530 + 96814 - 18712 + -76869 * 41228 ", "answer": "-3169039500", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8418", "question": "-21920 - 27006 ", "answer": "-48926", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8419", "question": "87 + -15 ", "answer": "72", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8420", "question": "-60820 - 3763 ", "answer": "-64583", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8421", "question": "36551 + 2683 - 98384 ", "answer": "-59150", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8422", "question": "-566 + 292 * 699 * 798 + -458 ", "answer": "162877160", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8423", "question": "-4712 + -9326 ", "answer": "-14038", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8424", "question": "223 * 66 + 543 - -38 ", "answer": "15299", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8425", "question": "-920685 - 358071 + -398000 ", "answer": "-1676756", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8426", "question": "-65 - 77 ", "answer": "-142", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8427", "question": "-6376 * 5369 - -5447 ", "answer": "-34227297", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8428", "question": "-84 * 53 * 1 ", "answer": "-4452", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8429", "question": "365 * -117 - -385 + -206 * -315 ", "answer": "22570", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8430", "question": "9053 - 3795 ", "answer": "5258", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8431", "question": "-59 * 98 ", "answer": "-5782", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8432", "question": "37404 + 94967 ", "answer": "132371", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8433", "question": "71420 + 68360 * -98739 ", "answer": "-6749726620", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8434", "question": "-261140 * -685265 - -458323 * -301092 - -423226 ", "answer": "40953136610", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8435", "question": "349145 * -49622 - -282529 ", "answer": "-17324990661", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8436", "question": "91250 - -53026 - 31507 ", "answer": "112769", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8437", "question": "69131 * -80781 - -67776 * -43854 ", "answer": "-8556720015", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8438", "question": "5892 + -7580 - 3922 ", "answer": "-5610", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8439", "question": "-5867 + -7853 * -8487 ", "answer": "66642544", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8440", "question": "-43 + 52 + -39 + 80 ", "answer": "50", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8441", "question": "482 + -2 ", "answer": "480", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8442", "question": "-329 - 506 + -998 - -977 * -30 ", "answer": "-31143", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8443", "question": "-409 - -594 ", "answer": "185", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8444", "question": "12 * 86 - 29 + -40 ", "answer": "963", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8445", "question": "-227 - 29 - 654 ", "answer": "-910", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8446", "question": "46 * -53 ", "answer": "-2438", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8447", "question": "-71 * -30 ", "answer": "2130", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8448", "question": "-28749 + -36772 - -85477 ", "answer": "19956", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8449", "question": "-112258 * -947921 * -229492 ", "answer": "-24420637440606056", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8450", "question": "729202 - 36775 ", "answer": "692427", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8451", "question": "77 * 41 - 47 - 65 + -35 ", "answer": "3010", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8452", "question": "333869 * 442470 ", "answer": "147727016430", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8453", "question": "-73 + -834 * -470 ", "answer": "391907", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8454", "question": "-59293 * -49788 + -82364 ", "answer": "2951997520", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8455", "question": "-23283 * -58316 + -79224 ", "answer": "1357692204", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8456", "question": "6 + -88 * -2 + 70 ", "answer": "252", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8457", "question": "-83 * 50 - 23 - 97 + 0 ", "answer": "-4270", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8458", "question": "415562 + -692016 ", "answer": "-276454", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8459", "question": "-30155 * -22000 * -33846 ", "answer": "-22453774860000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8460", "question": "-26 - 86 * 21 * 54 + 0 ", "answer": "-97550", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8461", "question": "-842 * 280 + -558 + -197 ", "answer": "-236515", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8462", "question": "-185 + -252 ", "answer": "-437", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8463", "question": "14962 * 42325 ", "answer": "633266650", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8464", "question": "-1085 - 132 * -9777 + 9606 + -687 ", "answer": "1298398", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8465", "question": "-1297 * -8999 - 9212 * 6122 * -1103 ", "answer": "62216309695", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8466", "question": "657 * -895 * 188 ", "answer": "-110546820", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8467", "question": "-43 + 35 * 74 - -27 ", "answer": "2574", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8468", "question": "-91733 + 18380 + -41744 ", "answer": "-115097", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8469", "question": "630540 - 437180 - 150661 - -788152 ", "answer": "830851", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8470", "question": "-546 * -382 ", "answer": "208572", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8471", "question": "-613 - -391 - -486 ", "answer": "264", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8472", "question": "-14 * -54 - 39 * -100 ", "answer": "4656", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8473", "question": "-1 + -5 * 22 ", "answer": "-111", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8474", "question": "4369 - -3445 - -6372 - 3025 - 955 ", "answer": "10206", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8475", "question": "-890 + 3624 - -6546 - 2142 ", "answer": "7138", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8476", "question": "-1230 - -9977 * -5089 ", "answer": "-50774183", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8477", "question": "-7651 * 1798 - -1925 - 9029 ", "answer": "-13763602", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8478", "question": "988589 * 947980 - -810052 + 490574 * -405817 ", "answer": "738080141314", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8479", "question": "-2552 - 287 + -644 ", "answer": "-3483", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8480", "question": "860270 + -34281 * -284734 ", "answer": "9761826524", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8481", "question": "-63964 * 86326 * -37009 ", "answer": "204354677574376", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8482", "question": "-90175 * 36590 ", "answer": "-3299503250", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8483", "question": "38 + 994 ", "answer": "1032", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8484", "question": "2324 - 5655 ", "answer": "-3331", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8485", "question": "-70351 * 4661 * 67616 + -85383 ", "answer": "-22171692925159", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8486", "question": "16868 - 63814 * 48020 ", "answer": "-3064331412", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8487", "question": "25402 + -67301 * -91794 + 74505 ", "answer": "6177927901", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8488", "question": "-75927 * -30070 ", "answer": "2283124890", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8489", "question": "51969 * -97554 ", "answer": "-5069783826", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8490", "question": "-7407 + -2726 * 4790 ", "answer": "-13064947", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8491", "question": "131417 - -966209 + 728103 * 735333 + -81949 ", "answer": "535399178976", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8492", "question": "715096 - -692384 + 357126 + -10367 ", "answer": "1754239", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8493", "question": "693882 * 865599 + 721389 * -73670 - -54778 ", "answer": "547478892466", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8494", "question": "-51 - -8 - 96 + 20 ", "answer": "-119", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8495", "question": "-320 * 331 * 65 - 500 ", "answer": "-6885300", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8496", "question": "64 * 29 + 70 ", "answer": "1926", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8497", "question": "-99 + 32 * 85 ", "answer": "2621", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8498", "question": "-210403 * 12147 * 866449 ", "answer": "-2214440237299209", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8499", "question": "420339 - -481248 + -836376 * -312401 + 50904 ", "answer": "261285651267", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8500", "question": "-9496 * 8770 * -5028 + 5564 * -9337 ", "answer": "418679486692", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8501", "question": "5177 + -9735 + 6175 + 9277 ", "answer": "10894", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8502", "question": "-86 - -66 - -67 - 12 - 63 ", "answer": "-28", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8503", "question": "-71379 + -16692 * 93899 ", "answer": "-1567433487", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8504", "question": "-3016 * 3218 ", "answer": "-9705488", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8505", "question": "-6764 * -81 + -5077 + -7829 ", "answer": "534978", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8506", "question": "-22 - 82 ", "answer": "-104", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8507", "question": "715 + 179 + 622 ", "answer": "1516", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8508", "question": "6667 * 5168 - 2627 + 5307 ", "answer": "34457736", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8509", "question": "29 + 85 + -85 - -43 + -99 ", "answer": "-27", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8510", "question": "752 - -900 - 200 + 438 * -617 ", "answer": "-268794", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8511", "question": "-517 - 116 + -726 * -227 - -952 ", "answer": "165121", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8512", "question": "3297 * 134 + 9632 ", "answer": "451430", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8513", "question": "-21 * -6 - 25 ", "answer": "101", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8514", "question": "-410 * -586 * -346 * -90 + 78 ", "answer": "7481696478", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8515", "question": "83710 - -73662 + -45370 * 68792 ", "answer": "-3120935668", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8516", "question": "677 * 518 ", "answer": "350686", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8517", "question": "873 * -577 * -158 + 202 ", "answer": "79588120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8518", "question": "76 * -45 ", "answer": "-3420", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8519", "question": "-90 - -55 - -37 + -7 * 18 ", "answer": "-124", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8520", "question": "-5182 + -5248 + 7329 + -1760 + -9259 ", "answer": "-14120", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8521", "question": "5406 + -6213 * 5829 - -5677 + 1230 ", "answer": "-36203264", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8522", "question": "-23970 * 56737 + 26754 - 23808 - 58126 ", "answer": "-1360041070", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8523", "question": "-794156 - 580376 * 64008 - -977337 * 254143 ", "answer": "211233856027", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8524", "question": "157662 + -205409 + 111140 ", "answer": "63393", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8525", "question": "49317 * -17010 - 81719 + 41565 ", "answer": "-838922324", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8526", "question": "-9333 + -8477 - 6224 ", "answer": "-24034", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8527", "question": "-35917 * 32237 + -74202 ", "answer": "-1157930531", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8528", "question": "-141167 * -866690 * 136901 * 352167 * -765252 ", "answer": "-4513949775503000562177625320", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8529", "question": "-3019 + 5870 + -8501 + -3402 ", "answer": "-9052", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8530", "question": "-91 - -83 - -60 * -95 ", "answer": "-5708", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8531", "question": "77827 + 75014 * 80773 * -57781 - 77588 ", "answer": "-350101193500743", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8532", "question": "144754 * -448349 - -49917 ", "answer": "-64900261229", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8533", "question": "817281 * 364697 - 588784 ", "answer": "298059340073", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8534", "question": "42 + 97 * -68 * 24 - -32 ", "answer": "-158230", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8535", "question": "-204550 * -703795 * -39660 ", "answer": "-5709503859135000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8536", "question": "-496 - -5804 + 7236 + -3878 ", "answer": "8666", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8537", "question": "-95683 - 14266 ", "answer": "-109949", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8538", "question": "49 * 52 + 25 ", "answer": "2573", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8539", "question": "-786900 - 591568 ", "answer": "-1378468", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8540", "question": "-99620 - -97311 - -46333 ", "answer": "44024", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8541", "question": "-21605 + -74864 - -59838 ", "answer": "-36631", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8542", "question": "1972 + -503 * 3786 - -8336 + -4434 ", "answer": "-1898484", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8543", "question": "31 - -203 + -914 - 825 * -784 ", "answer": "646120", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8544", "question": "-135 + 4205 ", "answer": "4070", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8545", "question": "-134 + 687 ", "answer": "553", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8546", "question": "-98 - 76 ", "answer": "-174", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8547", "question": "-432 + 472 + -294 * 906 ", "answer": "-266324", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8548", "question": "-86142 + 33765 + -54777 * -80452 ", "answer": "4406866827", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8549", "question": "9977 - -2342 - -5101 * 7318 * -8242 ", "answer": "-307666578237", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8550", "question": "31 - 44 - -55 * 46 + -50 ", "answer": "2467", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8551", "question": "98 + 19 ", "answer": "117", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8552", "question": "-98826 - -76820 * -27484 - 46448 ", "answer": "-2111466154", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8553", "question": "-720 * -695 ", "answer": "500400", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8554", "question": "-90 - 575 + 452 * 566 ", "answer": "255167", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8555", "question": "5 - 605 + 780 - -539 ", "answer": "719", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8556", "question": "-51642 - 74558 - 96964 + -80993 - 8387 ", "answer": "-312544", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8557", "question": "82 * 67 * 38 ", "answer": "208772", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8558", "question": "-61 + 81 - -36 - 26 - -23 ", "answer": "53", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8559", "question": "64617 - -13539 * -81716 + -46900 ", "answer": "-1106335207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8560", "question": "572 - 472 ", "answer": "100", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8561", "question": "-38 - -61 ", "answer": "23", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8562", "question": "60250 - -76182 ", "answer": "136432", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8563", "question": "-9128 - 8791 * -6773 * -4694 ", "answer": "-279487542570", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8564", "question": "31 * 29 ", "answer": "899", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8565", "question": "-313081 + -685107 * -508046 ", "answer": "348065557841", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8566", "question": "-8304 * 2047 - -4170 * -5807 ", "answer": "-41213478", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8567", "question": "868082 * 319977 + 919956 + 489538 * -268908 ", "answer": "146126509566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8568", "question": "17 + 38 ", "answer": "55", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8569", "question": "-2534 + -4263 * -9830 * -7341 + -8262 ", "answer": "-307626744686", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8570", "question": "143494 - -361876 ", "answer": "505370", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8571", "question": "-49435 + -185209 ", "answer": "-234644", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8572", "question": "53483 * 25739 + -14400 ", "answer": "1376584537", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8573", "question": "96 - 50 + 2 * 62 + 75 ", "answer": "245", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8574", "question": "-487161 * 751438 ", "answer": "-366071287518", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8575", "question": "-6591 + 2720 * -6991 + 8574 ", "answer": "-19013537", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8576", "question": "-1478 - -6779 + 3828 ", "answer": "9129", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8577", "question": "-262068 * 266738 - -570206 + -897870 ", "answer": "-69903821848", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8578", "question": "-3899 + -418 + -5067 ", "answer": "-9384", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8579", "question": "-23 - -46 + -17 - -78 ", "answer": "84", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8580", "question": "-552 - -253 + -957 * -915 * -736 ", "answer": "-644482379", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8581", "question": "-876 + 571 - 16 ", "answer": "-321", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8582", "question": "6956 + 7415 + 1068 - 5148 ", "answer": "10291", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8583", "question": "14317 + -93315 + -34724 - -84864 ", "answer": "-28858", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8584", "question": "-866258 - -415952 - -837922 - 606933 * 406334 ", "answer": "-246617126006", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8585", "question": "42 - 99 - -81 + -68 + 64 ", "answer": "20", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8586", "question": "-144354 - 715771 + 356819 + -526547 * 104444 ", "answer": "-54995178174", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8587", "question": "-26 * 37 ", "answer": "-962", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8588", "question": "85 + 67 - -84 ", "answer": "236", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8589", "question": "182 + 631 - -649 * -815 ", "answer": "-528122", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8590", "question": "80232 + -443 + 68676 ", "answer": "148465", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8591", "question": "-2519 - -82563 - 46453 * -95262 + -94705 ", "answer": "4425191025", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8592", "question": "953 - -668 ", "answer": "1621", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8593", "question": "-332555 - -119382 + 925634 + -232739 + -56040 ", "answer": "423682", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8594", "question": "-28 - -7 * -57 * -47 ", "answer": "18725", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8595", "question": "-125 * -85 * -203 ", "answer": "-2156875", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8596", "question": "-504025 + -904663 * -529636 + 991424 * -546718 ", "answer": "-62887757789", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8597", "question": "55619 + -35981 - -59389 ", "answer": "79027", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8598", "question": "-195 - -457 * 31 ", "answer": "13972", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8599", "question": "-99 + 35 + -83 + -37 ", "answer": "-184", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8600", "question": "-718 * -391 + -718 ", "answer": "280020", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8601", "question": "-19 * -79 + -1 ", "answer": "1500", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8602", "question": "61744 - -73999 - 8788 ", "answer": "126955", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8603", "question": "51047 * -521353 * 284910 + 329145 + 680708 ", "answer": "-7582454161831957", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8604", "question": "-358 * 803 + 149 * -309 * 251 ", "answer": "-11843765", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8605", "question": "71 - -35 ", "answer": "106", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8606", "question": "635 - -360 ", "answer": "995", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8607", "question": "3613 - -936 ", "answer": "4549", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8608", "question": "992260 + -460322 - 30433 + 4294 + -442573 ", "answer": "63226", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8609", "question": "8256 * 9359 + -5562 ", "answer": "77262342", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8610", "question": "-790 + -223 + -112 - -219 - -223 ", "answer": "-683", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8611", "question": "9638 - -663 ", "answer": "10301", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8612", "question": "81389 - 45234 + 62389 - 32605 - -39761 ", "answer": "105700", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8613", "question": "739 - 776 ", "answer": "-37", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8614", "question": "-57 + -98 - -15 ", "answer": "-140", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8615", "question": "-6135 - 7388 * 9590 * -3147 - -3853 ", "answer": "222967842958", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8616", "question": "747878 + 914147 ", "answer": "1662025", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8617", "question": "8970 + 822 * 4015 ", "answer": "3309300", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8618", "question": "-5336 * -5605 ", "answer": "29908280", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8619", "question": "-29 + 28 - -96 + 94 ", "answer": "189", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8620", "question": "-942386 - 453676 + 49143 * 252486 - -788486 ", "answer": "12407311922", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8621", "question": "27 * -65 * -90 + -39 ", "answer": "157911", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8622", "question": "90 + 97 - 28 + 26 ", "answer": "185", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8623", "question": "-791 + 21 - 379 ", "answer": "-1149", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8624", "question": "60 - 36 ", "answer": "24", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8625", "question": "-988 + 625 * -655 - -590 ", "answer": "-409773", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8626", "question": "461029 + 876594 * -23745 - 768339 * -186777 ", "answer": "122693789902", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8627", "question": "24 * 16 - -3 - 54 ", "answer": "333", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8628", "question": "792698 + 236574 * 83051 ", "answer": "19648499972", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8629", "question": "379694 + 207841 ", "answer": "587535", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8630", "question": "51 - 38 * -31 + -17 ", "answer": "1212", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8631", "question": "-1034 * 8524 + 5128 + -5931 ", "answer": "-8814619", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8632", "question": "891126 * 135935 - 742719 * 181611 ", "answer": "-13750727499", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8633", "question": "6286 - 1423 + -1672 - 2378 ", "answer": "813", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8634", "question": "1660 + 5184 - 2620 * -2757 + -4870 ", "answer": "7225314", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8635", "question": "-571625 + 403116 + -711449 ", "answer": "-879958", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8636", "question": "-542762 * -28191 - 208661 - 521285 * 333692 ", "answer": "-158647839339", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8637", "question": "214546 - 395453 - -564845 * -31851 ", "answer": "-17991059002", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8638", "question": "-83520 - 62191 - -52401 + -34359 * 22192 ", "answer": "-762588238", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8639", "question": "-3250 + -3728 + 9133 ", "answer": "2155", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8640", "question": "-57468 + 2 ", "answer": "-57466", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8641", "question": "-195 - -707 * 914 - -323 ", "answer": "646326", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8642", "question": "-48 + 13 ", "answer": "-35", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8643", "question": "-281312 + -533698 + 438376 - -347977 + -738602 ", "answer": "-767259", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8644", "question": "47 + 435 - 994 * -110 ", "answer": "109822", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8645", "question": "-475143 * 242975 * -152529 + -956581 * 754911 ", "answer": "17608426094535534", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8646", "question": "873397 + -821450 ", "answer": "51947", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8647", "question": "464121 - 922505 - 292073 - -4874 * -829098 ", "answer": "-4041774109", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8648", "question": "11 - -58 - -68 ", "answer": "137", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8649", "question": "40137 * -87174 * 4994 ", "answer": "-17473520772972", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8650", "question": "-8352 * -8474 - 2173 + 4192 - -5678 ", "answer": "70782545", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8651", "question": "-979 * 290 - -820 * 340 + 80 ", "answer": "-5030", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8652", "question": "-167 + -26266 * 29806 * -36199 ", "answer": "28339632250637", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8653", "question": "-934 * 612 * -508 ", "answer": "290376864", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8654", "question": "-31520 + -89561 + -33022 * 13056 + -23975 ", "answer": "-431280288", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8655", "question": "-834222 - 511039 * -495328 * 706950 * -613803 ", "answer": "-109841038104190887517422", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8656", "question": "88748 - 13511 + -89559 * 62721 * -20052 ", "answer": "112636696817265", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8657", "question": "-992 - 620 - 976 - 146 * -91 ", "answer": "10698", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8658", "question": "671283 * -855576 - 932374 - -808973 + -972179 ", "answer": "-574334719588", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8659", "question": "-576 * -608 - 388 - -150 ", "answer": "349970", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8660", "question": "-2622 - 7798 ", "answer": "-10420", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8661", "question": "594007 + 787710 + 135431 ", "answer": "1517148", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8662", "question": "3212 - -5995 - -5354 * 9653 ", "answer": "51691369", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8663", "question": "-44 - -225 - -591 * 84 * -282 ", "answer": "-13999427", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8664", "question": "159 + -554 + -46 + -413 ", "answer": "-854", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8665", "question": "-473 * -671 * 4 + -72 ", "answer": "1269460", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8666", "question": "23265 - -93934 ", "answer": "117199", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8667", "question": "-56824 + 46804 + -1539 - 21314 - 26373 ", "answer": "-59246", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8668", "question": "-657166 * 666399 + -4645 * 156160 ", "answer": "-438660128434", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8669", "question": "-91628 - -41131 + -53354 ", "answer": "-103851", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8670", "question": "-6286 - 6167 - -2590 - -1571 ", "answer": "-8292", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8671", "question": "-3384 - -6313 ", "answer": "2929", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8672", "question": "693555 + 174361 ", "answer": "867916", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8673", "question": "-874597 * -396062 * -666243 * -429113 ", "answer": "99031986400785531837426", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8674", "question": "-172726 - 207696 * -747723 ", "answer": "155298903482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8675", "question": "-544 + -893 - -172 - 11 - 267 ", "answer": "-1543", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8676", "question": "514 + -892 * -423 - 870 * -116 ", "answer": "478750", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8677", "question": "1584 - -6854 * 8653 - 6315 ", "answer": "59302931", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8678", "question": "62375 - 78564 ", "answer": "-16189", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8679", "question": "-43398 - -94384 - -36140 - 41784 * 53303 ", "answer": "-2227125426", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8680", "question": "-7517 - -2238 * -7886 + -6892 ", "answer": "-17663277", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8681", "question": "620 - 948 ", "answer": "-328", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8682", "question": "-270217 + 908129 * 583234 + 757611 * 659626 ", "answer": "1029391352455", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8683", "question": "43 + 40 ", "answer": "83", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8684", "question": "38674 - 19103 * 40969 + 82374 * -4897 ", "answer": "-1185977611", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8685", "question": "24 * 17 * 65 ", "answer": "26520", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8686", "question": "-23576 * 27190 + 88628 ", "answer": "-640942812", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8687", "question": "1758 + 9587 + 3362 + -8021 + -8609 ", "answer": "-1923", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8688", "question": "74 + -31 * 12 * -25 * -21 ", "answer": "-195226", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8689", "question": "1884 - -992 + 2219 + -8318 ", "answer": "-3223", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8690", "question": "892719 - -308267 + -789504 ", "answer": "411482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8691", "question": "97254 - -67810 * -55974 - -75446 * -71303 ", "answer": "-9175025824", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8692", "question": "-947 * -785 * 985 * 252 ", "answer": "184525506900", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8693", "question": "-1543 + -18431 - 57559 * 86022 + 67103 ", "answer": "-4951293169", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8694", "question": "40990 * -49477 - 250 + -64076 - 40010 ", "answer": "-2028166566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8695", "question": "-35966 - 450748 + -696951 - -122349 - 779383 ", "answer": "-1840699", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8696", "question": "909 - 391 - 475 + -749 + -35 ", "answer": "-741", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8697", "question": "69 + -88 + -51 + 9 ", "answer": "-61", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8698", "question": "5276 + -9419 + 8134 ", "answer": "3991", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8699", "question": "623408 - -978100 ", "answer": "1601508", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8700", "question": "-66 - 74 + 37 + 29 ", "answer": "-74", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8701", "question": "357 * -158 * 451 - 122 + 894 ", "answer": "-25438334", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8702", "question": "5297 + -9555 * 1265 * 7021 * -311 ", "answer": "26392502967122", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8703", "question": "6025 * -6551 + 8223 ", "answer": "-39461552", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8704", "question": "784 - 888 * 256 - -22 ", "answer": "-226522", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8705", "question": "-290 * 148 - -128 ", "answer": "-42792", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8706", "question": "-701 + 245 ", "answer": "-456", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8707", "question": "-807 * -463 - 499 ", "answer": "373142", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8708", "question": "-349968 * 259066 - -398945 + 851319 ", "answer": "-90663559624", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8709", "question": "-6840 + 4156 + -5833 - 4729 ", "answer": "-13246", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8710", "question": "161 - 40 * -68 - -732 * -127 ", "answer": "-90083", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8711", "question": "-638 + -557 - 322 * 995 ", "answer": "-321585", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8712", "question": "-56 + -53 * 50 ", "answer": "-2706", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8713", "question": "306765 + 252054 - 522799 * 1020 * -428318 ", "answer": "228402707082459", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8714", "question": "9389 + 9507 + -2748 + 5215 ", "answer": "21363", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8715", "question": "499 - 402 - 332 ", "answer": "-235", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8716", "question": "-547 - 673 + 848 + -690 * 167 ", "answer": "-115602", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8717", "question": "-930278 - 77649 + -144705 + 665880 ", "answer": "-486752", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8718", "question": "-10 * 43 + -43 + -69 + 86 ", "answer": "-456", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8719", "question": "-7229 - 633 + 2994 ", "answer": "-4868", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8720", "question": "57381 - 98305 - -12080 - 85327 ", "answer": "-114171", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8721", "question": "-67 + -23 - -38 ", "answer": "-52", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8722", "question": "599074 - -738169 - -397852 - 791651 * 23033 ", "answer": "-18232362388", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8723", "question": "-722 - -637 * 894 - 29 ", "answer": "568727", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8724", "question": "-471 + -810 * -819 ", "answer": "662919", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8725", "question": "632418 - -149593 ", "answer": "782011", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8726", "question": "43 * -75 + 3 ", "answer": "-3222", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8727", "question": "-3231 + 5103 ", "answer": "1872", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8728", "question": "-21348 - 40030 * -28021 ", "answer": "1121659282", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8729", "question": "-253 * 942 - 351 + -931 ", "answer": "-239608", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8730", "question": "-835 - -401 * 893 ", "answer": "357258", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8731", "question": "240939 + -968767 ", "answer": "-727828", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8732", "question": "-54969 * -67373 ", "answer": "3703426437", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8733", "question": "878 + -15 * 910 ", "answer": "-12772", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8734", "question": "93 * -2 ", "answer": "-186", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8735", "question": "9222 * 45962 + 14905 + -75933 + 62693 ", "answer": "423863229", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8736", "question": "-9920 + -5812 * 1839 ", "answer": "-10698188", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8737", "question": "-74 - 24 + -4 ", "answer": "-102", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8738", "question": "593051 + 674121 * 552709 + 424724 * -883437 ", "answer": "-2623559548", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8739", "question": "-179 + -128 - -613 * -23 * 582 ", "answer": "-8205925", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8740", "question": "-87 + 8 - 74 + -16 ", "answer": "-169", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8741", "question": "9504 - 8959 ", "answer": "545", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8742", "question": "-672701 + -188619 ", "answer": "-861320", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8743", "question": "390 * -117 + 962 - -928 + -553 ", "answer": "-44293", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8744", "question": "31 + -29 - 47 ", "answer": "-45", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8745", "question": "-60477 * 42051 + 3386 ", "answer": "-2543114941", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8746", "question": "-907958 - 167347 - 594961 * 364368 * 982503 ", "answer": "-212991666884484249", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8747", "question": "-522 * -158 ", "answer": "82476", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8748", "question": "-6278 * -3794 - 7266 - -439 * 3779 ", "answer": "25470447", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8749", "question": "-6271 - 26317 ", "answer": "-32588", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8750", "question": "382 - 3942 - 4483 + -3096 ", "answer": "-11139", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8751", "question": "92240 + -98337 ", "answer": "-6097", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8752", "question": "-917785 - 265778 * 835321 + -844617 - 588239 ", "answer": "-222012295379", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8753", "question": "9585 + -7194 - 9117 + 7909 ", "answer": "1183", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8754", "question": "-1035 * -1470 * 274 + 603 - -8882 ", "answer": "416886785", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8755", "question": "-54 + 17 + -42 ", "answer": "-79", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8756", "question": "-77980 - 85566 ", "answer": "-163546", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8757", "question": "386 * -631 + -153 ", "answer": "-243719", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8758", "question": "7576 - -1389 ", "answer": "8965", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8759", "question": "99 - -15 ", "answer": "114", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8760", "question": "84 * 75 * 20 * 2 * -50 ", "answer": "-12600000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8761", "question": "-926 - -2134 ", "answer": "1208", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8762", "question": "16 * -64 ", "answer": "-1024", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8763", "question": "-26357 + -52242 - 56755 ", "answer": "-135354", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8764", "question": "-207410 + 991792 * 300375 ", "answer": "297909314590", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8765", "question": "-305349 - -956532 * 694768 + 761642 * -608565 ", "answer": "201058855497", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8766", "question": "-5591 - 5061 + -2181 ", "answer": "-12833", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8767", "question": "-438087 * 921109 ", "answer": "-403525878483", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8768", "question": "-251 * 205 * 963 * 404 ", "answer": "-20018670660", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8769", "question": "7859 - 9027 + -137 ", "answer": "-1305", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8770", "question": "-3179 - -8673 * 1240 ", "answer": "10751341", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8771", "question": "-9240 * -6705 - 3763 * 6872 + -8026 ", "answer": "36086838", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8772", "question": "30 - -91 + 64 + -1 ", "answer": "184", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8773", "question": "3011 * 7430 - -7887 * 428 ", "answer": "25747366", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8774", "question": "-507110 - 894724 + 426021 + 902917 ", "answer": "-72896", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8775", "question": "-251 - 415 - 568 * 748 ", "answer": "-425530", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8776", "question": "-35 - 6961 + -8346 ", "answer": "-15342", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8777", "question": "-16693 - 70282 ", "answer": "-86975", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8778", "question": "9693 - 770 ", "answer": "8923", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8779", "question": "-32117 - 24205 * -23094 ", "answer": "558958153", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8780", "question": "-971984 - 645022 * -320043 + -532587 * -295419 ", "answer": "363770122915", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8781", "question": "-2389 + 4264 ", "answer": "1875", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8782", "question": "-383245 + 394122 + -110041 ", "answer": "-99164", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8783", "question": "-641075 - 592283 - 328706 ", "answer": "-1562064", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8784", "question": "987 + 676 ", "answer": "1663", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8785", "question": "763524 - 638455 + -381506 + -300396 * 560890 ", "answer": "-168489368877", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8786", "question": "44568 - -89004 * -27698 * 48628 * -26207 ", "answer": "3141677868867161400", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8787", "question": "34 * -8 * -23 + 39 ", "answer": "6295", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8788", "question": "5909 + -6283 ", "answer": "-374", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8789", "question": "-61 - 10 - -59 ", "answer": "-12", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8790", "question": "-654 + 288 - 59 - 910 + -457 ", "answer": "-1792", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8791", "question": "-235 + 375 ", "answer": "140", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8792", "question": "-6045 - 2366 + -2303 - 5560 ", "answer": "-16274", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8793", "question": "24433 - -97139 * -33075 - -68768 - -25416 ", "answer": "-3212753808", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8794", "question": "-94810 - -20338 ", "answer": "-74472", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8795", "question": "-28226 - -88764 * 1248 * 81346 ", "answer": "9011304209086", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8796", "question": "8 * -71 ", "answer": "-568", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8797", "question": "288 + -147 * 145 + -270 * -479 ", "answer": "108303", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8798", "question": "8709 * 478 * 7245 ", "answer": "30160224990", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8799", "question": "-64 - 82 - -36 * 37 * -20 ", "answer": "-26786", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8800", "question": "740019 * 182751 * 390375 ", "answer": "52794007489510875", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8801", "question": "932 + -118 - -204 ", "answer": "1018", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8802", "question": "-1053 + 4085 + 3551 ", "answer": "6583", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8803", "question": "926 * -954 - -870 ", "answer": "-882534", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8804", "question": "-44474 - 33578 ", "answer": "-78052", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8805", "question": "877 * -567 * -261 - -197 ", "answer": "129784796", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8806", "question": "-445 - 618 * 401 ", "answer": "-248263", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8807", "question": "-59443 * -68348 ", "answer": "4062810164", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8808", "question": "-618 - 835 ", "answer": "-1453", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8809", "question": "-25 + -67 * 5 - 65 + 81 ", "answer": "-344", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8810", "question": "479167 * 827177 + 375333 + 132294 ", "answer": "396356429186", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8811", "question": "14 * 93 + 90 ", "answer": "1392", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8812", "question": "951 + 68 ", "answer": "1019", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8813", "question": "-7272 * 2796 + 2917 - -9280 ", "answer": "-20320315", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8814", "question": "-6889 + -1361 + -644 - -529 ", "answer": "-8365", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8815", "question": "-5131 - -3601 * 1777 * 6840 ", "answer": "43768997549", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8816", "question": "27 * -13 + 4 * -48 + 19 ", "answer": "-524", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8817", "question": "136144 + -948122 + -655308 - 450200 + 61190 ", "answer": "-1856296", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8818", "question": "65 + -94 - -96 * 69 * 41 ", "answer": "271555", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8819", "question": "986109 + -450410 ", "answer": "535699", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8820", "question": "216 - -806 * 487 - 794 * 498 ", "answer": "-2674", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8821", "question": "-68 - 35 + -59 ", "answer": "-162", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8822", "question": "-60193 + 58560 ", "answer": "-1633", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8823", "question": "6637 - -1416 - 350 ", "answer": "7703", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8824", "question": "220074 + 677096 * -164944 - 481441 ", "answer": "-111683183991", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8825", "question": "933 * 958 ", "answer": "893814", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8826", "question": "-283411 + -230345 * -3436 ", "answer": "791182009", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8827", "question": "-68 + -90 * 0 - 79 + -18 ", "answer": "-165", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8828", "question": "-8464 + -649 + -1405 + 4867 ", "answer": "-5651", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8829", "question": "-8835 * -4697 + -5275 ", "answer": "41492720", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8830", "question": "-37107 - -725024 - -407556 + 97257 - 602199 ", "answer": "590531", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8831", "question": "-41 * 48 + 11 - 24 + 93 ", "answer": "-1888", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8832", "question": "-2823 - 8676 * -1763 ", "answer": "15292965", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8833", "question": "87893 + -19627 - 34206 ", "answer": "34060", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8834", "question": "-25221 * 42766 - 70627 ", "answer": "-1078671913", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8835", "question": "745 * 878 + 118 - 930 ", "answer": "653298", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8836", "question": "-291 - -574 ", "answer": "283", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8837", "question": "-69 + 24 * -11 * -89 * -99 ", "answer": "-2326173", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8838", "question": "761 + 205 ", "answer": "966", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8839", "question": "-42220 + -49791 * 86379 + 7294 ", "answer": "-4300931715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8840", "question": "-5844 + -6446 - -4864 ", "answer": "-7426", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8841", "question": "125562 - -865168 + -733039 + -43209 ", "answer": "214482", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8842", "question": "-3341 * -313 - 1436 ", "answer": "1044297", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8843", "question": "294203 * -254825 * 428628 ", "answer": "-32134360950810300", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8844", "question": "-556 - -907 ", "answer": "351", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8845", "question": "-705252 * 977450 - -49846 * 982435 + -268558 ", "answer": "-640378380948", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8846", "question": "686944 - -495477 - -724275 - 143935 + -496646 ", "answer": "1266115", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8847", "question": "1677 * 8727 ", "answer": "14635179", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8848", "question": "-481718 * 670544 ", "answer": "-323013114592", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8849", "question": "945 - -946 * -140 ", "answer": "-131495", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8850", "question": "-8565 * 6351 * 4942 * 9989 * 1461 ", "answer": "-3923236149237820170", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8851", "question": "42 - -79 - 57 - 17 * -93 ", "answer": "1645", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8852", "question": "-8671 + -7773 - -1549 - -7585 ", "answer": "-7310", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8853", "question": "-9094 + -4653 + 579 + -6466 - -1197 ", "answer": "-18437", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8854", "question": "-8068 - -32890 + 51331 ", "answer": "76153", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8855", "question": "375 - -131 + 208 - -544 * 173 ", "answer": "94826", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8856", "question": "923 + -620 + -424 - 213 + -803 ", "answer": "-1137", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8857", "question": "-60762 * -42806 * -62303 ", "answer": "-162048743050116", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8858", "question": "84 - 13 * -94 ", "answer": "1306", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8859", "question": "-68 + 99 - 58 ", "answer": "-27", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8860", "question": "-37824 - -91327 + 53500 * 24012 - -20434 ", "answer": "1284715937", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8861", "question": "-35471 - 62286 + -46770 ", "answer": "-144527", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8862", "question": "-113 + 922 * 388 + 374 ", "answer": "357997", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8863", "question": "575927 * -160386 + -498642 ", "answer": "-92371126464", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8864", "question": "-34515 - 27524 - -86190 - -32751 ", "answer": "56902", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8865", "question": "-12 + 61 + 3 ", "answer": "52", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8866", "question": "-675410 + -63619 * -504519 - -708777 ", "answer": "32097027628", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8867", "question": "941 - 70 + -452 - 801 * -52 ", "answer": "42071", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8868", "question": "-32 * -75 ", "answer": "2400", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8869", "question": "-98646 - -96610 * -88454 - -3202 ", "answer": "-8545636384", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8870", "question": "-482 * -322 ", "answer": "155204", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8871", "question": "32 + 23 * 68 ", "answer": "1596", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8872", "question": "-3190 + -8197 - -4662 + 9400 ", "answer": "2675", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8873", "question": "4288 * -8491 * -2246 + 2097 * -7555 ", "answer": "81759687533", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8874", "question": "-511 * 628 - -240 + 897 ", "answer": "-319771", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8875", "question": "598075 + -348639 * 387328 - -420394 * 674019 ", "answer": "148316494969", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8876", "question": "597281 - 719591 * 508628 + -969881 ", "answer": "-366004503748", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8877", "question": "664 - 223 + -364 + -356 ", "answer": "-279", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8878", "question": "-663701 + 20420 ", "answer": "-643281", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8879", "question": "30404 * 674153 ", "answer": "20496947812", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8880", "question": "-169 - 328 - 493 ", "answer": "-990", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8881", "question": "-286516 - 144521 * -314725 + 703803 + 508050 ", "answer": "45485297062", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8882", "question": "-154 * -81 - 379 ", "answer": "12095", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8883", "question": "459338 * 645082 - 383681 ", "answer": "296310292035", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8884", "question": "-86675 + 4973 - 34167 ", "answer": "-115869", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8885", "question": "-22 - -98 + -86 * 93 + -63 ", "answer": "-7985", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8886", "question": "-4828 + 3718 - -992 * -4387 * -9198 ", "answer": "40028811882", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8887", "question": "-688746 + -965891 * 244948 * 436802 ", "answer": "-103344325581008482", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8888", "question": "31643 + 14299 + 28815 + 48623 + 88943 ", "answer": "212323", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8889", "question": "-94577 - 54158 * 1606 * 23534 ", "answer": "-2046934416009", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8890", "question": "42 + -45 + 72 - -36 - 44 ", "answer": "61", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8891", "question": "-455 - 750 * 596 + -950 - 750 ", "answer": "-449155", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8892", "question": "-24 * 53 + 61 * 99 ", "answer": "4767", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8893", "question": "46938 - 61413 + -69215 * 39107 * -76290 ", "answer": "206501085756975", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8894", "question": "-63339 - 53635 + 8436 ", "answer": "-108538", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8895", "question": "58684 - 5650 ", "answer": "53034", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8896", "question": "37 * -34 * 29 ", "answer": "-36482", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8897", "question": "911422 + 335860 - -559637 + -363686 - 689013 ", "answer": "754220", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8898", "question": "-30 + -6 * -6 - -53 - -98 ", "answer": "157", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8899", "question": "-633470 + -196055 - -907527 * 106896 ", "answer": "97010176667", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8900", "question": "-956 - 306 ", "answer": "-1262", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8901", "question": "22 + -85 - 7 + 68 ", "answer": "-2", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8902", "question": "-349 - 26383 * 61851 * 23886 ", "answer": "-38977531489987", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8903", "question": "-58030 + -911457 * -358746 + 723100 + 258772 ", "answer": "326982476764", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8904", "question": "-6057 * -1466 ", "answer": "8879562", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8905", "question": "648 - -176 * -127 * -918 ", "answer": "20519784", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8906", "question": "-36 + -84 + -17 * -46 - -8 ", "answer": "670", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8907", "question": "-7953 + 2403 - 1625 - 1327 - 9755 ", "answer": "-18257", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8908", "question": "-53563 * -57407 - 12348 - -85334 - -45777 ", "answer": "3075009904", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8909", "question": "-1355 + 7627 ", "answer": "6272", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8910", "question": "9879 - -8360 * -880 * -1628 ", "answer": "11976880279", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8911", "question": "-61090 - 22577 - -76863 ", "answer": "-6804", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8912", "question": "47851 - -41855 * 76454 * 38147 * -14964 ", "answer": "-1826651287670598509", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8913", "question": "-6 + 24 ", "answer": "18", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8914", "question": "3374 - -7650 * -9542 ", "answer": "-72992926", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8915", "question": "92110 * 53134 + 17252 - 26846 + 59838 ", "answer": "4894222984", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8916", "question": "116 + -185 * 11 - -525 * -104 ", "answer": "-56519", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8917", "question": "-3489 * 8326 + -6522 * -2250 ", "answer": "-14374914", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8918", "question": "-2464 * 1650 + -1556 * -2268 + -2158 ", "answer": "-538750", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8919", "question": "-52886 + 22247 ", "answer": "-30639", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8920", "question": "7488 + 5343 ", "answer": "12831", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8921", "question": "-79960 + -8012 + 72089 - 59524 - 58474 ", "answer": "-133881", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8922", "question": "82 - 0 - 93 + 68 + 76 ", "answer": "133", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8923", "question": "27 + 18 - 46 - 25 ", "answer": "-26", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8924", "question": "-32 + -95 + 93 ", "answer": "-34", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8925", "question": "701095 - 436726 * -339217 * -892260 * 186823 ", "answer": "-24694965434156893608065", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8926", "question": "100 * 835 ", "answer": "83500", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8927", "question": "-96461 + -885516 + -58284 ", "answer": "-1040261", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8928", "question": "-98 + -48 - 7 ", "answer": "-153", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8929", "question": "-61980 - -73100 * 9198 ", "answer": "672311820", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8930", "question": "-67501 * -8367 ", "answer": "564780867", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8931", "question": "81 + -98 ", "answer": "-17", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8932", "question": "-8956 - -5109 * 9565 + 6881 * 3171 ", "answer": "70678280", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8933", "question": "816 * -636 * 199 ", "answer": "-103276224", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8934", "question": "620 * 286 + 899 ", "answer": "178219", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8935", "question": "-1746 + -7086 ", "answer": "-8832", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8936", "question": "89531 - -45268 * -19629 * 86707 * -27990 ", "answer": "2156485492888887491", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8937", "question": "592064 * -140474 - -438938 + 547570 ", "answer": "-83168611828", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8938", "question": "-967945 * -122564 - -690659 + 598864 - 163918 ", "answer": "118636336585", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8939", "question": "-868 - 777 * 878 - -74 + 432 ", "answer": "-682568", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8940", "question": "-817 - 621 + 500 ", "answer": "-938", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8941", "question": "1004 * -4821 * -7283 * -9207 - 3379 ", "answer": "-324563215544383", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8942", "question": "24732 - 64341 * 71457 * -51319 + -71391 ", "answer": "235944995773344", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8943", "question": "486 - 353 * 337 * 679 + -860 ", "answer": "-80774893", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8944", "question": "-47515 * -91045 - 41061 - 62877 + 62184 ", "answer": "4325961421", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8945", "question": "50 + -62 - -26 - 15 + -39 ", "answer": "-40", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8946", "question": "-904553 - -926273 * -103756 + -904201 - 952724 ", "answer": "-96109142866", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8947", "question": "-8486 * 74219 * 78633 ", "answer": "-49524827452722", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8948", "question": "-87 * -47 * -91 + 99 * -10 ", "answer": "-373089", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8949", "question": "855 - -744 + -314 * 189 ", "answer": "-57747", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8950", "question": "-649 * -806 - -837 - 152 ", "answer": "523779", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8951", "question": "-68674 - -26610 + -52205 - 4161 ", "answer": "-98430", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8952", "question": "328 - -8250 + 7834 + -2818 - 9268 ", "answer": "4326", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8953", "question": "3 * -567 + -819 ", "answer": "-2520", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8954", "question": "65612 * 20226 + 71875 ", "answer": "1327140187", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8955", "question": "-59964 * -65974 + 76479 + 91519 ", "answer": "3956232934", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8956", "question": "-57 * 27 ", "answer": "-1539", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8957", "question": "-338123 + 66314 * -194468 * -758514 - 405675 ", "answer": "9781759339661530", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8958", "question": "-46 - -80 - -83 + 5 ", "answer": "122", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8959", "question": "-68 - 11 + 72 - 48 - -21 ", "answer": "-34", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8960", "question": "-9555 * -4118 * -4638 + -32 ", "answer": "-182493658652", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8961", "question": "27 + 67 + -54 * -69 ", "answer": "3820", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8962", "question": "-20 - -12 - -21 - -22 - 9 ", "answer": "26", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8963", "question": "956193 - 544263 ", "answer": "411930", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8964", "question": "39600 + -35378 * 30606 + -22481 + -30356 ", "answer": "-1082792305", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8965", "question": "-577 * 752 - -681 ", "answer": "-433223", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8966", "question": "-228750 - 443232 * 293733 * -343043 ", "answer": "44661407964176658", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8967", "question": "6372 - 5307 * 8409 ", "answer": "-44620191", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8968", "question": "-72778 + -227476 * -392520 ", "answer": "89288806742", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8969", "question": "-670 * 519 - 806 ", "answer": "-348536", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8970", "question": "-358695 * 825754 - 981696 - 473906 ", "answer": "-296195286632", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8971", "question": "49560 - -974 * -25192 + 13732 - -62737 ", "answer": "-24410979", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8972", "question": "-682373 - 770655 * -455379 - 447109 ", "answer": "350938973763", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8973", "question": "-3 + 34 * -28 - 87 * 31 ", "answer": "-3652", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8974", "question": "856227 + 809323 ", "answer": "1665550", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8975", "question": "-90 * -35 + -14 ", "answer": "3136", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8976", "question": "-1100 + -425793 * 843219 ", "answer": "-359036748767", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8977", "question": "-3476 - 3762 * -7550 ", "answer": "28399624", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8978", "question": "-734563 * 576951 + 508020 ", "answer": "-423806349393", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8979", "question": "2221 + 9536 + 6117 - 3019 ", "answer": "14855", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8980", "question": "-67 + -85 * -15 * 1 - 97 ", "answer": "1111", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8981", "question": "-3215 + 8951 ", "answer": "5736", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8982", "question": "-472476 * -618395 - 861817 * 224805 ", "answer": "98436025335", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8983", "question": "1562 + 2456 * -8186 + -3997 ", "answer": "-20107251", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8984", "question": "88 * 60 + 33 ", "answer": "5313", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8985", "question": "-4315 + -6377 ", "answer": "-10692", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8986", "question": "-80740 - 64124 - 17441 * -49321 ", "answer": "860062697", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8987", "question": "-259256 - 801054 * -348402 * -653542 * 548873 ", "answer": "-100112383949320296730784", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8988", "question": "-839583 - -371973 - 680612 + -30436 - 679181 ", "answer": "-1857839", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8989", "question": "46599 - -77835 + 65002 + 4346 ", "answer": "193782", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8990", "question": "-561 + 555 - -451 ", "answer": "445", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "8991", "question": "8915 + -1528 ", "answer": "7387", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8992", "question": "-4906 + -2826 ", "answer": "-7732", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8993", "question": "79099 + -27194 ", "answer": "51905", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8994", "question": "70 + -81 + 85 ", "answer": "74", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "8995", "question": "-25558 * 55255 + -9123 - 27232 + -93561 ", "answer": "-1412337206", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8996", "question": "-823549 - -915542 * -329742 ", "answer": "-301893473713", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "8997", "question": "89309 * -71917 - -7800 * -64190 * -3380 ", "answer": "1685882324647", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "8998", "question": "-5917 + 6303 - -2664 + 2175 - -9412 ", "answer": "14637", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "8999", "question": "-65967 + 49015 * -19743 ", "answer": "-967769112", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9000", "question": "9 + -83 - 81 ", "answer": "-155", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9001", "question": "849 + 152 * -609 * 641 ", "answer": "-59335239", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9002", "question": "-34 + -15 + 26 + -46 * 0 ", "answer": "-23", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9003", "question": "573908 + -224567 + 16232 - 751177 - -358731 ", "answer": "-26873", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9004", "question": "-18 - -10 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9005", "question": "884 + -483 + 111 - -884 ", "answer": "1396", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9006", "question": "3016 * 5420 * -6673 - 6436 + -3661 ", "answer": "-109081672657", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9007", "question": "-48 - -49 ", "answer": "1", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9008", "question": "-984337 + -848580 ", "answer": "-1832917", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9009", "question": "120 - -206 + -610 - -693 ", "answer": "409", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9010", "question": "-680144 - -315961 ", "answer": "-364183", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9011", "question": "-45646 + 73661 ", "answer": "28015", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9012", "question": "646971 - -302413 + 587753 * -942894 * 803791 ", "answer": "-445451951398947578", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9013", "question": "-384761 * -657411 - 882878 ", "answer": "252945230893", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9014", "question": "93 * -45 + -74 - -86 ", "answer": "-4173", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9015", "question": "346682 - 204616 * 781492 ", "answer": "-159905420390", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9016", "question": "278 - -801 ", "answer": "1079", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9017", "question": "98021 * 79705 + -61498 * 29883 + -8715 ", "answer": "5975010356", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9018", "question": "-861190 * -107427 ", "answer": "92515058130", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9019", "question": "-3255 - -5708 ", "answer": "2453", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9020", "question": "-34 - 88 ", "answer": "-122", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9021", "question": "-671182 + 45408 * 775230 ", "answer": "35200972658", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9022", "question": "-390 - -934 ", "answer": "544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9023", "question": "12 + 150 + -610 * -847 - -974 ", "answer": "517806", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9024", "question": "-446 * 152 + 2096 ", "answer": "-65696", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9025", "question": "-365874 - -732066 + -2357 - 69430 ", "answer": "294405", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9026", "question": "-32 + -13 - -94 + -25 - 28 ", "answer": "-4", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9027", "question": "1929 * -1384 + 9785 - -7398 - -2227 ", "answer": "-2650326", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9028", "question": "-93 - -71 * -57 * 73 ", "answer": "-295524", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9029", "question": "847 * 893 * 854 + 714 - 611 ", "answer": "645940937", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9030", "question": "76 + -11 + -52 + -54 - -68 ", "answer": "27", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9031", "question": "-15180 - 76395 - 73426 - 84849 * 44508 ", "answer": "-3776624293", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9032", "question": "-105271 * -647900 - 574624 + 473498 - -802745 ", "answer": "68205782519", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9033", "question": "-68 + -1 * 42 - -41 - -9 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9034", "question": "371 * -4 + 230 + 825 + -71 ", "answer": "-500", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9035", "question": "8791 - -5052 - 3500 ", "answer": "10343", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9036", "question": "702650 - -728244 + 668512 * -265440 * 717428 ", "answer": "-127307473249548946", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9037", "question": "205217 * -754061 * 198228 + 721825 ", "answer": "-30675017093266211", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9038", "question": "12897 + 25114 ", "answer": "38011", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9039", "question": "-719 * 700 ", "answer": "-503300", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9040", "question": "3133 + -5190 * -711 * -5326 ", "answer": "-19653416207", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9041", "question": "-593727 * 920827 - 77664 ", "answer": "-546719929893", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9042", "question": "8162 - 6922 - -7618 - -7107 ", "answer": "15965", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9043", "question": "-69247 - 46985 ", "answer": "-116232", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9044", "question": "-357 - 477 - 259 - 544 ", "answer": "-1637", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9045", "question": "-485474 * -311738 ", "answer": "151340693812", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9046", "question": "-74 + 18 - -97 + 94 - -1 ", "answer": "136", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9047", "question": "19867 - 77219 ", "answer": "-57352", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9048", "question": "-2098 * 7679 - -6195 ", "answer": "-16104347", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9049", "question": "-8213 - 3668 + -483 ", "answer": "-12364", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9050", "question": "-509675 - -552771 * -512433 + 610796 - 388433 ", "answer": "-283258389155", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9051", "question": "25 * -9 + -35 + -80 ", "answer": "-340", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9052", "question": "82803 - 85535 - 12984 - 97270 ", "answer": "-112986", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9053", "question": "278250 + 561717 - -963905 ", "answer": "1803872", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9054", "question": "21370 - -17780 + 98993 ", "answer": "138143", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9055", "question": "6625 - 8312 - -7142 ", "answer": "5455", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9056", "question": "-68 - -75 ", "answer": "7", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9057", "question": "-6664 + -501 - -847 - 8619 * 9169 ", "answer": "-79033929", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9058", "question": "986 * 235 + 444 ", "answer": "232154", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9059", "question": "-265728 * -688602 + -642733 * -985375 - -921809 ", "answer": "816314783940", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9060", "question": "-74468 - -60321 * -70085 ", "answer": "-4227671753", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9061", "question": "264 - -92 - -480 ", "answer": "836", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9062", "question": "79641 * -18860 * 12689 + -68068 ", "answer": "-19059249348208", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9063", "question": "3060 - -5565 * -9523 + -7347 + -9490 ", "answer": "-53009272", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9064", "question": "-18253 - 72692 * 35383 ", "answer": "-2572079289", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9065", "question": "593567 + 281781 + -654532 * 504622 - 547100 ", "answer": "-330290918656", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9066", "question": "910 * -582 * -169 - 237 + 357 ", "answer": "89505900", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9067", "question": "-365803 + -710578 ", "answer": "-1076381", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9068", "question": "-657679 + -717656 + -651989 - -158200 - -614839 ", "answer": "-1254285", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9069", "question": "333112 * -379014 ", "answer": "-126254111568", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9070", "question": "248 - 7215 ", "answer": "-6967", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9071", "question": "76 * -24 ", "answer": "-1824", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9072", "question": "32 - -51 * 76 + 100 ", "answer": "4008", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9073", "question": "545819 + 571039 + 999969 - 953114 ", "answer": "1163713", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9074", "question": "-673073 - 862304 * -662509 ", "answer": "571283487663", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9075", "question": "-44 * 262 ", "answer": "-11528", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9076", "question": "-8245 * -591 + 1637 + -4752 ", "answer": "4869680", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9077", "question": "733 - -218 ", "answer": "951", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9078", "question": "-6483 - 7163 - 8185 + 7500 + 435 ", "answer": "-13896", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9079", "question": "-4104 * -3694 - -1345 ", "answer": "15161521", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9080", "question": "12 * -11 - -100 - -56 ", "answer": "24", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9081", "question": "-56384 + 67165 + -66994 ", "answer": "-56213", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9082", "question": "-268 + -41 ", "answer": "-309", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9083", "question": "544 + 857 - -773 * -474 + 106 ", "answer": "-364895", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9084", "question": "30234 * -48478 - 67151 + 85702 * 16907 ", "answer": "-16787289", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9085", "question": "42606 + 95246 + -82647 * -820 - -19370 ", "answer": "67927762", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9086", "question": "-295 + 770 - 242 + -24 ", "answer": "209", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9087", "question": "224 - 7390 + -156 * -4879 ", "answer": "753958", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9088", "question": "-591 + -927 * -516 + 45 + -919 ", "answer": "476867", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9089", "question": "204177 * 389777 - -164894 ", "answer": "79583663423", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9090", "question": "-10 + 56 ", "answer": "46", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9091", "question": "57 + 55 + -60 + -74 ", "answer": "-22", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9092", "question": "93 * -59 ", "answer": "-5487", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9093", "question": "94 + 71 - 86 ", "answer": "79", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9094", "question": "5362 * 9758 ", "answer": "52322396", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9095", "question": "-412 * 537 * 718 ", "answer": "-158853192", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9096", "question": "910 * -927 - 787 * -886 + 93 ", "answer": "-146195", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9097", "question": "-502 + -216 + 906 - -398 ", "answer": "586", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9098", "question": "-12286 - -52419 - -32855 ", "answer": "72988", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9099", "question": "88581 - -20779 * 62789 ", "answer": "1304781212", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9100", "question": "4 - -19 * 26 * 49 ", "answer": "24210", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9101", "question": "-387 - 78 ", "answer": "-465", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9102", "question": "360213 * 856885 ", "answer": "308661116505", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9103", "question": "16 - 283 + 139 * -844 ", "answer": "-117583", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9104", "question": "-333 * 927 + -57 * -523 + 540 ", "answer": "-278340", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9105", "question": "-791347 - -384463 - 585158 * -745719 + 850007 ", "answer": "436363881725", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9106", "question": "-192 + 805 - 99 + -126 + 28 ", "answer": "416", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9107", "question": "-1 - 3 ", "answer": "-4", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 1}
{"id": "9108", "question": "384 - 817 + -727 + 690 * -241 ", "answer": "-167450", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9109", "question": "-377691 - -244072 - -455041 + -163247 ", "answer": "158175", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9110", "question": "7776 * -8882 + 1184 ", "answer": "-69065248", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9111", "question": "-84 + -67 + 0 ", "answer": "-151", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9112", "question": "-55019 * 33350 - -2978 ", "answer": "-1834880672", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9113", "question": "77570 + -81522 + -30855 ", "answer": "-34807", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9114", "question": "1351 * -1944 - 6007 - -2381 ", "answer": "-2629970", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9115", "question": "8710 - -13817 ", "answer": "22527", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9116", "question": "57925 * 51233 - 55369 - 50591 - -4888 ", "answer": "2967570453", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9117", "question": "726885 + 272381 * -377924 * 850983 ", "answer": "-87599608835327367", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9118", "question": "950880 * 254256 - 340905 ", "answer": "241766604375", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9119", "question": "87353 + -43749 + 35798 ", "answer": "79402", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9120", "question": "-48860 - 71234 - -92559 + 68779 ", "answer": "41244", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9121", "question": "113 + -206 * 894 + -7 * -333 ", "answer": "-181720", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9122", "question": "-93236 - 71697 ", "answer": "-164933", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9123", "question": "5593 - 8315 ", "answer": "-2722", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9124", "question": "-65568 + 31534 * -92233 + -37016 ", "answer": "-2908578006", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9125", "question": "68867 - 42575 ", "answer": "26292", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9126", "question": "-3124 + -7050 - -3415 ", "answer": "-6759", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9127", "question": "6 * 77 + -30 - 62 ", "answer": "370", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9128", "question": "4678 + -2068 - -3454 * 7435 - 8508 ", "answer": "25674592", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9129", "question": "-6462 * 8995 + -1623 + -5646 ", "answer": "-58132959", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9130", "question": "-29 - 46 * -62 - 40 ", "answer": "2783", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9131", "question": "6839 + 3098 - -8917 - 7949 + -8837 ", "answer": "2068", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9132", "question": "-54004 * -69185 + -26259 ", "answer": "3736240481", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9133", "question": "540 - 680 - 825 ", "answer": "-965", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9134", "question": "43953 - -91396 + 9153 * -99733 - 8137 ", "answer": "-912728937", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9135", "question": "6220 + -4568 + 2258 + -3763 ", "answer": "147", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9136", "question": "-6075 - -930 + 3024 + 5961 ", "answer": "3840", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9137", "question": "-577 * 474 * 741 ", "answer": "-202662018", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9138", "question": "119 * 190 * -452 - -656 * 904 ", "answer": "-9626696", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9139", "question": "-29821 - 15735 + -56562 + -10155 + 45297 ", "answer": "-66976", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9140", "question": "-1467 + 8014 * -1570 - 9292 ", "answer": "-12592739", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9141", "question": "9925 * -80865 ", "answer": "-802585125", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9142", "question": "85 + -44 * -28 + -16 ", "answer": "1301", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9143", "question": "-4507 - 1018 - 8839 + 5244 ", "answer": "-9120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9144", "question": "-652 * -161 ", "answer": "104972", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9145", "question": "-24 + -28 + -8 + -34 * -82 ", "answer": "2728", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9146", "question": "4878 * 9523 ", "answer": "46453194", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9147", "question": "-5651 + -3285 * 4606 ", "answer": "-15136361", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9148", "question": "-596 + -243 - -385 ", "answer": "-454", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9149", "question": "-743009 + 395705 * -380588 * 759301 ", "answer": "-114351166849539549", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9150", "question": "-1978 - -930 - -9046 + 8671 * 9147 ", "answer": "79321635", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9151", "question": "-69639 + 72195 + 7327 ", "answer": "9883", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9152", "question": "72775 * 42272 + 2040 * 52058 ", "answer": "3182543120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9153", "question": "-59048 + 462370 * -224572 * -479337 ", "answer": "49772127866351632", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9154", "question": "-304359 + -953381 * 484700 * -632451 + 517714 ", "answer": "292257991883199055", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9155", "question": "2231 * 1203 + 236 * -5698 ", "answer": "1339165", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9156", "question": "-100 + -7 - -39 - -83 + -40 ", "answer": "-25", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9157", "question": "-34 - -30 ", "answer": "-4", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9158", "question": "-724 - -588 ", "answer": "-136", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9159", "question": "-56347 + 44356 * 59706 ", "answer": "2648262989", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9160", "question": "241 - -991 + -384 ", "answer": "848", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9161", "question": "86707 + -96166 * -1787 + -56260 ", "answer": "171879089", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9162", "question": "-94 - -21 - 76 - 82 - -10 ", "answer": "-221", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9163", "question": "-978979 - 703891 ", "answer": "-1682870", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9164", "question": "888 * 328 ", "answer": "291264", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9165", "question": "-140 + 673 ", "answer": "533", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9166", "question": "-31 * 73 ", "answer": "-2263", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9167", "question": "-903315 - 494013 + -104396 ", "answer": "-1501724", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9168", "question": "-610 + -192 + -461 + 410 ", "answer": "-853", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9169", "question": "-84 + -73 * 21 + -71 ", "answer": "-1688", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9170", "question": "12892 - -95706 + 72220 - -73868 ", "answer": "254686", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9171", "question": "-29 + -31 * -30 ", "answer": "901", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9172", "question": "37 + 23 * -73 + -91 * -30 ", "answer": "1088", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9173", "question": "946 * -416 ", "answer": "-393536", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9174", "question": "-37 + 26 * -28 ", "answer": "-765", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9175", "question": "64 * -71 ", "answer": "-4544", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9176", "question": "-4524 - 3023 - 1635 * 1035 ", "answer": "-1699772", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9177", "question": "-1515 + 6434 - -8012 ", "answer": "12931", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9178", "question": "388 - -631 + -772 * -57 ", "answer": "45023", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9179", "question": "46878 + -2554 ", "answer": "44324", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9180", "question": "-6978 - -3856 + 2991 * 3341 ", "answer": "9989809", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9181", "question": "-914 + 344 - -884 - -771 * -123 ", "answer": "-94519", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9182", "question": "799292 + -110945 * 357603 - -164388 ", "answer": "-39673301155", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9183", "question": "-45950 - -50515 + -5594 - 99996 ", "answer": "-101025", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9184", "question": "-97 + -51 - 28 - -75 ", "answer": "-101", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9185", "question": "-91 * 56 ", "answer": "-5096", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9186", "question": "66 + 95 + 95 * -40 - -73 ", "answer": "-3566", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9187", "question": "6919 + 5118 + 6105 - 1045 ", "answer": "17097", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9188", "question": "239713 + 568053 * 834458 ", "answer": "474016609987", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9189", "question": "-67 + 10 - -73 ", "answer": "16", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9190", "question": "-6203 + -7137 - -474 ", "answer": "-12866", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9191", "question": "-51 - -3 ", "answer": "-48", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9192", "question": "-917 * 348 + -724 * 490 + 837 ", "answer": "-673039", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9193", "question": "2861 + 3559 * -9667 - 8602 * -799 ", "answer": "-27528994", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9194", "question": "-3681 - 1273 * -1798 ", "answer": "2285173", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9195", "question": "-19 + 15 ", "answer": "-4", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9196", "question": "-617 - -152 - -21 ", "answer": "-444", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9197", "question": "-547 + -60 + -702 + -798 ", "answer": "-2107", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9198", "question": "-43057 - -1339 * -38514 * 25165 ", "answer": "-1297765283647", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9199", "question": "-9943 + -2372 * -3199 * -2964 ", "answer": "-22490924935", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9200", "question": "19803 + 80441 ", "answer": "100244", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9201", "question": "115525 - -699905 - -210708 * 183159 - 779610 ", "answer": "38593102392", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9202", "question": "-826167 - 509709 ", "answer": "-1335876", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9203", "question": "-545979 * 991520 ", "answer": "-541349098080", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9204", "question": "918813 + 699836 ", "answer": "1618649", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9205", "question": "-94 + -81 * -85 ", "answer": "6791", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9206", "question": "8765 * 9832 - -5997 ", "answer": "86183477", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9207", "question": "-1522 * -42676 + 853238 + 96854 + -684818 ", "answer": "65218146", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9208", "question": "-6574 - -1253 + 4190 - 9766 - 6947 ", "answer": "-17844", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9209", "question": "-832168 - 455703 + 608602 - 747386 ", "answer": "-1426655", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9210", "question": "239748 + 96793 + -849140 * 224932 ", "answer": "-190998421939", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9211", "question": "-7796 * 3120 * 4632 - 2590 ", "answer": "-112666547230", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9212", "question": "240863 - 421446 * -992777 + -708394 ", "answer": "418401428011", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9213", "question": "98 + 71 * -2 ", "answer": "-44", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9214", "question": "572434 + 869184 * 316466 ", "answer": "275067756178", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9215", "question": "-8830 * 1243 + 960 ", "answer": "-10974730", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9216", "question": "-322 + 10 ", "answer": "-312", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9217", "question": "892 - 684 - 902 ", "answer": "-694", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9218", "question": "40 + 0 * -85 + 0 + -30 ", "answer": "10", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9219", "question": "-5375 * 8690 - -8859 + -5913 ", "answer": "-46705804", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9220", "question": "1857 * -9698 ", "answer": "-18009186", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9221", "question": "-834 - 377 ", "answer": "-1211", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9222", "question": "-76093 - 57781 - 60850 ", "answer": "-194724", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9223", "question": "-386707 + 425154 - -641241 - -591799 ", "answer": "1271487", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9224", "question": "-9974 - 1940 ", "answer": "-11914", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9225", "question": "-6 - 0 - -88 + 77 ", "answer": "159", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9226", "question": "-292328 * 98110 + -506978 ", "answer": "-28680807058", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9227", "question": "763516 - -77848 ", "answer": "841364", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9228", "question": "37262 - 42783 - -25541 + -91492 * 92419 ", "answer": "-8455579128", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9229", "question": "-524228 - -985929 - 473650 - -716538 ", "answer": "704589", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9230", "question": "-8398 * -3263 * 3064 - 7213 - -1091 ", "answer": "83961787014", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9231", "question": "-92 * 59 * -19 ", "answer": "103132", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9232", "question": "-50545 * -63473 + 73540 ", "answer": "3208316325", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9233", "question": "-245549 * 501558 ", "answer": "-123157065342", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9234", "question": "60 + 22 * -53 ", "answer": "-1106", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9235", "question": "-32 * -12 * -13 * 5 ", "answer": "-24960", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9236", "question": "-2269 - -1025 * 2714 + 2792 ", "answer": "2782373", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9237", "question": "-255962 - 858501 ", "answer": "-1114463", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9238", "question": "147640 + 449027 - 66248 * -213146 ", "answer": "14121092875", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9239", "question": "-9303 - 4446 * -9604 - 5806 ", "answer": "42684275", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9240", "question": "871 - -731 * 705 + 328 ", "answer": "516554", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9241", "question": "802 * -2834 - 3670 + -6408 ", "answer": "-2282946", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9242", "question": "-6445 + 4162 + 3614 + -2384 * 2045 ", "answer": "-4873949", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9243", "question": "9 * 57 - -100 ", "answer": "613", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9244", "question": "-29 * 71 * 18 ", "answer": "-37062", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9245", "question": "-227370 + -720733 ", "answer": "-948103", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9246", "question": "-2829 + -6787 ", "answer": "-9616", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9247", "question": "-21 * 59 - 39 ", "answer": "-1278", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9248", "question": "-15421 * 9034 + 15363 - 77670 - -23556 ", "answer": "-139352065", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9249", "question": "71041 - -25407 * -93174 * 18098 + 64642 ", "answer": "-42842885226481", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9250", "question": "-219 - 824 * 743 ", "answer": "-612451", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9251", "question": "685 + 948 - 536 ", "answer": "1097", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9252", "question": "12462 * -95924 - 16751 * -85042 + 86434 ", "answer": "229220088", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9253", "question": "-607 * 74 + -469 + 509 ", "answer": "-44878", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9254", "question": "-39 * -72 + -45 + -69 + 51 ", "answer": "2745", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9255", "question": "242 * 315 ", "answer": "76230", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9256", "question": "17 * -4 + 95 + -55 ", "answer": "-28", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9257", "question": "957 + 257 * 525 ", "answer": "135882", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9258", "question": "-934800 - -541860 ", "answer": "-392940", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9259", "question": "858041 - 621431 - -35076 ", "answer": "271686", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9260", "question": "-51 * -15 - -2 + 37 ", "answer": "804", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9261", "question": "58 * -60 + 96 - -53 ", "answer": "-3331", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9262", "question": "-990 * 600 ", "answer": "-594000", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9263", "question": "45648 - -58233 ", "answer": "103881", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9264", "question": "970 + 80670 + 60951 * -62235 ", "answer": "-3793203845", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9265", "question": "15 - -36 * -37 ", "answer": "-1317", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9266", "question": "820760 - -614631 * -869887 - 187597 ", "answer": "-534658883534", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9267", "question": "118936 - 621712 ", "answer": "-502776", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9268", "question": "301870 * -876772 - 843559 - 515323 ", "answer": "-264672522522", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9269", "question": "-836 + -259 ", "answer": "-1095", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9270", "question": "-79 * 11 + -92 ", "answer": "-961", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9271", "question": "-3420 + -6062 - -9142 ", "answer": "-340", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9272", "question": "260 + -218 * -888 * -710 ", "answer": "-137444380", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9273", "question": "-250495 - 896307 - 64417 + 609883 ", "answer": "-601336", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9274", "question": "-142 + -620 ", "answer": "-762", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9275", "question": "-47943 - -21746 - 30748 + 10336 - -48410 ", "answer": "1801", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9276", "question": "65629 * -81249 ", "answer": "-5332290621", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9277", "question": "352856 + -988171 - 70041 + 968651 - -699471 ", "answer": "962766", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9278", "question": "-15 + 22 ", "answer": "7", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9279", "question": "-335735 * -856447 + 703378 - -320687 ", "answer": "287540257610", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9280", "question": "-2625 + 1212 ", "answer": "-1413", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9281", "question": "78 - 11 * -33 + -53 * 12 ", "answer": "-195", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9282", "question": "644 * 185 + 342 + -464 + 85 ", "answer": "119103", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9283", "question": "-2046 - 2084 + 3807 - 6574 ", "answer": "-6897", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9284", "question": "128 * -112 ", "answer": "-14336", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9285", "question": "-6698 + 2623 - 1118 + 2493 * -7827 ", "answer": "-19517904", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9286", "question": "-10886 - -249076 - -870995 * 248878 * 56633 ", "answer": "12276419997853320", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9287", "question": "26 * 94 - -20 * -65 ", "answer": "1144", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9288", "question": "-99778 - 22008 - 98167 * -66716 - -12118 ", "answer": "6549199904", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9289", "question": "96 + -59 - 99 ", "answer": "-62", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9290", "question": "50 + -26 - 99 + 1 ", "answer": "-74", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9291", "question": "-752 + -753 ", "answer": "-1505", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9292", "question": "-47 - 15 - 78 - 37 ", "answer": "-177", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9293", "question": "-16 * 18 + 46 ", "answer": "-242", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9294", "question": "4968 * 5889 * 4130 ", "answer": "120829559760", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9295", "question": "-68 + 93 - -63 ", "answer": "88", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9296", "question": "-465185 * -623746 ", "answer": "290157283010", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9297", "question": "-71 + -461 ", "answer": "-532", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9298", "question": "-888186 + -599422 * -827594 + -244991 ", "answer": "496076917491", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9299", "question": "-48650 + -89055 * 42112 + -58208 ", "answer": "-3750391018", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9300", "question": "-87512 - -75686 * -67868 * -55008 ", "answer": "282557252812072", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9301", "question": "549479 + 224629 ", "answer": "774108", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9302", "question": "49432 - 21068 ", "answer": "28364", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9303", "question": "-68 + -28 + 23 * 67 ", "answer": "1445", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9304", "question": "100 + 18 - 69 * -78 ", "answer": "5500", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9305", "question": "-70 - 57 ", "answer": "-127", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9306", "question": "846514 - 954528 * 265513 * -144426 ", "answer": "36603266639822578", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9307", "question": "-62657 * -93629 * -28000 ", "answer": "-164262343084000", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9308", "question": "4619 * -2779 * -5812 ", "answer": "74604000212", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9309", "question": "-553 - -601 * 821 - -16 ", "answer": "492884", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9310", "question": "188118 * 477707 - -713963 + 216534 + 745603 ", "answer": "89866961526", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9311", "question": "-9237 - -5343 ", "answer": "-3894", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9312", "question": "51370 * -492 * -21024 + -58 ", "answer": "531361416902", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9313", "question": "-5 + 347 - -622 ", "answer": "964", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9314", "question": "13 - -68 + -45 ", "answer": "36", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9315", "question": "76794 * 83939 * 50523 + 82496 - -4856 ", "answer": "325671842436370", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9316", "question": "72 + -53 ", "answer": "19", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9317", "question": "-7841 + -4166 * -1329 + 9473 - -9274 ", "answer": "5547520", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9318", "question": "-33474 - -9819 ", "answer": "-23655", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9319", "question": "-92 * 99 + 29 ", "answer": "-9079", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9320", "question": "-1339 + 84455 * 67723 - -73628 ", "answer": "5719618254", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9321", "question": "64 - -62 - 22 * 31 ", "answer": "-556", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9322", "question": "-225375 + 573602 + 270338 ", "answer": "618565", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9323", "question": "1360 - -7322 + 4411 - 7195 ", "answer": "5898", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9324", "question": "-24 + -91 + 40 - 72 ", "answer": "-147", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9325", "question": "-211587 - 438233 + -366934 + -40809 + 576185 ", "answer": "-481378", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9326", "question": "125 - -558 * 170 ", "answer": "94985", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9327", "question": "-200 * -535 * -134 - 546 ", "answer": "-14338546", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9328", "question": "-7218 + 9810 + 438 * 8913 ", "answer": "3906486", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9329", "question": "-408994 + -222609 + -574222 * -151731 - 316514 ", "answer": "87126330165", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9330", "question": "-77 - -70 ", "answer": "-7", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9331", "question": "16875 - -29586 ", "answer": "46461", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9332", "question": "-67516 * 84048 - -39372 ", "answer": "-5674545396", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9333", "question": "10179 * 32635 * -86658 ", "answer": "-28787065305570", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9334", "question": "-560 * -413 + -842 ", "answer": "230438", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9335", "question": "50382 + -10166 + -57889 * 4660 - 35766 ", "answer": "-269758290", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9336", "question": "-50216 + 2045 + 17648 + -27799 ", "answer": "-58322", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9337", "question": "-5316 + -5670 + 1765 - -411 + -5825 ", "answer": "-14635", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9338", "question": "424868 + 285936 ", "answer": "710804", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9339", "question": "42051 * -35798 ", "answer": "-1505341698", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9340", "question": "3560 * 7389 + -7276 ", "answer": "26297564", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9341", "question": "-51 - -93 - -67 ", "answer": "109", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9342", "question": "-51 * -45 - -117 + 313 + -267 ", "answer": "2458", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9343", "question": "-8152 * 6199 ", "answer": "-50534248", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9344", "question": "-3065 + -28159 - 86651 ", "answer": "-117875", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9345", "question": "3954 * 142 * 7181 - -4533 ", "answer": "4031906241", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9346", "question": "651180 + 575097 - -407732 ", "answer": "1634009", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9347", "question": "3242 - 6847 ", "answer": "-3605", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9348", "question": "-599522 - 578613 - -132829 - -967773 ", "answer": "-77533", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9349", "question": "190811 - -304584 ", "answer": "495395", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9350", "question": "5151 * -20490 * -98110 ", "answer": "10354920858900", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9351", "question": "181697 * -891648 * -898201 ", "answer": "145517334420185856", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9352", "question": "-97 * -4 + -32 + 58 ", "answer": "414", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9353", "question": "18237 + -68165 - -31489 * -61935 ", "answer": "-1950321143", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9354", "question": "-94 * -85 + 34 + 72 ", "answer": "8096", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9355", "question": "-350043 * 878257 * -688187 - 97628 ", "answer": "211567756937704909", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9356", "question": "-3809 - -8142 + -290 * -2353 ", "answer": "686703", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9357", "question": "-626 + -134 ", "answer": "-760", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9358", "question": "-17691 - -37961 + -81945 + -5386 * 79503 ", "answer": "-428264833", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9359", "question": "-32 + 81 - 83 - -17 ", "answer": "-17", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9360", "question": "-395 + -154 ", "answer": "-549", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9361", "question": "-37 - -33 - -82 ", "answer": "78", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9362", "question": "956095 + 907385 + 99580 * 855937 ", "answer": "85236069940", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9363", "question": "302 - -58 - -144 ", "answer": "504", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9364", "question": "6368 * 71822 ", "answer": "457362496", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9365", "question": "490 + -492 ", "answer": "-2", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9366", "question": "196 * -855 ", "answer": "-167580", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9367", "question": "-376 - 30 + 744 + -556 + -15 ", "answer": "-233", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9368", "question": "-922787 * 36586 * -196108 + -995957 ", "answer": "6620818891875699", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9369", "question": "-23164 + 27886 - 33896 + 15586 * -90605 ", "answer": "-1412198704", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9370", "question": "69 + 568 + 187 * -523 - 336 ", "answer": "-97500", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9371", "question": "-4229 - -2523 ", "answer": "-1706", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9372", "question": "-633 + -9992 ", "answer": "-10625", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9373", "question": "9228 + 22493 * -34093 * -71719 ", "answer": "54997991205659", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9374", "question": "54437 - 46559 - -71892 + -1728 * -54864 ", "answer": "94884762", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9375", "question": "54098 * 79441 + -74337 + -57849 * -89233 ", "answer": "9459564698", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9376", "question": "-67339 - -92253 - -29198 + -61997 ", "answer": "-7885", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9377", "question": "-88 + 80 ", "answer": "-8", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9378", "question": "206887 * -994183 * 329958 - 606375 ", "answer": "-67866928937926893", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9379", "question": "895038 * -888261 + 141653 * 197054 ", "answer": "-767114058656", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9380", "question": "66 - 34 + 42 * 88 + -61 ", "answer": "3667", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9381", "question": "-3488 - 5046 ", "answer": "-8534", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9382", "question": "-59 - 7 - -46 + 75 * -77 ", "answer": "-5795", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9383", "question": "217 * -460 + -553 * -988 ", "answer": "446544", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9384", "question": "-26928 - -39996 + 80305 - 41204 ", "answer": "52169", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9385", "question": "94 + 18 ", "answer": "112", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9386", "question": "-673642 + 557797 - 609108 * 884406 + 997933 ", "answer": "-538697887760", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9387", "question": "-757 + 321 + -328 - -416 ", "answer": "-348", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9388", "question": "-42 - -584 - -572 ", "answer": "1114", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9389", "question": "576358 * 684136 + 747168 + -718602 ", "answer": "394307285254", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9390", "question": "-84403 + 69797 + 69500 - -39764 - 20038 ", "answer": "74620", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9391", "question": "-739014 - -59656 * -886470 + -281081 + 588051 ", "answer": "-52883686364", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9392", "question": "264293 - -163533 + 921070 ", "answer": "1348896", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9393", "question": "-640675 * -107431 + -342773 + 758677 * 882162 ", "answer": "738104032826", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9394", "question": "15651 * 31090 + 39034 + 29196 ", "answer": "486657820", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9395", "question": "507 + -543 - 687 * -544 ", "answer": "373692", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9396", "question": "125 * -701 + 439 * 502 ", "answer": "132753", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9397", "question": "-39 - 46 ", "answer": "-85", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9398", "question": "-415244 - 231907 + 181386 * 482482 ", "answer": "87514832901", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9399", "question": "-9886 * -6283 - -9377 + -881 + 6429 ", "answer": "62128663", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9400", "question": "1574 * -69 ", "answer": "-108606", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9401", "question": "868777 - -602798 ", "answer": "1471575", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9402", "question": "-390 - 917 * 724 + 985 - -893 ", "answer": "-662420", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9403", "question": "-63 - -93 * 16 ", "answer": "1425", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9404", "question": "47 + -32 + -1 ", "answer": "14", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9405", "question": "6427 - -8530 + 9947 * -6709 ", "answer": "-66719466", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9406", "question": "146450 * -704931 + 95448 ", "answer": "-103237049502", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9407", "question": "-6224 * 3743 + 7900 ", "answer": "-23288532", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9408", "question": "-137 - 266 + 381 - 847 ", "answer": "-869", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9409", "question": "75667 * 44595 + -33993 - -35680 ", "answer": "3374371552", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9410", "question": "-5 - 58 * -3 - -23 ", "answer": "192", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9411", "question": "-71 + -85 * 66 - -33 + -24 ", "answer": "-5672", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9412", "question": "-8878 * -7914 * 5650 ", "answer": "396971779800", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9413", "question": "-525 * -950 + -372 + 337 ", "answer": "498715", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9414", "question": "-886 + -939 ", "answer": "-1825", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9415", "question": "387001 * 915153 ", "answer": "354165126153", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9416", "question": "666380 * -138397 - -463853 ", "answer": "-92224529007", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9417", "question": "-5272 + -4739 - 746 * 6641 - -5638 ", "answer": "-4958559", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9418", "question": "2904 + -4537 - 3074 + -5346 - -6885 ", "answer": "-3168", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9419", "question": "-226191 + -169102 + -753439 + -56262 - -956551 ", "answer": "-248443", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9420", "question": "-363 - 315 + -547 * -25 ", "answer": "12997", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9421", "question": "312 * -871 ", "answer": "-271752", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9422", "question": "-94671 - -9989 - 16989 * -62234 ", "answer": "1057208744", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9423", "question": "30116 + 66806 ", "answer": "96922", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9424", "question": "12 * -20 - 45 * -37 * 67 ", "answer": "111315", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9425", "question": "-108 + -4847 * -3895 + -3461 ", "answer": "18875496", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9426", "question": "-78674 - -76660 ", "answer": "-2014", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9427", "question": "393 - 730 ", "answer": "-337", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9428", "question": "1299 + 1501 + 80 + -2171 ", "answer": "709", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9429", "question": "-7816 + -8846 - -8438 + 6680 - -5207 ", "answer": "3663", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9430", "question": "-774 * 473 + 223 - 624 - -816 ", "answer": "-365687", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9431", "question": "-23 + -14 - 77 * -48 - -40 ", "answer": "3699", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9432", "question": "-48 + -84 * 93 + -15 ", "answer": "-7875", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9433", "question": "-62031 * -14914 + 75356 + 70832 ", "answer": "925276522", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9434", "question": "-5488 * -3074 ", "answer": "16870112", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9435", "question": "-65 - 4 * 14 ", "answer": "-121", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9436", "question": "428803 * 562159 * -224243 * 852270 ", "answer": "-46069455523129247399970", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9437", "question": "-8223 + -1351 ", "answer": "-9574", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9438", "question": "766759 * 657307 - 62125 + 212807 ", "answer": "503996208695", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9439", "question": "64703 + -55851 + 60408 - -92893 - 65958 ", "answer": "96195", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9440", "question": "-833 - -864 ", "answer": "31", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9441", "question": "-2 * -80 ", "answer": "160", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9442", "question": "-76 + -10 - 89 - -51 ", "answer": "-124", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9443", "question": "541469 + 102026 - -27103 ", "answer": "670598", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9444", "question": "-947955 - -880236 * 341851 ", "answer": "300908608881", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9445", "question": "-10091 - -47633 ", "answer": "37542", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9446", "question": "-6842 * -2408 ", "answer": "16475536", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9447", "question": "-3399 + -1163 - -5910 - -4446 ", "answer": "5794", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9448", "question": "561612 + -259825 ", "answer": "301787", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9449", "question": "514 + -644 - 177 * -186 * -191 ", "answer": "-6288232", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9450", "question": "622404 * -78852 ", "answer": "-49077800208", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9451", "question": "-2 + -19 + 61 ", "answer": "40", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9452", "question": "130 - 368 - -374 - -273 ", "answer": "409", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9453", "question": "-976739 * 179347 + -812534 ", "answer": "-175176021967", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9454", "question": "716 + -811 * 705 ", "answer": "-571039", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9455", "question": "86579 + -41129 - 8599 ", "answer": "36851", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9456", "question": "-5621 + 9203 - -9215 - -9040 ", "answer": "21837", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9457", "question": "7369 - -543 * -522 + 7728 + -7644 ", "answer": "-275993", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9458", "question": "-67553 * -57403 ", "answer": "3877744859", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9459", "question": "86 * 54 + -86 * 57 * -77 ", "answer": "382098", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9460", "question": "-820 * -168 ", "answer": "137760", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9461", "question": "6982 + -9798 - 5143 - 1212 ", "answer": "-9171", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9462", "question": "54399 * 18319 * -28437 ", "answer": "-28338473785797", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9463", "question": "28859 + 3028 * 42400 * -76619 ", "answer": "-9836898847941", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9464", "question": "89 - -14 ", "answer": "103", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9465", "question": "-413 + -754 + -352 + -401 ", "answer": "-1920", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9466", "question": "-4 * 98 - -37 * -57 - 47 ", "answer": "-2548", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9467", "question": "83 * 39 * -62 - -40 * -47 ", "answer": "-202574", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9468", "question": "1239 * -1756 ", "answer": "-2175684", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9469", "question": "-76 * -73 + 83 - -94 ", "answer": "5725", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9470", "question": "63006 - -18208 * 24332 ", "answer": "443100062", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9471", "question": "-72319 - -10125 + -31278 + -73616 ", "answer": "-167088", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9472", "question": "-4204 - -8089 ", "answer": "3885", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9473", "question": "415 - 788 + 137 ", "answer": "-236", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9474", "question": "-3327 - -9146 - -9822 * 3593 * -8279 ", "answer": "-292169596615", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9475", "question": "298336 - 264495 * -237631 ", "answer": "62852509681", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9476", "question": "-37112 - -90894 * 35541 - 65649 ", "answer": "3230360893", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9477", "question": "95125 - -38699 ", "answer": "133824", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9478", "question": "8979 + 1962 ", "answer": "10941", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9479", "question": "83392 - 18429 + -9904 * -85512 ", "answer": "846975811", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9480", "question": "526 + 97 - -667 - 730 + -643 ", "answer": "-83", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9481", "question": "-92 - -61 + -67 ", "answer": "-98", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9482", "question": "913 - 621 - 168 + -206 ", "answer": "-82", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9483", "question": "-189 + -106 + 773 - 207 ", "answer": "271", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9484", "question": "80225 + 80764 - 98193 ", "answer": "62796", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9485", "question": "-168398 * 142924 ", "answer": "-24068115752", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9486", "question": "-929 * -330 ", "answer": "306570", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9487", "question": "206502 + -314747 + 621506 ", "answer": "513261", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9488", "question": "-7026 + -7378 ", "answer": "-14404", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9489", "question": "-300465 - -861091 * 351751 - 732121 + 876570 ", "answer": "302889464325", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9490", "question": "-45133 + 22986 - 6035 * -91201 ", "answer": "550375888", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9491", "question": "-8098 - -3989 - -944 + -5765 + -6955 ", "answer": "-15885", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9492", "question": "-670 + -930 + -884 - 551 ", "answer": "-3035", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9493", "question": "94 * 79 * 51 * -3 ", "answer": "-1136178", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9494", "question": "-427448 * -430295 ", "answer": "183928737160", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9495", "question": "-2420 + 3715 ", "answer": "1295", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9496", "question": "-49 + 5 * -9 + 47 + 91 ", "answer": "44", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9497", "question": "360 * 965 + -219 * 400 - 746 ", "answer": "259054", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9498", "question": "-21 - -20 * -14 * 64 + 23 ", "answer": "-17918", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9499", "question": "726 * -9231 ", "answer": "-6701706", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9500", "question": "508 + -586 - -5697 + -6626 * -2494 ", "answer": "16530863", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9501", "question": "95114 - -27297 - -84397 * 50048 - -91176 ", "answer": "4224114643", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9502", "question": "492 + 385 + -65 - 106 * 864 ", "answer": "-90772", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9503", "question": "-75 + -7 + -28 ", "answer": "-110", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9504", "question": "-892546 * -320806 * -774685 + -729491 ", "answer": "-221818741614325551", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9505", "question": "-380 * 745 * -212 ", "answer": "60017200", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9506", "question": "504 + -850 - 867 - -378 ", "answer": "-835", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9507", "question": "-16292 * -12679 + -27129 + -35109 ", "answer": "206504030", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9508", "question": "49 - 24 - 68 + 28 + 92 ", "answer": "77", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9509", "question": "441 * 6581 + -7775 ", "answer": "2894446", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9510", "question": "7885 + 1243 * 209 + 2723 ", "answer": "270395", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9511", "question": "-791379 - 793670 - 630273 + 148506 - 968995 ", "answer": "-3035811", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9512", "question": "5252 - -9160 ", "answer": "14412", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9513", "question": "71 - -35 - 85 + 16 ", "answer": "37", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9514", "question": "-29308 * 83081 - 54387 - -84114 + -86762 ", "answer": "-2434994983", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9515", "question": "-581037 * -909577 + -24495 * -5656 + -297359 ", "answer": "528636137710", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9516", "question": "531 + -149 ", "answer": "382", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9517", "question": "451 + 159 - 757 * 152 * 916 ", "answer": "-105398014", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9518", "question": "-162893 * 524790 + -149612 * 822446 ", "answer": "-208532408422", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9519", "question": "8 - 13 - -52 * -66 ", "answer": "-3437", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9520", "question": "8987 * -8413 * 5392 - 2171 + -9758 ", "answer": "-407676358281", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9521", "question": "886 + 106 + -895 - 527 ", "answer": "-430", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9522", "question": "-675 * 486 + -375 * 118 * 512 ", "answer": "-22984050", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9523", "question": "34 * -46 + 0 + 33 + 95 ", "answer": "-1436", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9524", "question": "-37414 * 541476 * 216037 + 93700 - -181467 ", "answer": "-4376646716522201", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9525", "question": "-91799 - -29147 + 25891 + -99535 ", "answer": "-136296", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9526", "question": "-38940 - 88661 ", "answer": "-127601", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9527", "question": "-89592 * 56987 * -56753 - 71689 * 51612 ", "answer": "289753242227244", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9528", "question": "28 + 647 + -754 - -848 + 286 ", "answer": "1055", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9529", "question": "58084 + 69955 - 91751 * 80894 ", "answer": "-7421977355", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9530", "question": "263919 * 707515 ", "answer": "186726651285", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9531", "question": "4489 + -8212 + 3356 ", "answer": "-367", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9532", "question": "45 * 0 * 92 - -31 + 46 ", "answer": "77", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9533", "question": "9030 - 2774 - 3872 + 849 * -1965 ", "answer": "-1665901", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9534", "question": "-2196 - -6995 * 188 + -3818 ", "answer": "1309046", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9535", "question": "-634061 * -198733 ", "answer": "126008844713", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9536", "question": "572 - -99 + -668 ", "answer": "3", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9537", "question": "762 + 143 - -305 ", "answer": "1210", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9538", "question": "-862819 + 587819 + 149328 ", "answer": "-125672", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9539", "question": "-293 + 341 - -319 * -391 ", "answer": "-124681", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9540", "question": "-50871 * -46231 - 82727 * -66690 ", "answer": "7868880831", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9541", "question": "974 + -352 - 52 ", "answer": "570", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9542", "question": "45644 + -92408 ", "answer": "-46764", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9543", "question": "647035 + 56739 + -48140 ", "answer": "655634", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9544", "question": "-46 * -40 - -8 ", "answer": "1848", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9545", "question": "15832 * -16250 + -8418 + 12222 - -1703 ", "answer": "-257264493", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9546", "question": "724008 * -266506 * -305579 + 963324 - -332065 ", "answer": "58962224679567181", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9547", "question": "55 + 26 + -38 - 72 ", "answer": "-29", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9548", "question": "-806 * -286 ", "answer": "230516", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9549", "question": "-475 - 589 ", "answer": "-1064", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9550", "question": "3621 + 6261 * 2307 * 8072 ", "answer": "116592996765", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9551", "question": "73728 + -10503 ", "answer": "63225", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9552", "question": "-733280 * 979102 ", "answer": "-717955914560", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9553", "question": "-31321 - -10728 ", "answer": "-20593", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9554", "question": "56 + -87 * 18 ", "answer": "-1510", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9555", "question": "-77 - 98 - -21 - 88 * 81 ", "answer": "-7282", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9556", "question": "-66 + 72 - 68 ", "answer": "-62", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9557", "question": "-53 * 7 + -13 ", "answer": "-384", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9558", "question": "-898 - 428 + -611 * -647 + -476 ", "answer": "393515", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9559", "question": "54006 * -96064 + -27648 ", "answer": "-5188060032", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9560", "question": "-515 * -859 - 407 - 441 ", "answer": "441537", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9561", "question": "790941 - 933751 * 307757 + -442129 ", "answer": "-287368057695", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9562", "question": "107 + 242 ", "answer": "349", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9563", "question": "73 * -70 + -11 - -5 + -63 ", "answer": "-5179", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9564", "question": "495 * 577 - -516 ", "answer": "286131", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9565", "question": "96 + 29 - 42 ", "answer": "83", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9566", "question": "-97615 + -6432 + 64394 - -61871 ", "answer": "22218", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9567", "question": "572 * -852 ", "answer": "-487344", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9568", "question": "86 + 29 + 82 ", "answer": "197", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9569", "question": "166 + -386 ", "answer": "-220", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9570", "question": "4646 + 1410 ", "answer": "6056", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9571", "question": "-25914 * 96812 * -94282 - -44516 ", "answer": "236533377535892", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9572", "question": "-769285 * 745792 - -679611 * 716640 * 535148 ", "answer": "260635996131003200", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9573", "question": "11278 + 54248 - -87217 ", "answer": "152743", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9574", "question": "-9264 * 2950 + 4135 ", "answer": "-27324665", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9575", "question": "98 + 19 ", "answer": "117", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9576", "question": "-936 * 104 ", "answer": "-97344", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9577", "question": "-3011 * -8209 + -6797 ", "answer": "24710502", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9578", "question": "-492693 * 819563 ", "answer": "-403792953159", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9579", "question": "-83821 * 88014 * -84275 + 31052 * -40448 ", "answer": "621730940415554", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9580", "question": "49 - 18 - -68 ", "answer": "99", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9581", "question": "-6465 - 2946 * -2036 ", "answer": "5991591", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9582", "question": "1189 - -3717 ", "answer": "4906", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9583", "question": "-47 * 81 - -23 ", "answer": "-3784", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9584", "question": "-471401 - 960823 * -182 ", "answer": "174398385", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9585", "question": "277 - 19 - -150 * 831 + -309 ", "answer": "124599", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9586", "question": "3154 - -7668 * -1469 - 7206 ", "answer": "-11268344", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9587", "question": "-601026 + -193383 * 268795 ", "answer": "-51980984511", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9588", "question": "95 + 945 + -925 * -304 ", "answer": "282240", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9589", "question": "943635 * 3354 ", "answer": "3164951790", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9590", "question": "75 - -9 * 36 + 89 ", "answer": "488", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9591", "question": "916 - -931 ", "answer": "1847", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9592", "question": "164 * -819 * -224 + 138 ", "answer": "30086922", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9593", "question": "769548 * -394429 + -326280 * 213106 ", "answer": "-373064273772", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9594", "question": "-878 * 240 - 989 * 156 ", "answer": "-365004", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9595", "question": "-88539 - -39462 * 13423 ", "answer": "529609887", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9596", "question": "84 - -59 + 61 + -73 ", "answer": "131", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9597", "question": "-25336 * -562346 ", "answer": "14247598256", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9598", "question": "80 - 73 ", "answer": "7", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9599", "question": "-96 * 42 * -92 ", "answer": "370944", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9600", "question": "-408912 * 495092 - 222420 - -697008 ", "answer": "-202448585316", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9601", "question": "59138 - -47429 ", "answer": "106567", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9602", "question": "64838 - -42534 + 74440 - 93963 ", "answer": "87849", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9603", "question": "-782508 * -474155 ", "answer": "371030080740", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9604", "question": "640222 - 55276 ", "answer": "584946", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9605", "question": "867384 - 730611 ", "answer": "136773", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9606", "question": "35 - -61 * -9 - -59 ", "answer": "-455", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9607", "question": "9918 - 2552 + -7508 ", "answer": "-142", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9608", "question": "-733479 - 754338 ", "answer": "-1487817", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9609", "question": "-3 + 33 - 93 * -56 ", "answer": "5238", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9610", "question": "4681 - -1194 * -3274 + 981 + 4793 ", "answer": "-3898701", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9611", "question": "68 + -58 + -37 - 82 ", "answer": "-109", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9612", "question": "75248 - -89818 * 86158 ", "answer": "7738614492", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9613", "question": "-834971 * 585562 * -682626 * 820718 ", "answer": "273918308805736029502536", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9614", "question": "882 - -574 + 792 ", "answer": "2248", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9615", "question": "-918 + 334 ", "answer": "-584", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9616", "question": "619408 * -716776 * 786763 * 796352 ", "answer": "-278169345255502069342208", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9617", "question": "-17147 * 74430 ", "answer": "-1276251210", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9618", "question": "-768561 - -541657 ", "answer": "-226904", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9619", "question": "1300 + 1112 + 7181 - 3153 + -3722 ", "answer": "2718", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9620", "question": "-30 - -42 - 64 ", "answer": "-52", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9621", "question": "-5654 + -50803 + -16975 - -53913 ", "answer": "-19519", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9622", "question": "-330635 - 228964 - -704826 ", "answer": "145227", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9623", "question": "-311435 * -95800 ", "answer": "29835473000", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9624", "question": "-2839 * 6340 + 2198 * 6250 ", "answer": "-4261760", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9625", "question": "-301 * -124 + -786 ", "answer": "36538", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9626", "question": "-344922 + -963194 + -834749 + -333106 ", "answer": "-2475971", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9627", "question": "-729 * -853 * -963 * 12 ", "answer": "-7185948372", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9628", "question": "444956 + 34305 ", "answer": "479261", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9629", "question": "-786 + 149 - -451 * -988 + 530 ", "answer": "-445695", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9630", "question": "-83 + -24 + 71 + 74 ", "answer": "38", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9631", "question": "2056 - -7138 + -1673 + 6463 ", "answer": "13984", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9632", "question": "722 - -951 + -244 + 519 - -189 ", "answer": "2137", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9633", "question": "-46493 - -44345 - -46050 ", "answer": "43902", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9634", "question": "545629 * 254361 ", "answer": "138786738069", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9635", "question": "-362 * 501 + -567 + -745 ", "answer": "-182674", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9636", "question": "872521 + 319604 * 309049 ", "answer": "98774169117", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9637", "question": "1460 * 6785 - 869 + 1516 + 4943 ", "answer": "9911690", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9638", "question": "648652 * 797065 + -556301 + -615518 + -9335 ", "answer": "517016625226", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9639", "question": "-569 - -753 - 966 ", "answer": "-782", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9640", "question": "-57732 + -883501 * 204819 - -870611 ", "answer": "-180956978440", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9641", "question": "-25 + 54 ", "answer": "29", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9642", "question": "-305 + 898 * 512 - 734 ", "answer": "458737", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9643", "question": "-58 + 37 - 14 ", "answer": "-35", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9644", "question": "99 + -22 - 94 + 59 - 24 ", "answer": "18", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9645", "question": "-2443 + -487 ", "answer": "-2930", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9646", "question": "68846 - -43574 + -86086 - 42050 - -70210 ", "answer": "54494", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9647", "question": "82550 - 92402 * 41903 - 55568 ", "answer": "-3871894024", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9648", "question": "-573 * 924 - -746 ", "answer": "-528706", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9649", "question": "526 + -48 - -372 * 296 + -520 ", "answer": "110070", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9650", "question": "-60 - -3 * -87 * -49 ", "answer": "12729", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9651", "question": "37615 * -19716 + 57075 + -18492 ", "answer": "-741578757", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9652", "question": "-269536 * 113098 + 446860 ", "answer": "-30483535668", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9653", "question": "-658 + -671 + -241 * 912 - 230 ", "answer": "-221351", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9654", "question": "321 * -57392 ", "answer": "-18422832", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9655", "question": "1945 + 4015 ", "answer": "5960", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9656", "question": "-836 + -176 * -637 ", "answer": "111276", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9657", "question": "8261 - -74474 * -46880 + -63636 ", "answer": "-3491396495", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9658", "question": "-4731 * 725 + -7375 - 8579 ", "answer": "-3445929", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9659", "question": "70727 * 86715 * -6979 * 79135 ", "answer": "-3387203353300962825", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9660", "question": "210098 - -960248 - 459516 ", "answer": "710830", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9661", "question": "77 + 91 + 26 ", "answer": "194", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9662", "question": "-65609 * -87810 ", "answer": "5761126290", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9663", "question": "8 - -60 + -5 + -1 ", "answer": "62", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9664", "question": "54 + 4 + 20 * -15 * -90 ", "answer": "27058", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9665", "question": "853 + -9 ", "answer": "844", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9666", "question": "-53587 * 97501 - 94320 * 49915 * 96656 ", "answer": "-455060010302887", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9667", "question": "562 - 2437 ", "answer": "-1875", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9668", "question": "74 - 33 ", "answer": "41", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9669", "question": "53 + -80 - 96 ", "answer": "-123", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9670", "question": "-832696 * 849116 + 391319 - 999772 + -821679 ", "answer": "-707056926868", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9671", "question": "68054 - -690455 * 225509 ", "answer": "155703884649", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9672", "question": "-24262 + 43923 + 1519 * 44997 * -90173 ", "answer": "-6163364476978", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9673", "question": "50 * -86 * -29 + -54 ", "answer": "124646", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9674", "question": "-61904 - 99220 + 47143 ", "answer": "-113981", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9675", "question": "846 - 870 + 316 * -13 * -390 ", "answer": "1602096", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9676", "question": "-455 * -488 * -943 - 209 * 507 ", "answer": "-209489683", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9677", "question": "-246 * -477 * 787 - -468 ", "answer": "92348622", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9678", "question": "-78 * 31 ", "answer": "-2418", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9679", "question": "911 - -877 + 296 - 221 * 583 ", "answer": "-126759", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9680", "question": "433669 * 526294 * -845730 ", "answer": "-193027210116330780", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9681", "question": "69887 + -60776 ", "answer": "9111", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9682", "question": "92303 + 61665 ", "answer": "153968", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9683", "question": "57 * -74 * 61 + 95 * -3 ", "answer": "-257583", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9684", "question": "-278141 + 139030 ", "answer": "-139111", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9685", "question": "240443 - 855035 * -16910 + -356188 - -331912 ", "answer": "14458858017", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9686", "question": "755 + -514 - -430 ", "answer": "671", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9687", "question": "16027 - -45797 + -23776 ", "answer": "38048", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9688", "question": "-25659 * 28472 - -98848 - 25348 + -10300 ", "answer": "-730499848", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9689", "question": "-32280 - -79622 + 78192 * 3671 + 39370 ", "answer": "287129544", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9690", "question": "-628920 - -208161 - 350100 - -628420 ", "answer": "-142439", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9691", "question": "-31 + 46 ", "answer": "15", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9692", "question": "-1667 * 9460 - 2389 ", "answer": "-15772209", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9693", "question": "-91345 + 27096 ", "answer": "-64249", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9694", "question": "-496 * 843 ", "answer": "-418128", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9695", "question": "-64 - -24 * 69 ", "answer": "1592", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9696", "question": "-85725 * -19853 + 56397 + 61992 ", "answer": "1702016814", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9697", "question": "50 + 93 ", "answer": "143", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9698", "question": "8 - 580 * 311 + -807 ", "answer": "-181179", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9699", "question": "6258 - -9473 ", "answer": "15731", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9700", "question": "3594 * -9066 + -1519 ", "answer": "-32584723", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9701", "question": "-336711 * 240102 - -520116 - 792361 + 395568 ", "answer": "-80844861199", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9702", "question": "-59119 * -56456 + -22944 + 32553 ", "answer": "3337631873", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9703", "question": "48 * -74 * -250 * 521 * 628 ", "answer": "290542944000", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9704", "question": "-353 - 13 ", "answer": "-366", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9705", "question": "6451 - 3621 ", "answer": "2830", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9706", "question": "6878 * -2331 + 9820 ", "answer": "-16022798", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9707", "question": "153002 + -5585 * 766800 ", "answer": "-4282424998", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9708", "question": "337 - 140 - 38 ", "answer": "159", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9709", "question": "7925 + -2789 + 5222 - -8750 ", "answer": "19108", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9710", "question": "-2221 - 4087 ", "answer": "-6308", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9711", "question": "53031 + 63041 - -65507 - -46031 ", "answer": "227610", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9712", "question": "56 * -23 * -19 ", "answer": "24472", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9713", "question": "-11753 * 68088 ", "answer": "-800238264", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9714", "question": "355 - -691 + -967 - 713 ", "answer": "-634", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9715", "question": "38 - -63 + 42 * -65 ", "answer": "-2629", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9716", "question": "-7958 - 817 * -2618 - 639 + -9265 ", "answer": "2121044", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9717", "question": "75501 * 58427 - -55995 * 85151 ", "answer": "9179327172", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9718", "question": "-5486 - -9299 * 9170 ", "answer": "85266344", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9719", "question": "4222 - -51071 ", "answer": "55293", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9720", "question": "-7033 - -6156 ", "answer": "-877", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9721", "question": "-12662 * -121 - 79241 * 11599 ", "answer": "-917584257", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9722", "question": "1519 - -7278 * -5527 * -9927 ", "answer": "399318599581", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9723", "question": "-32426 + 33351 ", "answer": "925", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9724", "question": "3851 * 3228 - 9267 + -1104 + 3387 ", "answer": "12424044", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9725", "question": "-152104 - 86710 - 370779 * 18154 ", "answer": "-6731360780", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9726", "question": "-46954 * 91933 - -76738 * -98934 * -52121 ", "answer": "395698174234250", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9727", "question": "765 + -15 - -567 + -344 ", "answer": "973", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9728", "question": "-901022 * -249245 * -75055 ", "answer": "-16855493766811450", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9729", "question": "-78585 * 93030 * -69746 * -46556 ", "answer": "-23738738884681438800", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9730", "question": "767590 * 77759 + 835031 ", "answer": "59687865841", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9731", "question": "-352 - 9895 - -4832 - -7177 * -7373 ", "answer": "-52921436", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9732", "question": "-5 + 32 ", "answer": "27", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9733", "question": "-31935 + 904387 * 391593 + -207628 ", "answer": "354151378928", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9734", "question": "-41 + -58 - -54 - 81 - 17 ", "answer": "-143", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9735", "question": "507919 - -700184 - -257788 - 560222 - 55585 ", "answer": "850084", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9736", "question": "-133577 * -454292 ", "answer": "60682962484", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9737", "question": "-19 + -87 ", "answer": "-106", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9738", "question": "2709 - 2218 ", "answer": "491", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9739", "question": "1834 + -5062 ", "answer": "-3228", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9740", "question": "-691281 * 59867 + 23771 ", "answer": "-41384895856", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9741", "question": "-309217 + 406289 - -476331 ", "answer": "573403", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9742", "question": "9949 - 7534 - -3343 - 1788 * 1058 ", "answer": "-1885946", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9743", "question": "-93 + -2 - 5 * -65 ", "answer": "230", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9744", "question": "-1697 + 1355 + 6614 * -3397 ", "answer": "-22468100", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9745", "question": "-84 + -49 ", "answer": "-133", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9746", "question": "32111 - 14373 + -15582 - -68867 + 5393 ", "answer": "76416", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9747", "question": "314 + 846 - -167 ", "answer": "1327", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9748", "question": "867 * -341 - -61 * -570 - 782 ", "answer": "-331199", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9749", "question": "2265 * -1962 ", "answer": "-4443930", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9750", "question": "806636 * 458636 + 43641 + 631108 * -112281 ", "answer": "299090914789", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9751", "question": "8531 - 8351 ", "answer": "180", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9752", "question": "-7 + 61 * -74 - 19 ", "answer": "-4540", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9753", "question": "-28103 * 506174 ", "answer": "-14225007922", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9754", "question": "-76 - -7 + 70 ", "answer": "1", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9755", "question": "433881 + -343474 * -927213 * 874225 ", "answer": "278417546209763331", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9756", "question": "-3887 + 8165 + 5713 - -3295 ", "answer": "13286", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9757", "question": "-737601 * -515868 - -181633 ", "answer": "380504934301", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9758", "question": "-1670 + -7754 * -25 * -7837 ", "answer": "-1519204120", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9759", "question": "-84 + -12 - -31 + 64 ", "answer": "-1", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9760", "question": "54247 + -631828 * 148216 ", "answer": "-93646964601", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9761", "question": "471 * 825 * -581 * -139 * -890 ", "answer": "-27929026298250", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9762", "question": "-16125 * 35000 * -32173 + 52947 - -60016 ", "answer": "18157636987963", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9763", "question": "-9321 - -5307 ", "answer": "-4014", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9764", "question": "-923 + 143 + 810 ", "answer": "30", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9765", "question": "3635 + 7491 - 1442 - -1250 - -890 ", "answer": "11824", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9766", "question": "-89 * -41 * -64 ", "answer": "-233536", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9767", "question": "-413 + -128 + -71 ", "answer": "-612", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9768", "question": "-419626 - 217621 ", "answer": "-637247", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9769", "question": "-786888 + -51018 - 868570 * -378288 - -818521 ", "answer": "328569588775", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9770", "question": "-34156 * -73624 * -74634 * -36421 ", "answer": "6835574138556964416", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9771", "question": "52587 + 24615 ", "answer": "77202", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9772", "question": "-4717 + 3593 ", "answer": "-1124", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9773", "question": "96 * 72 ", "answer": "6912", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9774", "question": "-85792 * 249672 * -522290 - 82262 * 141696 ", "answer": "11187367140196608", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9775", "question": "-803696 + -236665 * -73166 ", "answer": "17315027694", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9776", "question": "-39023 - 83814 - 13915 * -19930 ", "answer": "277203113", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9777", "question": "167 * 9557 + 3631 * 9499 + -2735 ", "answer": "36084153", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9778", "question": "138799 * 71134 - -822360 + 775913 ", "answer": "9874926339", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9779", "question": "-382 - -739 ", "answer": "357", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9780", "question": "809727 * 331585 * 592432 * 680928 ", "answer": "108311157863778336376320", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9781", "question": "44670 - 17217 + 60866 - 81291 ", "answer": "7028", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9782", "question": "-1634 + 9592 - 714 ", "answer": "7244", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9783", "question": "26 + -37 ", "answer": "-11", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9784", "question": "-57028 * -72269 + -79243 - 20182 ", "answer": "4121257107", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9785", "question": "991 - -83 ", "answer": "1074", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9786", "question": "221744 - 230187 * -545579 + 525542 ", "answer": "125585940559", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9787", "question": "-41 + 972 * -902 + -430 * 142 ", "answer": "-937845", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9788", "question": "5597 * 3921 - 2173 ", "answer": "21943664", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9789", "question": "811314 * -604606 - -502808 - 772062 + 39419 ", "answer": "-490525542119", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9790", "question": "86775 * -11281 - 85722 ", "answer": "-978994497", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9791", "question": "-40 * -79 * 59 + -95 ", "answer": "186345", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9792", "question": "-24 - 68 * 6 ", "answer": "-432", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9793", "question": "76396 - -14218 + -30667 * 47111 ", "answer": "-1444662423", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9794", "question": "-82 * -393 ", "answer": "32226", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9795", "question": "979975 * -524673 ", "answer": "-514166423175", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9796", "question": "95814 - -734599 ", "answer": "830413", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9797", "question": "-2738 + -1217 + -5635 ", "answer": "-9590", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9798", "question": "80230 * 41021 ", "answer": "3291114830", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9799", "question": "99803 + 14775 - -5721 - 13361 ", "answer": "106938", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9800", "question": "-742951 - 702045 ", "answer": "-1444996", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9801", "question": "13 - -33 * 47 ", "answer": "1564", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9802", "question": "8 - -1 * 20 * -28 ", "answer": "-552", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9803", "question": "-2645 * -7089 + 2832 - -2583 ", "answer": "18755820", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9804", "question": "-55332 + 90441 - 52187 ", "answer": "-17078", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9805", "question": "-170577 * 671824 + 629870 ", "answer": "-114597092578", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9806", "question": "-430270 + -584918 ", "answer": "-1015188", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9807", "question": "-131 - -901 + 173 ", "answer": "943", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9808", "question": "-59739 + -62851 * 49767 * -85208 - -83552 ", "answer": "266522590357949", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9809", "question": "-36 + -88 - -37 + 29 * -36 ", "answer": "-1131", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9810", "question": "-26324 * -18954 ", "answer": "498945096", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9811", "question": "70347 * -81329 * -20084 ", "answer": "114905608357692", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9812", "question": "-1128 * 8576 ", "answer": "-9673728", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9813", "question": "-3003 * 5058 * 7840 ", "answer": "-119083124160", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9814", "question": "27 + 372 + 522 ", "answer": "921", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9815", "question": "61060 + 59880 ", "answer": "120940", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9816", "question": "-55 * 1 ", "answer": "-55", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9817", "question": "427300 - -563129 - -141573 ", "answer": "1132002", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9818", "question": "-71 + 96 * -57 - 52 - -37 ", "answer": "-5558", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9819", "question": "-6601 - -205 * 2626 - -4472 * 3557 ", "answer": "16438633", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9820", "question": "-90264 - 50612 ", "answer": "-140876", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9821", "question": "-9677 + 2731 ", "answer": "-6946", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9822", "question": "4873 - -6033 * -6398 * 984 * -1201 ", "answer": "45615838979929", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9823", "question": "-575 + -991 + 730 * -570 ", "answer": "-417666", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9824", "question": "-65484 - -61785 + -36199 ", "answer": "-39898", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9825", "question": "7268 - 7119 + 222 * 7101 ", "answer": "1576571", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9826", "question": "-49516 - 97567 * -73211 * 23033 + -56247 ", "answer": "164524203807258", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9827", "question": "-164 + -78 * -796 * 747 ", "answer": "46379572", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9828", "question": "645 - 914 ", "answer": "-269", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9829", "question": "-508 - 876 - -797 + 508 ", "answer": "-79", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9830", "question": "31437 * -75888 + 10874 ", "answer": "-2385680182", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9831", "question": "-692 + 914 ", "answer": "222", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9832", "question": "42 - 5 - 44 + 85 ", "answer": "78", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9833", "question": "-6585 * -21860 + 21961 + 90443 - -42852 ", "answer": "144103356", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9834", "question": "-73 * -22 + 19 + -34 * 93 ", "answer": "-1537", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9835", "question": "7592 + -3220 * -393 ", "answer": "1273052", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9836", "question": "341210 * -865907 + 500035 ", "answer": "-295455627435", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9837", "question": "-13 + -81 + -40 + 44 ", "answer": "-90", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9838", "question": "526162 + -877638 + -469319 + -3617 - -777970 ", "answer": "-46442", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9839", "question": "4513 * -1978 - 9400 ", "answer": "-8936114", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9840", "question": "-52 + -51 - 37 + -44 ", "answer": "-184", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9841", "question": "-465156 + 289516 ", "answer": "-175640", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9842", "question": "46 * 24 * 76 - 64 ", "answer": "83840", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9843", "question": "4674 - 4937 + -44 ", "answer": "-307", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9844", "question": "13982 + 54926 - 77967 + 64781 + -72452 ", "answer": "-16730", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9845", "question": "-879 - -7434 - -7175 ", "answer": "13730", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9846", "question": "669 * 6488 - 6752 - 2071 ", "answer": "4331649", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9847", "question": "-20202 + 37291 * -64176 + -63822 ", "answer": "-2393271240", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9848", "question": "-96 - -4 * 52 ", "answer": "112", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9849", "question": "-8646 - 4374 - 6046 ", "answer": "-19066", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9850", "question": "-1729 - -6481 - -7971 - 5317 + 1639 ", "answer": "9045", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9851", "question": "-738 * -814 - 452 ", "answer": "600280", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9852", "question": "-93340 + -41519 + 59316 * 63152 ", "answer": "3745789173", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9853", "question": "327867 * -622954 ", "answer": "-204246059118", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9854", "question": "-5469 * -8158 ", "answer": "44616102", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9855", "question": "-12957 * -41135 + 36262 - 20518 ", "answer": "533001939", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9856", "question": "-5724 + -1358 + 7751 + 7348 ", "answer": "8017", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9857", "question": "87580 * 88993 - -37233 ", "answer": "7794044173", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9858", "question": "85 + -28 + -99 + -2 - 93 ", "answer": "-137", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9859", "question": "433 * -2149 ", "answer": "-930517", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9860", "question": "-291 * -78 + 637 + -112 + 130 ", "answer": "23353", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9861", "question": "281 * -826 - 109 + -411 ", "answer": "-232626", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9862", "question": "76 + 771 + -71 ", "answer": "776", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9863", "question": "-5640 - 9472 + 5502 ", "answer": "-9610", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9864", "question": "4619 + -778 ", "answer": "3841", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9865", "question": "5142 * -9815 - 2659 + -5066 * -1687 ", "answer": "-41925047", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9866", "question": "419 * 670 ", "answer": "280730", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9867", "question": "8680 - 2845 ", "answer": "5835", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9868", "question": "4873 - -923 * -7944 * 9875 ", "answer": "-72406576127", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9869", "question": "-3041 * 9872 - -3132 ", "answer": "-30017620", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9870", "question": "3453 + 9248 * -5226 ", "answer": "-48326595", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9871", "question": "542025 - -627983 + 210145 * -979508 - 485458 ", "answer": "-205838024110", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9872", "question": "819 - 622 + -311 - 291 ", "answer": "-405", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9873", "question": "-63 + -25 ", "answer": "-88", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9874", "question": "69 + 43 ", "answer": "112", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9875", "question": "-39223 * 318 * -27664 + -24552 ", "answer": "345050668344", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9876", "question": "8283 * -5478 - 7145 - -6120 ", "answer": "-45375299", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9877", "question": "4635 - 8891 * -9209 * -6547 ", "answer": "-536050148158", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9878", "question": "896 * -344 + -650 * -489 ", "answer": "9626", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9879", "question": "-863 * -111 + -973 - -451 ", "answer": "95271", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9880", "question": "6108 - 5487 * -3120 + 5592 + -5774 ", "answer": "17125366", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9881", "question": "-43769 - 4406 + -27375 ", "answer": "-75550", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9882", "question": "-9831 + -3014 ", "answer": "-12845", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9883", "question": "313 - 7069 * 1566 * -362 ", "answer": "4007359861", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9884", "question": "5046 * -8807 - -7102 * 8304 ", "answer": "14534886", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9885", "question": "37 * -19 ", "answer": "-703", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9886", "question": "290 + -10 ", "answer": "280", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9887", "question": "-1987 - -8794 - -9753 + -218 + 1027 ", "answer": "17369", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9888", "question": "3514 * 5188 * -4401 ", "answer": "-80233011432", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9889", "question": "-21 * -33 ", "answer": "693", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9890", "question": "-269381 - -686534 - 823218 + 366829 * 524410 ", "answer": "192368389825", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9891", "question": "-3667 * -5171 * -6181 - 3221 ", "answer": "-117204477538", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9892", "question": "-241 - -9075 * -1635 + 2669 + 970 ", "answer": "-14834227", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9893", "question": "-831619 - 237097 ", "answer": "-1068716", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9894", "question": "569630 - 907773 - -303012 + -31222 + -832856 ", "answer": "-899209", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9895", "question": "374 * -769 + 558 ", "answer": "-287048", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9896", "question": "-81039 * -51186 + 31939 + -84208 + 49882 ", "answer": "4148059867", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9897", "question": "934 * 5971 - -7894 ", "answer": "5584808", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9898", "question": "9973 + -9278 + 2835 - 5273 ", "answer": "-1743", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9899", "question": "51 + -87 - 11 * -63 ", "answer": "657", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9900", "question": "962053 * -407251 - 920998 * 210977 * -582665 ", "answer": "113216891867431287", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9901", "question": "-442 + 612 ", "answer": "170", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9902", "question": "1043 + -5056 - -6402 + 624 ", "answer": "3013", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9903", "question": "19 - -47 - -30 ", "answer": "96", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9904", "question": "-68316 * -4704 - 32189 + 74156 ", "answer": "321400431", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9905", "question": "45 + -25 * -78 - -72 - -24 ", "answer": "2091", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9906", "question": "10305 + 87605 ", "answer": "97910", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9907", "question": "-10405 * -28648 * 7184 * -29257 ", "answer": "-62651649251822720", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9908", "question": "-904995 * -168104 - -265086 + -811539 ", "answer": "152132733027", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9909", "question": "1966 + 117 * 5843 ", "answer": "685597", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9910", "question": "237 - -415 - -431 ", "answer": "1083", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9911", "question": "404 * -606 - 369 * 453 + -644 ", "answer": "-412625", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9912", "question": "757849 + -483473 * 214386 ", "answer": "-103649084729", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9913", "question": "-14549 + -71253 * -520045 ", "answer": "37054751836", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9914", "question": "-6313 + 5595 * -4824 ", "answer": "-26996593", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9915", "question": "387 + -245 + -204 + 120 - 606 ", "answer": "-548", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9916", "question": "90125 * -46627 * 76651 - -58987 ", "answer": "-322107306643138", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9917", "question": "894313 + 840964 - -468879 * 150748 * 451858 ", "answer": "31938485390967413", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9918", "question": "64 * -46 * 66 - -98 ", "answer": "-194206", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9919", "question": "704360 * -323611 + 696454 - 456736 ", "answer": "-227938404242", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9920", "question": "-77 - -62 - -37 * 35 * 90 ", "answer": "116535", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9921", "question": "241 * -148 * -373 - 307 ", "answer": "13303857", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9922", "question": "-98499 * 807998 + 848634 - 342882 + 44261 ", "answer": "-79586444989", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9923", "question": "5386 * 5573 * 2158 * 4890 ", "answer": "316749320286360", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9924", "question": "-75 - -66 * -2 ", "answer": "-207", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9925", "question": "17379 - -86494 - 86602 + -4084 ", "answer": "13187", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9926", "question": "-34 * -4 + 66 + -95 ", "answer": "107", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9927", "question": "-494 - -84 - 549 ", "answer": "-959", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9928", "question": "46782 * 15060 * 64070 ", "answer": "45139680464400", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9929", "question": "7439 * -5389 * 2420 - -750 ", "answer": "-97014825070", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9930", "question": "-6303 + -48067 ", "answer": "-54370", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9931", "question": "906 - -644 ", "answer": "1550", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9932", "question": "96 * -43 - -75 * 8 - 91 ", "answer": "-3619", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9933", "question": "861 * -827 * -968 * 899 * 549 ", "answer": "340185700612296", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9934", "question": "-229873 * -81656 ", "answer": "18770509688", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9935", "question": "-8625 * 5315 * -2515 * 2551 + -663 ", "answer": "294110697158712", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9936", "question": "-8277 * -2721 + -936 * -7890 - -9561 ", "answer": "29916318", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9937", "question": "91107 - -44251 ", "answer": "135358", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9938", "question": "90 + 57 - -78 * 87 ", "answer": "6933", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9939", "question": "-29 - -10 * 36 - -93 ", "answer": "424", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9940", "question": "-762763 * 407969 * 497580 ", "answer": "-154838764720300260", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9941", "question": "1751 * -375 ", "answer": "-656625", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9942", "question": "7633 - -93521 * -53696 + 95349 + 78573 ", "answer": "-5021522061", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9943", "question": "44 + -75 - 99 ", "answer": "-130", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9944", "question": "913438 + 222445 + 100156 * 403207 * 500556 ", "answer": "20214253428898235", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9945", "question": "332019 * 705855 + -987199 ", "answer": "234356284046", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9946", "question": "460705 - 373131 ", "answer": "87574", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9947", "question": "-169919 + -315186 ", "answer": "-485105", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9948", "question": "-29 - -733 ", "answer": "704", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9949", "question": "-8923 + -4341 * -311 ", "answer": "1341128", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9950", "question": "-83 + -42 + 57 - -76 ", "answer": "8", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9951", "question": "-71729 - -98750 - -66369 ", "answer": "93390", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9952", "question": "816 + -108 + -592 ", "answer": "116", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9953", "question": "628 + 37 * 745 - -946 - 106 ", "answer": "29033", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9954", "question": "-21248 + 17510 ", "answer": "-3738", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9955", "question": "-51 - 23 + -62 * -47 * -83 ", "answer": "-241936", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9956", "question": "-84122 * 95419 * -12900 + -8013 ", "answer": "103546198814187", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9957", "question": "391605 * 485523 - -631861 + -265240 ", "answer": "190133601036", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9958", "question": "-523152 - -34885 ", "answer": "-488267", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9959", "question": "-595769 * 103070 + 594672 + 222772 ", "answer": "-61405093386", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9960", "question": "913314 - 710953 - -311823 - 628728 ", "answer": "-114544", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9961", "question": "-413044 * 595897 * -67891 * -707336 - 455623 ", "answer": "-11819673626796330375591", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9962", "question": "-189 + -979 * -138 + 985 * -765 ", "answer": "-618612", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9963", "question": "68627 - 89552 - 75820 - 74751 * -57398 ", "answer": "4290461153", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9964", "question": "15484 - -4251 ", "answer": "19735", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9965", "question": "121 - 586 ", "answer": "-465", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9966", "question": "21525 * 50039 ", "answer": "1077089475", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9967", "question": "-4455 - -1697 ", "answer": "-2758", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9968", "question": "-54 - -100 ", "answer": "46", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9969", "question": "41972 - -63446 ", "answer": "105418", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9970", "question": "337 * -436 - 182 ", "answer": "-147114", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9971", "question": "3 * -20 ", "answer": "-60", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9972", "question": "27285 - 573768 * 807 * 705956 * 394350 ", "answer": "-128904873447806886315", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9973", "question": "856190 * -280736 + -581752 + -550389 - 867243 ", "answer": "-240365355224", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9974", "question": "-30 * -27 + 78 * -62 - -84 ", "answer": "-3942", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9975", "question": "-98592 + 83723 + -69127 - 90918 ", "answer": "-174914", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9976", "question": "-84 + -9 ", "answer": "-93", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9977", "question": "913215 * -686966 - -159728 ", "answer": "-627347495962", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9978", "question": "-89796 - -28462 + -16293 ", "answer": "-77627", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9979", "question": "-31 * -76 * -85 ", "answer": "-200260", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9980", "question": "350 * 228 + 669 ", "answer": "80469", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9981", "question": "131 - 435 ", "answer": "-304", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9982", "question": "-78 - -69 ", "answer": "-9", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9983", "question": "9590 * -9612 ", "answer": "-92179080", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9984", "question": "-17 - 25 ", "answer": "-42", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9985", "question": "59252 * 16796 ", "answer": "995196592", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9986", "question": "-13 + 792 * 967 ", "answer": "765851", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9987", "question": "5821 * 4032 * -1802 + -4112 + -4883 ", "answer": "-42293439139", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 4}
{"id": "9988", "question": "-73503 - 66461 - 48037 ", "answer": "-188001", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9989", "question": "-232286 + 233605 + -134548 + -253942 ", "answer": "-387171", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9990", "question": "37 - -67 * -27 + -100 - -38 ", "answer": "-1834", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9991", "question": "-74 + 46 ", "answer": "-28", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 2}
{"id": "9992", "question": "819 + -608 ", "answer": "211", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 3}
{"id": "9993", "question": "28042 - 24301 * -67059 ", "answer": "1629628801", "num_terms": 3, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9994", "question": "-1 * -3 ", "answer": "3", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 1}
{"id": "9995", "question": "88122 * -96681 - 71102 - 29327 ", "answer": "-8519823511", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9996", "question": "342888 + -660838 * -595220 * 186053 ", "answer": "73182830183003968", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
{"id": "9997", "question": "-46451 - -82383 ", "answer": "35932", "num_terms": 2, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9998", "question": "49943 + -43169 * -77015 + 27325 - -29636 ", "answer": "3324767439", "num_terms": 5, "num_digits": 5}
{"id": "9999", "question": "-33338 * 340713 * 384025 + 793886 ", "answer": "-4362020924151964", "num_terms": 4, "num_digits": 6}
